<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="user8">
	<document><![CDATA[PhD defence at University of Ottawa done. We gave him a hard time, but he passed. Very stressed kid, but he is celebrating now.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Jim Flaherty, Canada's former finance minister, is dead at 65. #canada		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If work emails are banned after hours like in France, we would spend the full days just caching up on unread email. http://t.co/UqIp2iuTko		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Teacher Appreciation: Why We Teach - http://t.co/MAzmltn8ia		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A Gentle Introduction to Scikit-Learn: A Python Machine Learning Library - http://t.co/r6dEAVGanz		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The new spring for Artificial Intelligence is definitely here. http://t.co/C6U5klJh3B		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[U.S. Navy researchers turned seawater in fuel (liquid hydrocarbon CO2 + H2). At a larger scale it would replace oil. 
http://t.co/qwqlbyVKw8		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Data never sleeps http://t.co/0l8eB1gReR We definitely need #NLP to automatically analyse, synthesize, summarize the overload of text.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username presented keynote LASM workshop @username  challenges in NLP for social media #EACL2014 very instructive http://t.co/GzVHsbONZT		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I shared this before but can't resist to share it again. Why is X the unknown? The origin of the unknown x http://t.co/ZCTowR88mp		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Scribes Are Back, Helping Doctors Tackle Electronic Medical Records http://t.co/K5B7cpqysB		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Data (information) has only value if you have the ability to do something useful with it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Google continued its acquisition spree http://t.co/JB15RJsT7S		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A manifesto for bringing women in science out of the shadows - http://t.co/qsCCZgqUL1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Double benefit: language for foreigners and companionship for seniors. http://t.co/caaNv2AFBk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Learning from ants to build nano-robots? http://t.co/eSnLz6qvPe		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Visit the working rebuild of #Colossus – the world's first programmable digital electronic computer #Computerfacts http://t.co/4OPVooxqS6		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Two accepts and one reject resulted in a rejected paper at SIGKDD. :-(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Attending as guest the graduation dinner for the school of IT at the university of Sydney Australia #usyd http://t.co/U2WWWqgUQp		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Great invension for #seniors with tremors http://t.co/cu4RyAlbyN		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning at the rescue: a machine as an equal board member of an investment firm. http://t.co/4BBpqJzeA4		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cryptography as we know it is now compromised. http://t.co/TnWmLzaFY2
#cryptography #security		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Bell curve usage is not just at school. Google uses them too. http://t.co/zeIB6kB8Bc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Nano-motors 500 times smaller than a grain of salt. Imagine the possibilities. http://t.co/S1QlSLQ8ii		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[33 meter pool at Bronte beach, Sydney, Australia. 7am May 26 2014 http://t.co/crW6Vrj0Su		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It is beard season in Australia http://t.co/tfPHuoQGpy #Australia #beard #melanoma #skincancerawareness		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Demand for computer science education programs is booming. http://t.co/W6plA4LNyf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Twitter is opening up their entire archives to researchers. #Twitter http://t.co/dmK0BWSVJc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The next battleground for Amazon, Microsoft, Facebook and Google: Artificial Intelligence: http://t.co/jCMOWUEstU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[In the last 12 months, hackers have exposed the personal information of 110 million Americans. http://t.co/vGUU36gdq3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Modular robotics for adaptive furniture that could help the elderly and disabled. http://t.co/y0udXqI778		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[What is Holding you Back From Your Machine Learning Goals? - http://t.co/e3JBiJSIqS		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Alan Turing, the father of computing and Artificial Intelligence, died 60 years ago (June 7, 1954)  http://t.co/AJsfOgPugY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[For an answer to Fermi's paradox, think of aliens 65 million light years away looking at us. They would see Cretaceous Period dinosaurs.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My team got 3 papers accepted at the 2014 IEEE/ACM International Conference on Advances in Social Networks Analysis & Mining. Way to go team		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Humans will miss the Earth if they destroy it. The Earth will not miss humans if the homo sapiens would get extinct." David W. Schindler		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Using Entrepreneurship to Transform Student Work - http://t.co/zB0fo9FCV9		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Google Inc to buy Skybox Imaging satellite maker for US$500-million http://t.co/FwwV2hyuzE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#WorldCup2014  exoskeleton: mind-control robotic suit to help #paraplegic . #robots #machinelearning http://t.co/fFxDYDhVE9		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[U. Alberta isn't listed, yet 99% of my grad students are swallowed by #Microsoft  #Facebook #Google  #Yahoo #Amazon  http://t.co/HZEfBDccGO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Microsoft is trying to popularize Machine Learning. Azure machine learning available in July. #machinelearning 
http://t.co/XjtcBgJY3x		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RapidMiner Scoops Up Radoop For Hadoop Analytics Processing http://t.co/a3RpSrxplz via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The truth about saturated fats.
http://t.co/V0s6YWFR4s via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Robots in our society. #robotics http://t.co/PFguafZNs0		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[For Japanese robots already have a soul. #robots #singularity http://t.co/Yoh664fBPv		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Mining electronic health records. Data Mining helping medicine. #datamining #healthrecord #healthit http://t.co/PhRB5jnbpA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Google is replacing MapReduce with Cloud Data Flow. #dataanalytics  #bigdata #datascience  http://t.co/WzGcKhquf8 #analytics		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why Computers Won’t Be Replacing You Just Yet. #bigdata #machinelearning #nlp #predictiveanalytics http://t.co/JhOakTLZJa		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Poaching of employees between giants: Amazon vs Google and the cloud. http://t.co/bFIX9zX3oA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Communities - http://t.co/fVtIg6H7Ol		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[What to expect from the Android "L" release. http://t.co/jSzsP8YLN8		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why doctors still use pen and paper? #ehealth #healthinformatics #medicalinformatics http://t.co/Xfg4nnKMjf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The first Brazilian generation of power from ocean waves. http://t.co/S9a5Mktoui		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[What is worse Argentina loose against Netherlands & play their arch-rivals Brazil for 3 place or win 2 go 2 finals humiliating Brazil again?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[In the city, it is the first few meters that count. #electriccar http://t.co/f9gNA1uVwI		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sorry for my dear Brazilian friends. I don't want to upset them but this is awesome. The new way to spell Brazil = BRA7-1L #WorldCup2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Robots Learn to Learn from Each Other. #Robotics #ML #machinelearning #AI http://t.co/aM933Lrqpt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Exquisite, beautiful goal. Thank you M. Götze. Couldn't be more wonderful when the stress was at the highest. #WorldCupFinal  #WorldCup		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Acquires Newsle To Deliver More Relevant News About Your Connections - http://t.co/c0d63NANph		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[How machine learning is saving lives while saving hospitals money http://t.co/XVeCRMOJQ4 #machinelearning  #ML #bigdata		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Engineers in city hall Edmonton should watch this video http://t.co/XCXFHycXk1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#Microsoft Deep Learning project ADAM recognizes dogs. #deeplearning #machinelearning http://t.co/ti8ia3qUWq		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Is it really a new age of artificial intelligence? Is Deep Learning another hype? #deeplearning #machinelearning #ai http://t.co/wl6JIWIoi3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[PredictionIO an open source Machine Learning server. #machinelearning http://t.co/2UT475Wg5B		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#Google to use #bigdata to map what a healthy human being should be. #healthinformatics http://t.co/ef989W7W11		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[NLTK 3.0 out. http://t.co/5HdPh6wtrN #nlp #BigData  #DataAnalytics		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Russ Greiner and some of his internatioal summer students at AICML. http://t.co/XdJhFcfNCF #aicml #uofa #machinelearning		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[An artificial leaf that produces oxygen from water and light. http://t.co/FHGqlKWHKH		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Presented today our paper on Speech Act Identification at Concordia University.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Robin Williams Crazy First Appearance on Johnny C…: http://t.co/9pgg6571un		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My student defended with high colours his thesis on identifying animals from camera trap images. Congrats! #machinelearning		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Representing University of Alberta at the World Universities Network in Rochester NY for Exploratory Workshop on BigData #bigdata #ualberta		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Brain Augmentation: What's the Deal? - Bubblews http://t.co/eGes1ZvQNV via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Completion rate for #MOOCs  is very low because MOOCs simply repackage & extend the lecture format. Will that change? http://t.co/BCNPKkgStz		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Towards a Deep-Learning Doctor? You'd be the judge. #bigdata  #DataScience  #machinelearning  http://t.co/tK3PMzvMks		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[On my way to #ACM SIGKDD in New York. For the first time the conference is sold out. 2200 registered at #KDD2014. http://t.co/VVPo6vRe1N		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Went through #kdd2014 registration today. I predict registration tomorrow morning will be chaotic given the record number of registrants.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My ticket to enter the Blomberg building in New York tomorrow for #kdd2014 events. My former student works there. http://t.co/maYmkbfieu		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Listening to an excellent talk by Submit Gutwani on automatic question and feedback generation for student assessment (ASSESS #kdd2014 )		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Submit Gulwani Microsoft computer technologies can automate repetitive tasks in education: problem, solution & feedback generation #kdd2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[S. Gulwani, Example-Based Learning in Computer-Aided STEM Education | August 2014 | Communications of the ACM http://t.co/qGiZ4ECXow		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[About recommender systems. @username  my tastes can't be reduced to a vector in a feature space. #kdd2014  invited talk.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  at #kdd2014  Key AI tasks cannot be reduced to classification problems. #bigdata  #machinelearning #DeepLearning		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A new way to detect an #earthquake using fitness wristbands. #bigdata  #DataScience  
http://t.co/yX9Ap90wwT		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#kdd2014 Dan Doctoroff CEO Blomberg: "In God we trust; all others bring data". From book Elements of Statistical Learning. #DataScience		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Practical application talk #kdd2014  Inferring Gas Consumption and Pollution Emission of Vehicles throughout a City

http://t.co/suUdd8tfWC		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username #kdd2014  Rule 1/7 Small changes can have a big impact on Metrics. 7 rules of thumb for website experimenters http://t.co/sTU6iWDjop		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[ACMSIGKDD #kdd2014  covered in the news. http://t.co/1kSpatC5ge		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[500 million tweets a day. 10 may be of interest to a client. 1 or 2 may lead to action. #datascience #bigdata 
http://t.co/OwZjYXuv4Q		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Machines read fast & programmed correctly can find things we might never have the time to find ourselves. http://t.co/HFcNHJkGo9 #kdd2014		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#kdd2014 Test of Time Award goes to M. Ester, H-P Kriegel, J. Sander and X. Xu for DBSCAN paper at KDD 1996. #KDD  http://t.co/txNja2gXUj		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#IceBucketChallenge met. Pledge for http://t.co/2k6uvJ9QVY. Now @username @username and Kalina Yacef http://t.co/fuTqUD2iIh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Presented our paper on Discovering Statistically Significant Co-location Rules at DAWAK'14 Intl Conf Data Warehousing & Knowledge Discovery		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[On stage receiving a surprise appreciation present on the 25th of DEXA conference. http://t.co/ZQjAoDYNDD		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hiring Data Scientists: What to look for? #bigdata #datascience http://t.co/nRQlSevbvb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#HeForShe campaign: Emma Watson, at UN speech, tells men to fight for gender equality. Take action. http://t.co/vtIVCDeMrB		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[NASA Invents a Folding Solar Panel Inspired by Origami | WIRED http://t.co/ZR4y8hsUTh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Out in the Open: The Site That Teaches You to Code Well Enough to Get a Job | WIRED http://t.co/AOggouwOA1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I just committed to stand up for gender equality.  #HeForShe
I am number 54,259. Will you join me? @username http://t.co/FpXQPgJN35		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Good Morning Dave. You are looking well today. Home security, Machine Learning at the rescue #machinelearning http://t.co/r8UWAgzMct		]]></document>
</author>