 eh ehh hh. h.. ... ..  . b  bo boo ook oks ks  s o  on on  n m  my myt yth tho hol olo log ogy gy, y,  , t  th tha hat at  t i  is is. s.  . i  i  i k  kn kno now ow  w i  i  i s  sh sho hou oul uld ld  d h  ha hav ave ve  e a  an ans nsw swe wer ere red ed  d t  to to  o a  a  a l  lo lot ot  t o  of of  f h  he hel ell llo lo  o t  tw twe wee eet ets ts  s t  th tha hat at  t i  in inc ncl clu lud ude ded ed  d m  me me  e a  an and nd  d n  no now ow  w n  no not ot  t a  an any nym ymo mor ore re. e.  . i  i  i w  wa was as  s j  ju jus ust st  t t  to too oo  o b  bu bus usy sy  y o  of off ff  f l  la lat ate te  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #s #so sor orr rry ry  y i  i  i d  do don on' n't 't  t a  ag agr gre ree ee. e.  . i  is is  s n  ni nic ice ce, e,  , b  bu but ut  t (  (s (si six ixx xx) x)  ) i  is is  s c  co coo ool ol! l!! !!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y i  is is  s t  to tom omo mor orr rro row ow  w (  (i (i. i.e .e. e.  . h  he her ere re) e), ),  , d  de dec ec. c.  . 4  4t 4th th  h i  i  i m  ma may ay  y n  no not ot  t a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s a  an ans nsw swe wer er  r (  (l (li lik ike ke  e t  th the he  e m  ma man an  n o  of of  f m  my my  y l  li lif ife fe  e d  do doe oes esn snt nt  t a  al alw lwa way ays ys) s), ),  , b  bu but ut  t (  (l (li lik ike ke  e h  hi him im) m)  ) i  i  i s  se see ee  e i  it it  t a  al all ll! l!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? y  yo you ou  u h  ha hav ave ve  e a  a  a n  ni nic ice ce  e b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  to too oo! o!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : n  ne new ew  w f  fa fav avo vor ori rit ite te  e i  in ins nst sta tag agr gra ram am. m.  . y  yo you ou  u h  ha hav ave ve  e o  on one ne? e?‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i  i w  wi wis ish sh! h!! !!! !!  ! s  so so  o e  et ete ter ern rna nal all lly ly  y i  in in  n ?  ?? ??  ? w  wi wit ith th  h y  yo you ou. u.. ... ... ..  . ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th the her ere re' e's 's  s a  a  a v  ve ver ery ry  y t  th thi hin in  n l  li lin ine ne  e b  be bet etw twe wee een en  n f  fa fas ash shi hio ion on  n a  an and nd  d f  fa fak ake ke. e.  . c  ch che hec eck ck  k m  my my  y i  in ins nst sta tag agr gra ram am: m:  : a  a  a n  ni nic ice ce  e p  pi pic ic  c o  of of  f t  th tha hat at  t i  i  i t  tu tur urn rne ned ed  d i  in int nto to  o a  an an  n o  ol old ld  d s  st sty tyl yle le  e p  ph pho hot oto tog ogr gra rap aph ph. h.  . f  fo for or  r t  th the he  e n  ni nic ice ces est st  t #  #p #ph pho hot oto tog ogr gra rap aph phe her er  r o  ou out ut‚ t‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ g  go goo ood od  d r  re rea ead ad! d!  ! y  yo you our ur  r s  si sil ile len enc nce ce  e t  to tow owa war ard rds ds  s m  me me  e i  is is  s d  de dea eaf afe fen eni nin ing ng. g.. ... ..  . #  #u #ur urs rsi sil ile len ent ntu tus usc scr cre rea eam am  m ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ho hop ope pe  e y  yo you ou  u g  ge get et  t t  th the he  e s  st stu tuf uff ff  f o  on on  n t  ti tim ime me  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù m  ma may ayb ybe be  e t  to tod oda day ay, y,  , m  ma may ayb ybe be  e t  to tom omo mor orr rro row ow. w.. ... ..  . ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #b #bl bli lis iss ss  s i  is is  s t  th the he  e n  ne new ew  w m  ma mag agi gic ic  c w  wo wor ord rd. d.  . b  bl bli lis iss ss  s i  is is  s a  as as  s o  ol old ld  d a  as as  s t  th the he  e w  wo wor orl rld ld. d.  . b  bl bli lis iss ss  s i  is is  s w  wi wit ith thi hin in  n e  ev eve ver ery ryo yon one ne  e o  of of  f u  us us. s.  . l  lo loo ook ok  k f  fo for or  r i  it it. t.  . f  fi fin ind nd  d i  it it! t!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? 1  11 11: 1:1 :11 11  1 a  am am  m r  ri rig igh ght ht  t h  he her ere re  e r  ri rig igh ght ht  t n  no now ow. w.  . m  ma mak ake ke  e a  a  a w  wi wis ish sh! h!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  it it' t's 's  s b  be bea eau aut uty ty. y.  . i  it it' t's 's  s s  st str tre ren eng ngt gth th. h.  . i  it it' t's 's  s w  wi wis isd sdo dom om. m.  . #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : t  th thi his is  s i  is is  s o  on one ne  e o  of of  f t  th the he  e b  be bes est st  t m  m/ m/‚ /‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù w  wh wha hat at  t a  ab abo bou out ut  t m  my my  y l  la lat ate tes est st  t e  ed edi dit it? t?  ? ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? h  ha hap app ppy py  y f  fc fck ckn kn  n b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay, y,  , ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? t  to tom omo mor orr rro row ow  w i  is is  s m  my my  y #  #b #bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y a  an and nd  d j  ju jus ust st  t n  no now ow, w,  , t  th the he  e p  po pos ost st  t d  de del eli liv ive ver ery ry  y m  ma man an  n d  de del eli liv ive ver ere red ed  d a  a  a b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y p  pr pre res ese sen ent nt  t f  fr fro rom om‚ m‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ i  i  i a  am am  m n  no now ow  w f  fo fol oll llo low owi win ing ng  g p  pe peo eop opl ple le, e,  , ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? c  co coo ool ol  l o  on ons nst sta tag age ge  e p  ph pho hot oto to  o o  of of  f y  yo you ou, u,  , a  an and nd  d ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #r #ri rip ipm pmo mot otl tle ley eyc ycr cru rue ue  e c  co cou oul uld ld  d u  u  u c  cr cre rea eat ate te  e s  so son ong ngs gs  s w  wi wit ith th  h t  th thi his is  s s  sp spi pir iri rit itu tua ual al  l t  th the hem eme me? e?  ? #  #e #es esp spe pec eci cia ial all lly lyh yho hop ope pe  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? a  ar are re  e y  yo you ou  u g  ge get ett tti tin ing ng  g i  in ins nsp spi pir ira rat ati tio ion on  n f  fo for or  r n  ne new ew  w m  mu mus usi sic ic  c f  fr fro rom om  m j  jo jos ose sep eph ph  h c  ca cam amp mpb pbe bel ell ll, l,  , n  ni nik ikk kki ki? i?  ? i  it it' t's 's  s s  st sti til ill ll  l e  ea ear arl rly ly  y i  in int nto to  o d  de dec ec. c.  . 4  4, 4,  , b  bu but ut  t t  to tod oda day ay  y i  is is  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y &  &  & i  i' i'm 'm  m s  so so  o h  ha hap app ppy py  y t  to to  o b  be be  e a  al ali liv ive ve! e!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : y  ye yes es‚ s‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù m  my myt yth tho hol olo log ogy gy  y i  is is  s p  pa par art rt  t o  of of  f m  my my  y w  wo wor ork rk. k.  . i  i' i'm 'm  m a  a  a c  cl cla las ass ssi sic ici cis ist st. t.? .?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  to tod oda day ay  y i  is is  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay. y.  . g  ge get ett tti tin ing ng  g a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y f  fr fro rom om  m m  my my  y f  fa fav av  v m  mu mus usi sic ici cia ian an  n &  &  & c  cr cre rea eat ati tiv ive ve  e i  in ins nsp spi pir ira rat ato tor or  r w  wo wou oul uld ld  d b  be be  e s  so so  o n  ni nic ice ce! e!  ! t  ty ty  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou  u ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : "  "h "he hey ey  y r  ro ros ose se, e,  , h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  to to  o y  yo you ou! u!" !"  " ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! x  xo xo  o ?  ?? ??  ? f  fi fig igs gs  s v  vi vis isi sio ion on! n!  ! i  i  i w  wi wis ish sh  h y  yo you ou  u a  a  a g  go goo ood od  d n  ni nig igh ght ht. t.  . t  to tod oda day ay  y f  fo for or  r m  me me, e,  , d  de dec ec. c.  . i  is is  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay. y.  . c  ca can an  n i  i  i g  ge get et  t a  a  a "  "h "ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay" y"  " w  wi wis ish sh  h f  fr fro rom om  m y  yo you ou, u,  , p  pl ple lea eas ase se? e?  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay? y?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  tw twe wee eet et  t f  fr fro rom om  m w  wo wou oul uld ld  d b  be be  e w  wo won ond nde der erf rfu ful ul! l!! !!  ! p  pl ple lea eas ase se  e w  wi wis ish sh  h m  me me  e a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay, y,  , n  ni nik ikk kki ki? i?  ? i  it it' t's 's  s t  to tod oda day ay  y :  :) :)  ) t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou  u f  fo for or  r y  yo you our ur  r b  be bes est st  t w  wi wis ish she hes es, s,  , j  ja jam ami mie ie! e!! !!  ! x  xo xox oxo xo  o ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y r  ro ros ose se‚ e‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! x  xx xx  x ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay‚ y‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! t  to tod oda day ay  y i  is is  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay. y.  . i  i' i'm 'm  m e  en enj njo joy oyi yin ing ng  g i  it it. t.  . i  it it  t w  wo wou oul uld ld  d b  be be  e o  ou out uts tst sta tan and ndi din ing ng  g i  if if  f y  yo you ou  u p  po pos ost ste ted ed  d a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  tw twe wee eet et  t t  to to  o m  me me. e.  . p  pl ple lea eas ase se? e?  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : l  li lif ife fe  e i  is is  s n  no not ot  t a  ab abo bou out ut  t w  wh who ho  o h  hu hur urt rt  t y  yo you ou  u a  an and nd  d b  br bro rok oke ke  e y  yo you ou  u d  do dow own wn. n.  . i  it it' t's 's  s a  ab abo bou out ut  t w  wh who ho  o w  wa was as  s a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s t  th the her ere re  e a  an and nd  d w  wh who ho  o m  ma mad ade de  e y  yo you ou  u s  sm smi mil ile le  e a  ag agi gin in" n"  " f  fu fun unn nny ny. y.  . i  i  i c  ca can an' n't 't  t l  lo loa oad ad  d y  yo you our ur  r p  po pos ost st  t o  on on  n m  my my  y i  in ins nst sta tag agr gra ram am. m.  . i  is is  s m  my my  y i  in ins nst sta tag agr gra ram am  m l  la lag agg ggi gin ing ng? g?  ? h  hm hmm mm, m,  , m  mu mus ust st  t b  be be. e.. ... ..  . #  #w #wt wtf tf  f ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : y  ye yes es  s i  i  i t  th thi hin ink nk  k i  in ins nst stg tgr gra ram am  m i  is is  s l  la lag agg ggi gin ing ng  g .  .. ... ..  . n  ne nee eed eds ds  s t  th the he  e ?  ?? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äùy ùyu yup up  p y  yu yup up! p!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  it it' t's 's  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y a  an and nd  d i  i  i s  sm smi mil ile le  e i  if if  f i  i  i w  wa wan ant nt  t t  to to. o.. ... ... ..  . c  ca can an  n i  i  i h  ha hav ave ve  e a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  b- b-d -da day ay  y f  fr fro rom om  m y  yo you ou? u?  ? #  #p #pl ple lee eez ez  z t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s i  in int nte ter ere res est sti tin ing ng! g!  ! i  id idk dk  k w  wh why hy  y i  i  i l  li lik ike ke  e t  th the he  e t  te ter erm rmi min ina nat ato tor or. r.  . m  ma may ayb ybe be  e b  be bec eca cau aus use se  e o  of of  f t  th the he  e s  sa sal alv lva vat ati tio ion on  n t  th tho hou oug ugh ght ht  t t  th tha hat at' t's 's  s a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s t  th the her ere re  e h  ha hap app ppy py  y h  ho hol oli lid ida day ays ys! s!  ! w  wh why hy  y i  i  i c  ca car are re? e?  ? b  be bec eca cau aus use se  e i  i  i l  lo lov ove ve. e.  . i  i' i'm 'm  m h  ha hav avi vin ing ng  g a  an an  n a  aw awe wes eso som ome me  e b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y a  an and nd  d i  i  i c  ca can an' n't 't  t w  wa wai ait it  t f  fo for or  r t  th the he  e #  #s #si six ixx xxs xse sen ens nse se  e s  sh sho how ow  w t  to tod oda day ay! y!! !!? !?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!  ! j  ja jay ay  y z  z, z,  , t  ty tyr yra ra  a b  ba ban ank nks ks, s,  , a  an and nd  d j  je jef eff ff  f b  br bri rid idg dge ges es  s s  sh sha har are re  e a  a  a b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y w  wi wit ith th  h y  yo you ou! u!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nks ks  s a  ag aga gai ain in, n,  , h  ha hah aha hah aha ha! a!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : .  .  . h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  to to  o y  yo you ou  u g  gi gir irl rl  l :  :- :-) -)‚ )‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y !  !  ! i  i  i h  ho hop ope pe  e i  it it  t w  wa was as  s a  aw awe wes eso som ome me? e?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  it it  t w  wa was as! s!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? m  my my  y b  bd bda day ay  y i  is is  s t  to tod oda day ay, y,  , b  bu but ut  t s  si sin inc nce ce  e t  th thi his is  s m  mo mon ont nth th  h i  is is  s a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s o  on one ne  e b  bi big ig  g p  pa par art rty ty  y a  af aff ffa fai air ir  r w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the he  e h  ho hol oli lid ida day ays ys  s a  an and nd  d m  ma man any ny  y b  bd bda day ays ys, s,  , i  i' i'l 'll ll  l s  st str tre ret etc tch ch  h m  mi min ine ne  e u  un unt nti til il  l d  de dec ec  c 3  31 31. 1.. ..  . l  lo lol ol  l t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou, u,  , d  da daw awn wn! n!! !!  ! i  i  i w  wa wan ant nt  t t  to to  o t  th tha han ank nk  k a  al all ll  l m  my my  y f  fr fri rie ien end nds ds  s o  on onl nli lin ine ne  e &  &  & o  of off ffl fli lin ine ne  e f  fo for or  r a  al all ll  l t  th the hei eir ir  r n  ni nic ice ce  e &  &  & b  be bes est st  t w  wi wis ish she hes es  s f  fo for or  r m  me me  e o  on on  n m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!! !!! !!  ! #  #t #th tha han ank nky kyo you ou  u ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! i  it it' t's 's  s v  ve ver ery ry  y v  ve ver ery ry  y e  ea ear arl rly ly  y i  in int nto to  o d  de dec ec. c.  . a  an and nd  d a  af aft fte ter er  r s  so som ome me  e s  sl sle lee eep ep  p i  i' i'm 'm  m v  ve ver ery ry  y m  mu muc uch ch  h a  aw awa wak ake ke! e!  ! #  #l #lo lol ol  l a  an and nd  d t  th the he  e n  ni nig igh ght ht  t b  be bef efo for ore re  e s  st st. t.  . n  ni nic ich cho hol ola las as' s'  ' b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e g  gi giv ive ve  e e  ea eac ach cho hot oth the her er  r g  gi gif ift fts ts  s i  in in  n n  nl nl. l.  . i  it it' t's 's  s c  ca cal all lle led ed  d s  st st. t.  . n  ni nic ich cho hol ola las as' s'  ' e  ev eve ve  e &  &  & g  gi gif ift fts ts  s e  ev eve ve! e!  ! d  de dec ec. c.  . t  th tha hat at  t i  is is. s.  . e  es esp spe pec eci cia ial all lly ly  y f  fo for or  r k  ki kid ids ds, s,  , t  th thi his is  s i  is is  s o  on one ne  e o  of of  f t  th the he  e y  ye yea ear ar' r's 's  s e  ep epi pic ic  c e  ev eve ven eni nin ing ngs gs! s!  ! a  an and nd  d t  th thi his is  s i  is is  s o  of of  f t  th the he  e r  re rea eas aso son ons ns  s w  wh why hy  y i  i  i l  lo lov ove ve  e h  hi him im: m:  : h  he he' e's 's  s s  so so  o p  pa pas ass ssi sio ion ona nat ate te  e a  ab abo bou out ut  t w  wh wha hat at  t h  he he  e l  lo lov ove ves es  s t  to to  o d  do do! o!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : l  li lif ife fe' e's 's  s p  pr pro rob obl ble lem ems ms  s w  wo wou oul uld ldn dn' n't 't  t b  be be  e c  ca cal all lle led ed  d "  "h "hu hur urd rdl dle les es" s"  " i  if if  f t  th the her ere re  e w  wa was asn sn' n't 't  t a  a  a w  wa way ay  y t  to to  o g  ge get et  t o  ov ove ver er  r t  th the hem em. m.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!! !!! !!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : w  wh whe hen en  n i  is is  s y  yo you our ur  r b  b  b d  da day ay? y?‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù d  de dec ec  c 4  4. 4.  . f  fo for or  r m  me me  e t  th tha hat at' t's 's  s a  al alr lre rea ead ady dy  y y  ye yes est ste ter erd rda day ay  y ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : i  i  i t  th tho hou oug ugh ght ht  t i  it it  t w  wa was as  s m  mi mig igh ght hty ty  y a  at att ttr tra rac act cti tiv ive ve  e l  lo lol ol‚ l‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  it it' t's 's  s a  a  a m  ma mat att tte ter er  r o  of of  f o  op opi pin ini nio ion on. n.. ... ..b .bu but ut  t f  fo for or  r m  me me, e,  , e  eh ehh hhh hh. h.. ... ..n .no no. o.  . #  #l #lo lol ol  l o  of of  f c  co cou our urs rse se  e i  i  i d  do do  o a  an and nd  d i  i  i a  ag agr gre ree ee  e t  to to  o t  th tha hat at! t!  ! h  ha hah aha hah aha ha! a!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  is is  s t  th the her ere re  e s  so som ome met eth thi hin ing ng  g y  yo you ou  u s  st sti til ill ll  l h  ha hav ave ve  e t  to to  o p  ph pho hot oto tog ogr gra rap aph ph? h?  ? #  #a #as ask sks ksi six ixx xx  x i  it it' t's 's  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  to tod oda day ay. y.  . p  pl ple lea eas ase se  e w  wi wis ish sh  h m  me me  e a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay? y?  ? #  #a #as ask sks ksi six ixx xx  x n  ne nev eve ver er  r d  do do  o s  st ste ter ero roi oid ids ds  s n  ni nik ikk kki ki. i.  . t  th the hey ey  y w  wi wil ill ll  l k  ki kil ill ll  l y  yo you ou. u.  . t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou, u,  , r  ro rod odn dne ney ey! y!! !!  ! i  it it  t s  su sur ure re  e w  wo wou oul uld ld  d b  be be! e!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôv ôve ve  e b  be bee een en  n a  aw awa way ay  y f  fo for or  r a  a  a w  wh whi hil ile le. e.  . n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g p  pe per ers rso son ona nal al. l.  . t  to tod oda day ay  y i  is is  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y &  &  & a  a  a s  sp spe pec eci cia ial al  l d  da day ay  y #  #n #ni nik ikk kki kit iti tim ime me  e w  w/ w/  / i  i' i'm 'm  m a  a  a w  wo wom oma man an, n,  , r  ro rod odn dne ney ey. y.  . ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? g  go goo ood od  d n  ni nig igh ghf hf  f a  an and nd  d t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou  u f  fo for or  r f  fa fav avi vin ing ng  g o  on one ne  e o  of of  f m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  tw twe wee eet ets ts  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ho hop ope pe  e y  yo you ou  u h  ha had ad  d a  a  a g  gr gre rea eat at  t b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou, u,  , y  ye yes es  s i  i  i d  di did id! d!! !!! !!  ! i  i' i'm 'm  m g  go gon onn nna na  a g  ge get et  t t  th the he  e n  ne new ew  w a  al alb lbu bum um  m s  so soo oon on! n!  ! a  a  a #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t o  of of  f y  yo you ou  u &  &  & #  #l #le lei eic ica cas asi six ixx xx  x a  an and nd  d a  a  a l  le len ens ns. s.  . i  i  i t  th tho hou oug ugh ght ht  t y  yo you ou' u'd 'd  d l  li lik ike ke  e t  th the he  e c  co com omb mbi bin ina nat ati tio ion on  n ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppi pin ine nes ess ss  s d  do doe oes esn sn' n't 't  t r  re res esu sul ult lt  t f  fr fro rom om  m w  wh wha hat at  t w  we we  e g  ge get et, t,  , b  bu but ut  t f  fr fro rom om  m w  wh wha hat at  t w  we we  e g  gi giv ive ve. e.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i' i'm 'm  m n  no not ot  t #  #f #ff ff  f -  -i -in ing ng  g t  to tod oda day ay, y,  , '  'c 'ca cau aus use se  e i  i  i g  go got ot  t a  a  a l  lo lot ot  t t  to to  o d  do do, o,  , b  bu but ut  t t  th the her ere re' e's 's  s o  of of  f c  co cou our urs rse se  e o  on one ne  e g  gu guy uy  y t  th tha hat at  t a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s g  ge get ets ts  s a  a  a #  #s #sh sho hou out uto tou out ut  t :  :  : .  .. ... ... ... ... ..? .?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? a  a  a b  bi big ig  g m  me meg ega ga  a #  #s #sh sho hou out uto tou out ut  t f  fo for or  r t  th the he  e o  on one ne  e a  an and nd  d o  on onl nly ly  y !  !! !!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? n  no no  o #  #m #mo mod ode der ern rnv nvi vin int nta tag age ge  e a  ar are re  e t  th the hey ey  y c  cr cra raz azy zy? y?? ??? ??? ??  ? a  aw awe wes eso som ome me! e!  ! r  re rea eal al  l g  gu gui uit ita tar ar  r s  st stu tuf uff ff! f!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : t  th thi his is  s i  is is  s a  a  a w  wo won ond nde der erf rfu ful ul  l p  pi pic ic! c!! !!! !!! !!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k u  u  u h  ha hah aha hah aha ha! a!  ! w  wh whe hen en  n c  co com ome mes es  s i  in in  n a  an and nd  d e  en ent nte ter ers rs  s t  th the he  e p  pa par art rty ty! y!  ! #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? g  go got ot  t i  it it! t!  ! #  #i #it itu tun une nes es  s #  #c #cd cd  d #  #7 #7" 7"s "si sin ing ngl gle le  e j  ju jus ust st  t n  no not ot  t y  ye yet et: t:  : t  th the he  e #  #v #vi vin iny nyl yla lal alb lbu bum um  m ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  in in  n m  my my  y #  #w #wi wis ish shl hli lis ist st  t f  fo for or  r #  #s #si six ixx xxm xma mas as  s !  !! !!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? b  be bet etw twe wee een en  n y  yo you our ur  r b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y a  an and nd  d x  xm xma mas as! s!  ! o  on on  n m  my my  y #  #w #wi wis ish shl hli lis ist st  t !  !  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? n  ni nik ikk kki ki, i,  , c  ca can an  n w  we we  e p  pr pre re- e-o -or ord rde der er  r t  th the he  e #  #v #vi vin iny nyl yl  l #  #m #mo mod ode der ern rnv nvi vin int nta tag age ge  e ?  ?? ??  ? w  wh whe hen en  n w  wa wal alk lks ks  s i  in int nto to  o a  a  a r  ro roo oom om. m.. ... ..  . #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? s  se sen end nd  d m  me me  e t  th the he  e p  pi pic ic  c y  yo you ou  u w  wa wan ant nt  t e  ed edi dit ite ted ed  d a  an and nd  d i  i' i'l 'll ll  l m  ma mak ake ke  e i  it it  t f  fo for or  r y  yo you ou  u c  ca can an  n w  we we  e p  pr pre re- e-o -or ord rde der er  r t  th the he  e #  #v #vi vin iny nyl yl  l v  ve ver ers rsi sio ion on  n o  of of  f #  #m #mo mod ode der ern rnv nvi vin int nta tag age ge  e ?  ?  ? w  wi wil ill ll  l i  it it  t b  be be  e a  av ava vai ail ila lab abl ble le  e o  on on  n y  yo you ou' u'r 're re  e w  we wel elc lco com ome me  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #t #ta tag aga gar art rt  t #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? y  yo you ou' u'r 're re  e w  we wel elc lco com ome me! e!  !    