Unless they talk to me first. Then its like everything is let loose Today's my 18th birthday! I’m inviting you to open a shop on Etsy. Use my link to list your first items free. http://t.co/rQ7GwgJTAa via @username Check out my etsy store! http://t.co/DfHxvwJ9dc Hand made iphone case by me on Etsy https://t.co/LxWrgEfaJu Handmade infinity scarf by me!  https://t.co/7KvdF289Ng via @username Check out this scarf I made!  https://t.co/7KvdF289Ng I am so happy with my tattoo! Its getting very itchy though This is the first of many more to come #tattoo #quote http://t.co/keMlhZE4yp I really want to care about what I look like (hair+makeup) but it actually takes a lot of time+effort to make my face look good Its so boring waiting for someone to wake up when they are right next to you I really want black acrylic nails! There is a girly side to me after all Watching The Texas Chainsaw Massacre has def convince me never to give people ride in places you don't know I really want to go blonde but I know I wont keep up with the roots so my little air balloon of an idea just crashed and burned Does writing in caps make it look like I an shouting at the teacher? http://t.co/16IENtiVto Which is your fave? ( Ignore the table) #nailart http://t.co/cCFVy0DMT4 Its so fing cold, but no storms or even rain Guess what Im watching?! http://t.co/J8yRauUZuz I really want to lose weight and be who I really am, with winged eyeliner and red lipstick, but then I remember I go to school with (c) (C) with fucking idiots who bully you if you have more confidence than them, or enough confidence to be different. So I just sit at home with no confidence being someone who Im not so I wont be bullied like I have for about 99% of my life This is so accurate http://t.co/IJcCjqo3iv Goodnight everyone! I just found out I have 1 new UnFollowers on Twitter using Tweet Sponge! http://t.co/lh6tT9zznm Morning! :) Nobody puts Baby in the corner Found a new game! Its called Map of the Dead, but I thinks its only for iphone...? http://t.co/6yNvLI34a4 Omg O have pins and needles in my feet I cant walk savee meee Going for a walk with a real life friend! Wow I am so proud of myself I just found out I have 1 new followers on Twitter using Tweet Sponge! http://t.co/lh6tT9zznm @username I am probably too late, but please don't. I know its not enough, and I'm just a stranger, but please. I just found out I have 1 new UnFollowers on Twitter using Tweet Sponge! http://t.co/lh6tT9zznm Happy #InternationalWomensDay  to my fellow women :) If I could change myself right now and be who I really am on the outside and not just inside I would do it in a heartbeat Lazy day watching movies in bed #nomakeup #natural http://t.co/BBvuDculUG Time to treat my skin and hair a little better I think. Dye and harsh chemicals don't do it any favors! http://t.co/UU9sxVeVqR I just found out I have 1 new followers on Twitter using Tweet Sponge! http://t.co/lh6tT9zznm Choc filled donut #yum #healthy haha http://t.co/NFbDli9bxj This is such a bad photo but doesn't matter. This little pup weighed under 20 kg when we found her,… http://t.co/vg2OpdsqNJ Redoing my hair bc it looks shit at the mo and I feel better with long hair I hate it when people who supposedly love you make you feel like shit I am falling into the black hole of misery I just found out I have 1 new followers on Twitter using Tweet Sponge! http://t.co/lh6tT9zznm Check out my shop! http://t.co/JEwHCL5G2h  #etsy #shop http://t.co/BqvvaDDdlv Today is not my day Go check out my etsy store at http://t.co/JEwHCL5G2h or @username Exactly http://t.co/l5V4WyY0D0 39 tweets to go for 500 tweets! Time to care a little for my skin an hair instead of harming it with harsh chemicals and not letting it heal http://t.co/7YvVwj3hFz http://t.co/JEwHCL5G2h have a look! I just found out I have 1 new followers on Twitter using Tweet Sponge! http://t.co/lh6tT9zznm Pancakes for breakfast! I don't know whats been going on about this earthquake but I hope everyone is okay Why do you care what people think? Are you hooked up to their leash? I have fallen in love with green tea Please check out my shop? http://t.co/JEwHCL5G2h it would mean alot if youd tell me what you think #Etsy #Etsyshop I passed all my classes! Yay! Just another three to four months of torture then summer! Great Friday night with the girls! Love to know who the guy on chat roulette we did foot porn to was Shot bingo was cool http://t.co/Srr9WUhAZ3 Lots of walking today! Check out my shop? #Etsy #Etsyshop http://t.co/JEwHCL5G2h During the week I have classes, So I am not awake at 3 in the morning please stop fucking texting expecting me to awnser! Sometimes the people who talk a lot are the people who should shut it and sit in a corner I really want this year to speed up about 4 months Cant wait to move in with the boyf, I will be a domestic goddess! Relaxing bath after a productive day at school. http://t.co/fFwLndVHQQ I just found out I have 3 new UnFollowers on Twitter using Tweet Sponge! http://t.co/lh6tT9zznm Yesterday I was the ONLY student in my class. There were only two other students in the entire schoool But I found out a guy from the year below me has great music taste. Don't you want somebody to love? Don't you need somebody to love? I always feel like somebody is watching me I don't want a guy to treat me like a princess, I just want someone who actually cares and tries. Its time to sink or swim Thank god its friday Have you ever not noticed something until someone points it out and then you can never unnotice it and it really pisses you off? Slender Man and Barney Stinson http://t.co/D6slpja6eB I’m inviting you to open a shop on Etsy. Use my link to list your first items free. http://t.co/WS3WYdtNng vía @username Watching #twilight while doing homework. Daydreaming New exciting things are going up on my etsy shop soon! Watching Jaws. The worst part is when the dog doesn't come back :( We're gonna need a bigger boat I feel like an adult because I have to do my own stuff now, and I have to sign everything without my parents. But then I still feel like whats the point because I still live with my parents, I am still in college, studying for my car and no job. Would piercing and tattooing be considered within the "personal image" sector of working? #asktwitter Pissed at my license school right now. They've given me the password and username so I can do tests online, but they've (c) (C) forgotten to actually give me the fucking tests. I sign in and its completely blanc. How the fuck am I meant to do them? Watching barbie fairytopia with my boyfs niece I really want a full makeover, but I have no money and I need to lose weight. There should be a test or something they make you take at 18 to see if you can be an "adult" yet. You know its coming up to eater when the creme eggs come out in the shops http://t.co/qzUTBSkBFe Im getting old already! I shouldn't have a bad back at 18 Making pancakes for the family. Sunny today :) http://t.co/fufP9q919p Horror movie marathon I want a bigger room and a double bed Make that a super king size bed please Insidious Chapter 2 with @username  :) The black bride bit is a little fucked up... This is really confusing 