@username SO punny! Also I can't come up with anything other than Blues Clues. :) What a terribly productive day @username taught me a new way to count to four. I hope Sue Collie is proud #oneonethree :) Hands down best party of my junior year #NIFAafterparty #thereisnoplacelikenebraska Boarding an airplane for the very first time in a few hours! #nervous Embarrassed myself by having a literal panic attack right before takeoff, but I'm in the keys now and it's beautiful here #ocean :) Something I've learned about Keys locals: It is perfectly normal to bike down the street dressed as a pirate. After tanning beachside, snorkling above coral reef & drinking rum on a boat, I just don't think I'm coming back to Nebraska, guys #paradise @username @username I miss you both so much! We need a family dinner asap when we're reunited :) Ready to see some dolphins today. DOLPHINS. #DOLPHINCITY You know what I miss? http://t.co/HCqJzRB You know that panicky lady that Kristen Wigg had to sit by on the airplane in "Bridesmaids"? That's me. #gladtobeonland Never having @username help me study for Geology again #relativedatingpuns bed. i missed you Just made myself the best dinner I've eaten in 2 weeks. Now to clean my room and watch a Ryan Gosling movie It seriously made my day to be greeted with "Kelkie you home!" and a massive hug from all 6 of my Teddy Bears at once :) "They roared their terrible roars, they rolled their terrible eyes, they gnashed their terrible teeth, and they showed their terrible claws" Creeping on my geology TA's Facebook. #shereallylovesrocks @username and I are about to take a page from "New Girl" and get a jar for our teamroom #schmidt @username I used to think I liked you, but now I know I love you! #reginafanforlife "I look forward to Lord Tubbington kicking his ecstasy habit" Geo professor just related class material to Titanic @username #neverletgojack Familiarizing myself with Romney's political plans is making me sick to my stomach. I bet Santorum's will actually make me vomit. Guess who finally got a name? "Windy, W-I-N-D-Y." Thankful for such supportive littles.  I love @username and @username :) #familynight Today is a super wonderful great day :) Why is Arrested Development the funniest TV show ever? Some of the tracks from Fun.'s new album are auto tuned... Thanks for ruining one of my favorite bands, Fueled by Ramen. It's ASUN day, UNL! Get out there and vote #fusion! @username Is it the same person that will call me whilst watching @username? :) Another good day ahead :) @username Welll.... what day? :) @username What class is this for? Personally I'd write about how America is afraid of China's economy :) @username ROUGH! Well good luck :) Sex and sexuality lesson in lecture today.... Everyone is making this so much more awkward than it needs to be #wereincollageguys @username sorry I'm hastily tweeting :) My dad got a new puppy!!!!!!!! I get to see her this weekend!!!!! Ahhhh!!!!!!!!! How have I lived my life before putting hot coco into my coffee? Omg how many passive aggressive hints do I have to drop tonight? #gtfobitch I just woke up in my own bed, it's Saturday, and I don't have an obligation to speak about anything. #weird #speechproblems Tonight I had prime rib and wine for dinner, played with a puppy, got into my program, and I'm about to roll up to NIFAdos #bestnightEVER Dear Team Meatball (@username @username), Who can tell me how exactly we became "Team Meatball?" Sincerely, your fellow meatballer @username Omg. I'm making brownies. Right. Now. Weird..... God I love the rec #ellipticaltweet @username we're definitely making time to hang out more:) #ilovemylil I just ruined my favorite new dress. #imgoingtocry Seriously jazzed about my future right now Sick of beating around the bush with these scholarship essays. I just want to say "I'm way more fucking awesome than everyone else applying" So pumped to babysit in celebration of St. Patrick's day. #not21 #eighteendays I can be a really great schmoozer sometimes Leather-braided belt, leather-braided sandals, leather-braided bracelet. Too much? Look who I drove next to on the interstate to Omaha? @username @username #huneds #rackcity http://t.co/eEGDets My vanity makes my wallet cry @username Why are you changing them to RTF? SEE I'VE BEEN WAITING ALLLLL DAYYYYY FOR YOU TO CALL ME BAYYBAYYYYYY I wish I were in Harry Potter land with @username I'm about to change my middle name to "Doin'it". Just one word. "Doin'it". Best weekend ever. I couldn't have imagined a better last hurrah as a minor. #glowpaint #technofun. @username your new twit pic is adorrraablleee! @username @username My account is "protected". But YES family night before I leave for Texas!! Can't wait for @username to come home and make fried dough #nomnomnom @username @username I leave on my 21st, the 4th, for speech nationals! I'll be gone for a week! @username @username both? :) Bashar Al-Assad? More like Bashir Al- ASSad #amirightguys @username O MY GOD MY STRAIGHTER JUST BURNED OUT I THINK MY LIFE IT OVER Couple on campus is holding hands... While riding their bikes. #hipsterpda My sister is 20 today!! For the next seven days, we are the same age :) HAPPY BIRTHDAY @username :) I am walking death @username my health My teammates are SO FUNNY #peercoachinglove :) Why did I think it was ok to run after I've been sick all week? And why haven't I picked up my dry cleaning yet?? #dumbblondeday Speech: Real Talk. #ijustgotschooled Pink eye, two ear infections, and a never-ending sinus infection. #didibreakarecord I wish my local Walgreen's Pharmacy had a frequent visitor punch card Heellllooooo last day of being a minor :) Today is already awesome :) @username is the best :) #21 Microwaved shot at 7am @username   :) #21 #gettinbelig It's. So. Hot. Here. #SanMarcosTX #AFA12 Chick-fil-A changed my life @username I'm following you again! :) Texas was fun, but I'm so happy to be home http://t.co/uCF6nvy My passport came in while I was away! Too bad my last name isn't "Colsow" #spainhereidontcome Well don't I just have the best little :) @username http://t.co/Ise6bdd #thatawkwardmoment when you finally show up to class after not attending for over two weeks #solost #seriouslywhatisgoingon @username A kid fell asleep in Geology today. To wake him up, my professor kicked him Thanks to @username and @username for the best 21st birthday crawl I could've ever imagined #frogspermshots #oliver #ourlives :) @username I like the February 4th entry I've got about two hours to study for an exam for a class that I haven't attended for 3 weeks. Can someone drop an "Eye of the Tiger" beat? Completely infatuated with #TheLumineers thanks to @username @username I'm requesting a live serenade of "One Thing" #onedirectionislikecracktome @username @username We sure are! 10ish, right? I'm starting to like country music now? "There will be no study guide. I'm too much of a heartless bitch to make one. Happy finals and go fuck yourself."-Actual email from my TA @username stopping by the teamroom  with that ipod? :) @username Where did you park my car? @username my phone is dead. meet me in the teamroom at 3:15? Awesome, awesome, awesome formal :) I don't know if you guys noticed, but my most famous relative, Charles Colson, is trending right now. @username Just got sorted into RAVENCLAW! :) @username your tweets made me sign up for Pottermore :) http://t.co/aOjgTwb @username GO 'SKERS!!! I'm so proud of you guys!!! :) :) 