got cover? http://t.co/tPBGf7PA ORSETTO DI SUINO carrefour http://t.co/xiOtl8pr @username I'd love a "she had diamonds on the inside" version. #marcjohns ft. #benharper polemic chiaraland is polemic http://t.co/hf9o74Dq @username is the five-seconds rule true? http://t.co/Rm5hHElN polemic chiaraland is polemic #part2 http://t.co/nFID8flm Norimberga here we come! "Imagine you can drink back the best parts of your past" http://t.co/97QBlBHr got fish? http://t.co/MMbSXeiX There, there. http://t.co/Szn2O95b by @username @username moving to Germany in march! No time/money for London :( (ti spiegherò meglio!) CAUSE NOOOTHING COMPARES TO IUUUUUU That don't impress me much. @username NON. HAI. MAI. MANGIATO. UN. SOFFICINO? hipsters killed the vatican stars http://t.co/SwH5IYyH @username anche, anche. @username rotellina -> settings -> account -> request your archive. @username ops @username surreal men live in surreal houses http://t.co/iq4mXvMO @username Body Mass Index :) "things don't always end as you potato" @username too late. @username ...I WILL! tasteful and moving <3 @username (btw, if all the guys in London are like this, start looking for a job for me there) @username yeah! Anche se il film non l'ho mai visto. case da incubo Ravensburg edition https://t.co/nl9XOdIdsQ @username I could try... Thorsten. @username I'll find out tomorrow! furniture porn http://t.co/C9H05xc1g7 way back home #stripes http://t.co/7PlWs5Xj4z way back home #stripesagain http://t.co/XI0BR06L2O TROVATA CARNE DI CAVALLO NELL'EQUINOZIO Choir of Young Believers: Paralyze http://t.co/3TBDK3ZjPq via @username @username CINQUE ANNI? Thorsten è ENORME. @username this is cool if you need to create a vintage effect for events/video/whatever! http://t.co/FcbzcHZpB7 #milano Just because you're a bit dead inside. http://t.co/0XBl8YwjRg @username if I teleport to London NOW, could you bake this for me..? #WANT https://t.co/pgGe5Fsr1R on saturday I don't go to school. http://t.co/MWaSuM37kK Gente che meriterebbe un epitaffio in Handwriting Dakota. small truths http://t.co/yDm6T5ziLi @username pic or you didn't bitched. joy factory http://t.co/qFQUVhe0bQ bayern sushi in #munich http://t.co/q7DZgNE0gs @username continuo ad amare i sofficini e a temere Björk, ora more than ever. surfing in Munich http://t.co/KYOb32zmMF ci dobbiamo volere bene, that's all. @username let's go, i'm serious! (where are you, btw?) Castro enjoying the sun http://t.co/iKdKixZO1H Blue sky is overrated. http://t.co/4wLMbvGvDs The grass is always greener on the other side http://t.co/shi6i0vzwe home is where Thorsten destroying stuff is. @username and then he left http://t.co/8Cjq3y1IzS @username forse ce l'ho in studio, qui no! Sorry. Look at that fucking hipster. http://t.co/k4t15FY59f Girls who are boys (who like boys to be girls) http://t.co/32SwztsDKQ @username why? happy family http://t.co/gAXMs3K5AU something, something, something, dark side. Loosing my religion http://t.co/1DloZFLYG9 boardgames and Valpolicella http://t.co/Ay9QANpYfy Weird dreams are made of this http://t.co/29JDpNb8Wa Go with the flow http://t.co/g3X6MfDRCR Here comes the sun http://t.co/WUOuHwDFQC @username ahahah almost right, but unfortunately there´s no proper translation from italian for this... OALD @username is OALD. tivibi. Auguri. in the aeroplane over the beer Ravensburg alternative music scene. http://t.co/vCbV8jxbe3 Self portrait with salad http://t.co/89m9XOlk0d @username strane perversioni su twitter! @username "you can leave your hat on" butter edition? my niece is better than yours http://t.co/wE2232RqhU @username your pijama probably looks muuuuch better than any outfit i saw here today. @username love you and your style <3 @username i'll write you tomorrow... there's a hole on the wall http://t.co/mwfl4p1ERH 6. The Tom Cruise: http://t.co/96JcmN5dyL All I need is blue. http://t.co/M4SReaEhxo You spin me right round baby, right round. http://t.co/ZBO2AwDxsC astenersi perditempo e 500 days of summer. una bella playlist elettronica easy on spotify? @username baffi @username offro io sexy type http://t.co/0odyUNfx41 Ovosodo way of life. @username @username tenetevi forte: non ho mai visto star wars. hello, I love you http://t.co/RhldIoSZGa The Barbonialist. @username wtf? (il whitewalker finale spacca) (anche Khal Drogo) FINALMENTE IN VACANZA http://t.co/r4Ne6GygFo Have you ever thought about just getting a new career?  http://t.co/Waf4SnXtmv @username mh. This is below your standard. @username ma tu non dovresti essere a san francisco wearing some flowers in your hair? Horses are shy too. http://t.co/Sa2FSudWGT Beyond http://t.co/509GvIEXAk @username when? Be right back, went for cake. http://t.co/xvDSlxIr6r 