@username hope so!! The people can be so annoying when they can't do the things u do! I'm extremely awkward Another day in the theater! cmd + shift + @username ???? I have serious problems with him! @username as long you feel the same for you, that's so far to be weird. Star wars makes me happy???????? CHVRCHES - The Mother We Share: http://t.co/aXpscgoPod ???????? The way is long but u can make it easy on mee!! That's exactly what I need it Sorry twitter if I don't write,  but I have a life to enjoy So .. don't miss me Aragorn son of Arathorn heir the throne of isildur King of gondor ... All or nothing. Right now the world looks so exciting I want to see the world,  follow a map to its edges and keep going. Forgot the plans, trust my instincts, let curiosity be my guide ???? No answers is an answer Coffee morning? It was enough, more than enough!! How many people can make you feel extraordinary? Mi life only goes in one direction ... forward. I'm soo far to be OK with that!???? @username nothing in here? This is my month!!! That was so cruel You're such a heavenly view I need to try harder Don't feel bad if people remember u when they need u, feel privileged that u're like a candle that comes 2 their mind when there is darkness I want you as a birthday present @username ???? I have the more gorgeous best friends in the world @username @username I'm so freaking lucky!!!!???????????? When you said your last goodbye I died a little bit inside @username hace mucho calor ???????? Look at the stars, look how they shine for u! @username we don't care? Don't feel yourself so important! I'm kinda obsessed with SUITS???? @username good one? best one!!! After mad men of course. @username u should, then u won't think that about BB. @username exactly,  where R U? Wait on me I know how to love you Autumn is coming???????????? Why does that not surprise me Energy and heat dissipate over time! Alejandra cortes films present,  the girl who can't sleep???? When u can touch someone's heart that's limitless @username and?.. By the way i saw the girl who was ur gf,  the little one I just don't remember her name :P @username I actually  don't, and I was just saying ???? @username enjoying my vacations, nothing interesting  to say, jajajajaja and no, that's so far 4 me @username maybe that's weird but I would like to bring flower to maricela ????,  u can join me! She was the best teacher???? Clémency Poésy is perfection???? Only brave warriors fall off their horses in battle. How can kneeling cowards know what a fall is? The ultimate goal of design is not to reduce complexity, but to create the illusion of simplicity? Black sheep Chapuuuuu called me???? I really want to go to watch the movie but I really can't go and i feel terrible about it. In case u don't know it @username goodbyes sucks???? Me against myself Dary!!!!! Chuck bass? ... I prefer Ted Mosby. I'm so far to be prepar to go to the university again???? Good Morning? The summer is oficially over. The only thing that make me happy is the autumn coming???????? I'm noooot ready for tomorrow???? I won't see the Chelsea play ???????? And there's no chance that we'll work it out That's why you and I ended over U.N.I @username people always think whatever they want ... so ... let the assholes be the assholes, I know u r so sweet :) OMG Holland is so perfect???? The only thing I like about the new video of nicki minaj was drake ???? Who the hell invents flying cockroachs??? I won't sleep until I see that fuckin cockroach dead! I miss bother my brothers :'( @username dame tu whats por dm :) A tiny horror story : MONDAY???? She will be loved Lilly Wood and The Prick - Prayer In C (Robin Sch…: http://t.co/Exme2qUJwq ???? I feel the flames of your fire and it's burning my heart! I'm following the map that leads to you A heart of steel starts to grow Turn the pain into power???? Can we just take a moment to appreciate jerome's beauty!???? Next time I will work alone I made all the hard work as usual I do all the fucking work and u complain about it ???? @username you're eyes are so beautiful ???? Can't wait for the video! @username @username agree with her #LOVEYOUTO ???? October ???????????? See anybody could be good to you! font based on the style of lettering seen on cassandre posters designed by atipo. download it for free: http://t.co/vzyoXxzHRa Notice me, take my hand Without my wings I feel so small Such a lovely place When u ready come a get it! This must be love The sound of my heart, the beat goes on and on and on ... So honey now, take me in your loving arms! 