finally making progress w/ #dissertation study... importing data into UCINET :) #sna #fb #in http://tumblr.com/xyb3zprvo2 love reading @username and learning about random notebooks available as alternative to #moleskine :) UN declares Internet access a human right http://tumblr.com/xyb40s0lpy asperger's surging among children of silicon valley http://tumblr.com/xyb40skr2j #ImANerd ... so into #coding today, surprised to find out that it's already lunchtime hi @username thanks so much for the kind words! made my day :) hi @username, your blog looks really good, love the images! did you take them yourself? sadly, i don't read german... #geekgirl #quote #MadeMyDay coworker says "love your red laptop ... it matches your dress" #research study shows oversharing on @username linked to psychological needs (via @username) http://t.co/QxtRClj #doctor shares perspective on wearing ties in clinic (via @username) #InfectionControl  http://t.co/TsOtfmu safety #tips for ladies wearing high #heels from @username via @username http://t.co/c9602vh #UES designer thrift sale by @username ... too bad it ends today TheIceBreak - a new dating site for couples to quantitatively measure their relationship http://t.co/EvRB9lM Interactive & Print Design Salaries via @username @username http://t.co/xVbXfB3 a brief History of Social Network Analysis (with citations)  http://t.co/ds0c0RE @username @username test “six degrees of separation” #SNA #research via @username http://t.co/c8QPgUH Facebook: No more 'no comment' for pharma - FiercePharma - Pharma marketers have moved onto the social... http://t.co/QnGrSW7 playing around with libSNA - a #python library for #sna http://t.co/dU4uPjy #ResearchPaper, "Alcohol Interferes With the Restorative Functions of Sleep" - avail. Nov 2011 in ACER http://t.co/bjgBkAK Daily coffee reduces risk for skin cancer - A new study backs up previous research that shows caffeine may... http://t.co/L1sGcdr volunteering at the hospital tonight! what are your #hurricane #irene plans? #fb Just completed a 2.60 mi run with @username. Check it out! http://t.co/yjMSvdN #RunKeeper Always have your stuff when you need it with @username. 2GB account is free! http://t.co/nh8T3Fc Google API Is Here! http://t.co/zzF354ko I just made a 10¢ donation to National Breast Cancer Foundation thru @username's  Cups of Hope Program http://t.co/2hbBPs2q I just made a 10¢ donation to National Breast Cancer Foundation thru @username's Cups of Hope Program http://t.co/2hbBPs2q #metadata is the backbone of organizing knowledge: taxonomies, ontologies, controlled vocab, facets, nomenclatures, indices, schemas, ... mindmaps, outlines, lists, table of contents, indices, menus, flowcharts, blueprints, tags,... how do you structure your thoughts? @username #outlines and #flowcharts are awesome tools.. but i'll one-up you by mentioning #twitter #hashtag =p Apple helps MDs cut thru medical apps clutter http://t.co/Iu321qMs this has been one of the most productive saturdays in a long while Link: Mining Data for Better Medicine http://t.co/hR6ckm9P social mining... wisdom of crowds research by cog sci professors @username http://t.co/4LRbYpcf News - 'facebook light' for dementia patients http://t.co/6B2N3jwF Cornell researchers measured the #mood of tweets.. http://t.co/XaahRFSs Link: Monitoring patients using intelligent t-shirts http://t.co/0xjuTMpZ Dogs May Soon Be Used To Detect Lung Cancer   http://t.co/Oe3Iq8Ne Link: Academia or Industry #research #career? Finding the Right Fit http://t.co/3116myd8 @username yikes! 18hrs/wk for 1 course sounds like a lot... teaching is not easy, even at part time =/ Infrographic: The Science of Salary via @username http://t.co/v0BIM4qV Link: learn to code at codecademy http://t.co/xzcNYyVY Photo: Nick Felton’s #Infographic Wine Label via @username http://t.co/xe6pYf2t Photo: The Food Allergen Detector http://t.co/YEivtrzX News: a pill to help you stay sober and drink all you want http://t.co/NuBQlxjm Video: Reconstructed Images From Brain Activity http://t.co/DLNBLYw4 HealthTap Apps Have Doctors Ready To Answer Your Questions (via @username) http://t.co/KfrBYfh7 Photo: Men Help Women Fight Breast Cancer in Quirky Mobile App (via Mashable) Rethink Breast Cancer has... http://t.co/yDcXFNeh Photo: The Anatomy Of A Social Media Strategist [Infographic] (via @username) http://t.co/WVyk3A4G Adidas Debuts Intelligent Soccer Cleats Embedded With Stats Tracker Technology (via @username) http://t.co/6qHh0VkP Park & Bond Mixes Men's Fashion With Editorial Tips #onlineshoppingformen http://t.co/GKcYIvOy Lance Armstrong To Launch Self-Tracking App For Cancer Patients http://t.co/OJwRz7qz Link: The five uber-skills of Academia http://t.co/GIxff467 News: Man assaults wife for not liking his facebook update (@username) http://t.co/gdeD8SGH Infographic: the history of digital storage  http://t.co/StInQitR Infographic: 7 disruptive technological innovations http://t.co/oIxLxxsb installed R and the statnet package tonight. let's see what it can do..! Paper: Social Network Analysis with sna  http://t.co/DGOeM9rz Makeup Makes Women Appear More Competent - › Wearing makeup … increases people’s perceptions of a woman’s... http://t.co/SJaR3KgR @username yea.. but it's not just applying makeup and perfume, but also putting it on well =P @username no worries, i can help you get started with that!  @username oh then I need to get trained first aah! How Twitter Tracks the Spread of Disease in Real Time http://t.co/XD171xBr Slides: The Art of Social Design http://t.co/7SLZaHTY Photo: Man Gets Smartphone Dock Installed In Prosthetic Limb http://t.co/F3SMYgaE thx from ny --loving the sunshine!! @username I bought a jacket to wear in the rain. It might never rain again. You're welcome, philly. What are essential references for R? 13 Answers: http://t.co/UniuJzEc #rstats (via @username @username) @username whoo hoo! you're on a roll! am curious to see if i can access ms sql server from macosx command line...  http://t.co/KpJlotX9 Do you know the difference between EMR vs EHR?  http://t.co/6NjKRZjQ thank you @username for a wonderful presentation on Maximizing Sustainable Pace and raffle gift! :)  http://t.co/ZgWkyj2x Company Predicts The Future By Scanning Current Websites - › Through scanning across 50,000 sources that... http://t.co/L6EKBByN Infrographic: Black Friday Trends w/ Foursquare data http://t.co/JIXJlQIS Facebook users separated by 4.74 degrees http://t.co/Go0ZvILS Photo: (via Jeweler Posts Facebook Love Notes On Californian Jumbotron @username) http://t.co/2AzpfiMX Photo: (via A Visual Break Down Of The Social Media Business [Infogrpahic] @username) http://t.co/dQh5R9Qr Photo: (via Popgadget Personal Technology for Women: Doctors testing portable breast cancer detector) http://t.co/M5BoFjJQ Photo: (via Light-Emitting Earphones Can Cure Winter Blues @username) http://t.co/hE8LEgQj Photo: The installation reevaluates our relationship with public spaces and how they affect our perception.... http://t.co/mlPJYCQG Photo: (via Tablet Owners Spend More Time and Money Shopping Online [INFOGRAPHIC]) http://t.co/3SypCxiC Photo: (via How to Use Google Search More Effectively [INFOGRAPHIC]) http://t.co/4eF9JbV6 I read Experiencing Architecture - 2nd Edition by Steen Eiler Rasmussen http://t.co/xjBLehYT Photo: (via Hemorrhoid venn diagram) found in a medical textbook http://t.co/4r52n74G Video: Jay Bradner: Open-source cancer research (via Video on http://t.co/kcFKejBL) http://t.co/Q1GL7Ml3 Video: Abraham Verghese: A doctor’s touch (via Video on http://t.co/kcFKejBL) http://t.co/0Md6Rpms Link: Sheryl Sandberg encourages women to take high tech jobs (via @username) http://t.co/itNTTXjN Photo: (via Neuroscience Helps Improve Website Design @username) http://t.co/OFi1HDL1 happy holidays! a wonderful day filled with family & friends ...plus coding! :) #python #networkx just RSVP'd for "NY SPIN 1/10: Making Business Agile: Governing Ambiguity with the UVF" http://t.co/d0VhCHAR via @username #agile Video: TV Lets You Reach In And Play With On-Screen Objects (via @username) http://t.co/dWwJBDL6 Top 10 Under-Hyped Web Apps, 2011 Edition http://t.co/ijMbLF2p i just rsvp'd for this event! http://t.co/H8a7ikFc People say they need involvement in communities - An overwhelming majority of Americans say it’s important... http://tumblr.com/xyb12xcm1d Clue as to why alcohol is addicting: Scientists show that drinking releases brain endorphins - The finding... http://t.co/uT0z5XdD [Study] shows facial features in product design linked with subconscious baby-loving. http://t.co/1JaHZU8r Video: The Future of Health Care: Robots and Networks | Pew Research Center’s Internet & American Life... http://tumblr.com/xyb130rwlg Video: “Smartphone health apps won’t be used daily. Self-report fails. Texting programs annoy. Enchanted... http://tumblr.com/xyb1317cag Starving in a World of Plenty § SEEDMAGAZINE.COM - RESEARCHERS ARE BEGINNING TO UNCOVER THENEUROLOGICAL... http://tumblr.com/xyb132f29l Mercedes Lets Drivers Access Facebook, Yelp And Google From Their Car’s Dashboard @username - › The social media... http://t.co/Ba97dMrs Photo: Doctors in the U.K. are taking 3-D imagery to a whole new level, starting today: They’reperforming... http://tumblr.com/xyb13349fm Photo: Infographic: Apple’s App Store Visualized | Fast Company http://tumblr.com/xyb133tk6p "People call me a feminist whenever I express sentiments that differentiate me from a doormat or a..." http://tumblr.com/xyb134i6m3 