Caracas, The City of Lost Bullets.: http://wp.me/pt5wl-7a Stuck in America. http://flic.kr/p/8eaKRz @username I love True Blood and Lie to Me! Hard work combined with attention to details should have the d... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 updates on my website - "moments" gallery: http://www.valentinacugusi.com/ http://fb.me/DERbDr5o watching #esp vs. #por  ..go spain!!! #worldcup #Oscars live on AP live stream..Angelina is really gorgeous!! good morning! I'm still tired :S You may not be sure of how you feel today because your mood ke... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 new upload. http://flic.kr/p/8eCukf RT @username: Close Up by Martin Schoeller | MediaStorm http://t.co/jHbQ0J8B The hectic pace of your life slows down a bit now that the Moo... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 Japan One Year Later: Photographs by James Nachtwey - LightBox http://t.co/X0HRbO16 via @username back from Sardinia! Soon I will upolad a lot of photos on Flickr ;) @username thanks so much :) Fill your paper with the breathings of your heart. http://flic.kr/p/8gqgUK It's great to have self-confidence, but you can take it to an ... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 new twitter background ;) @username thanks ;) tomorrow morning shopping in bologna :D The Resistance. http://flic.kr/p/8gKE1E You enjoy the increased pace of your life, yet it is wise for ... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 new upload! http://flic.kr/p/8gUWbb Attending OCHA Event next week at European Commission! @username ahahah, why not? I would like to work one year in india as volunteer, anyway I have to apply and wait :) @username me too I was looking for Tanzania but last year I was in Kenya so I want to change area somehow..and India always inspires me! the departure. http://flic.kr/p/8h1Mi3 "Courage is knowing what not to fear." - Plato http://tumblr.com/xhbd1iedb flight for Bordeaux in few hours! Although your intentions are good, you probably won't be able ... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 RT @username: Photoshop CS6 Is the Best Version In Recent Memory—And It's Free Now http://t.co/h7F2663H Why bother? We're living it. RT @username: Orwell's '1984' Getting New Film Adaptation (Exclusive) http://t.co/wuUMmoMX Grand Format : Helmut newton, l’exposition – la bande annonce http://t.co/u357G2Et via @username http://t.co/n1z8onpg Stanley Kubrick's Expo in Brussels! RT @username: Here's why I have absolutely no interest in owning the new iPad http://t.co/opeuNcPL by @username I'm at EU Committee Of the Regions (Brussels, Brussels) http://t.co/aKJoIKsD RT @username: Burma rejoices on a long-delayed day for democracy http://t.co/rCfQHg7A "European Innovation Partnership on Active and Healthy Ageing" Conference (@username European Commission - CHAR w/ 5 others) http://t.co/3hKmgnxm RT @username: Check out these 10 gadgets that have been repurposed as modern home and office accessories - http://t.co/2hxTK1vj By the end of the day, you may be wishing that you hadn't expr... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 in Brussels again..holidays were amazing but too short! Workshop w/ Rob Hornstra - Milan: http://t.co/DMwhDdX6 "Sometimes I get real lonely sleeping with you." - Haruki Murakami (A Wild Sheep Chase) http://t.co/pYyBcu1A Trying to control your feelings today may be a good idea, but ... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 RT @username: France election campaign enters final day http://t.co/kv5iUgzQ WWF - Living Planet Report http://t.co/9ffP2yyx via @username 173 followers on #Instagram after only 5 months with my iPhone..thanks!!! Stockholm Photography Week - May 31, June 2: http://t.co/4MBwoquj Leonard Freed Expo in Rome: http://t.co/qodXETAD Back from Bordeaux..great time in Dordogne! I love love love France <3 I've just received an invitation from Getty Images..so happy!! I'm back from holidays, I've spent a great time in Dordogne and took a lot of photos..enjoy my latest uploads on Flickr! stop-motionnnn!! http://flic.kr/p/8m5VcM Childhood is the most beautiful of all life's seasons. http://flic.kr/p/8mb2CR You may believe that you have a plan that cannot fail but it's... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 @username wow!! bella foto ;) You might need to retreat today as you manage the unexpected c... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 The last rendez-vous. (stop-motion video) http://flic.kr/p/8moc1S DIY Clothes Tutorial: Shirt to skirt. http://bit.ly/1PqBHY From today I'm a Getty Images Contributor :) You may have a day that is filled with lots of things to do th... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 new upload: http://flic.kr/p/8mMmXg @username me too :)) You may need to attend to a complex array of desires that make... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 Dublin in two days! Photo: film-grain: http://tumblr.com/xhbec0qxz There is no need to worry if you encounter deep emotions today... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 W/Paris Saint-Germain Coach :) http://t.co/OhtihQok @username @username leaving for Dublin in 4h :D You cannot escape the fact that you have a lot to finish up no... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 The New Photojournalistic Social Advocacy: Nuru Project - LightBox http://t.co/mP4gnD9z via @username @username DCU in Dublin, Ireland! "I wonder how many people I’ve looked at all my life and never seen." - John Steinbeck, Winter of Our... http://t.co/bT4pD1mq You may not be able to recall all the details about what recen... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 in Belfast on Sunday! You may be feeling quite smart, but your intelligence won't he... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 Pacifists in the Cross-Fire http://t.co/vuEgVBwa You can win someone's approval today by wearing him or her dow... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 thinking about my hometown, Modena, which has been hit again by a major #earthquake first photo taken in dublin, ireland! http://fb.me/u1ooCM8G Photo: Untitled. (by {.clochette la fée.}) http://tumblr.com/xhbfohmje Although yours is often considered the sign of self, today's a... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 I want to go back to Dublinnnnn!! waiting for Minolta X-700 + Rokkor 50mm f/1.8: a present from by boyfriend <3 Updates on my website, gallery sections: Moments&Landscapes! http://fb.me/u8OaMOtV The distinction between love and friendship may become an issu... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 It's a bee world. http://flic.kr/p/8stHip I hold this to be the highest task for a bond between two people: that each protects the solitude of the other. http://flic.kr/p/8syKKB You aren't barging ahead so fast now, for you realize that acc... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 @username thanks Dan :) but you're better than me for this kind of photos! Penneys/Primark is one of the best places where to shop ever! At #UrbanOutfitters in Dublin I've found an awesome watch necklace..so happy for it :)) Talking via Skype with my new friends met in Dublin, I love them! Even with all your grand visions of amazing adventures, the ro... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 Bombay Bicycle Club - How Can You Swallow So Much Sleep http://t.co/69osnfw via @username 900 fans..thank you all!! You may be feeling upbeat today, but your newly discovered opt... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 YouTube Channel featuring all my stop-motions! http://fb.me/Fe9HRAsa Please, please, please, let me get what I want. http://flic.kr/p/8tn6Yg brussels-paris-berlin-rome..next ten days will be tough! 