Pretty woman ???? Oh oh @username I don't know ANNNEEE  ???? soon I will come and visit you Telegram ipv Whatsapp ????. Goed: Secret massages sturen. Slecht: krijg rare of foute notificaties @username hahaha succes! ;) komt goed moppie Jhené Aiko Covers Tupac's 'Keep Ya Head Up': http://t.co/F84mxOXfml via @username Pharrell cries.. So cute. Love happy http://t.co/Ktqk2Ng3QP @username whisky cola Catfish: Privacy? Priva-wie? http://t.co/BtqBQWz4dM I just completed an activity using RunKeeper. Wwooohooo http://t.co/kaa8r0CYw0 Avant, I like your new album.. Listening to The Letter.. 20 Jobs That Will Make Yours Look Like a Dream Job http://t.co/obDajghcua Yep, it's all true...Differences Man and Woman http://t.co/OlD6n38QXp via @username Weekend - whisky - Jimmy Woo http://t.co/CnvSRfVatZ @username sowieso man is kut programma @username of baileys “@username: How do you survive a long distance relationship? #KLMblog #COTA http://t.co/zlp2NgOCPj http://t.co/9Ze7JGtSQB”@username @username why not Eating bibimbap in Seoul - good food #Seoul #bibimbap http://t.co/ggit36mRfD Choco cake, fluffy tart & espresso in Seoul http://t.co/zJx3ZUxqfc A happy girl eating cake and drink coffee - #yukieseoul http://t.co/bi3lvCWXu2 Looking for my rebound chick, in brothers Workshop: How to make Korean ice cream "Patbingsu ???" @username ???????? (Hankuk University of Foreign Studies) http://t.co/W7a3fL9H1M Lunch: cold buckwheat noodles with crushed ice, greens and egg - but it didn't taste good ???? #yukieseoul http://t.co/H1GBcSy8na Lunch: tender pork bones stew with Korean perilla leaves, shoots & side dishes #seoul #food #yukieseoul #kimchi http://t.co/Iyo2hxdspo Dinner: kimchi soup, bulgogi with lemon juice and croquettes of sweet potato #lekker #seoul #food #yukieseoul http://t.co/yHONXEJt3T Cantine lunch: "Samgyetang" chicken ginseng soup. It is usually stuffed, but this one wasn't. Taste good #seoul http://t.co/b2mB7WCjQu Happy = ice cream ?? http://t.co/OjwjSnt2ax Temple food: everything organic & vegetarian - buddhist Food #sodelish #lekker #seoul http://t.co/UYaFikzd23 Korean Food: mix between Western and East - Strawberry Pizza at Restaurant "I have a dream" #seoul #pizza #gangnam http://t.co/wZYFiQIz6c Making Korean Rice wine "Makgeolli" with the French teacher. First step preheat the jar were we put the ingredients http://t.co/EZUOCUmolW Mix: cooked rice, rice water and Nuruk. The fermentation starts with the nuruk, a Korean fermentation starter #hufs ???? http://t.co/kPqvbRuc5l @username yes the teacher said its used to sterilize all the bacteria. It didn't broke haha Beautiful South Korea - Jeonju  #korea #jeonju http://t.co/CLsj5tMAyU So fluffy, that I want to die.. Suikerspin mix met softijs, cornflakes en Oreo #lekker #korea #food #seoul #icecream http://t.co/0ShgCbbaoW The last ceremony with the teachers. Thank you. I enjoyed every courses at HUFS. Now it's time to go home :(  #seoul http://t.co/sLBfkEEaT0 I loved Korean food so much, that my stomach hurts #Korea  #Seoul #foodie @username yeaahhh goedzo! Join the club @username heyyy Alex! Gefeliciteerd jonge god hahaha :) Happy Birthday Joshua. His bday cake made by my sister in law. First try fondant cake #cake #foodie #fondant #taart http://t.co/fhXroXjGDb “@username: Play Chess Now - Free! 10 Million+ players. Play live games, solve quick tactics puzzles.  https://t.co/3h5WDM7PFG” @username "My love for food is only limited by the capacity of my stomach" #foodquotes Oester & parels & bloody mary #lekker #burgemeester #linschoten http://t.co/zSyXPQwpxi English breakfast. Plymouth, UK #plymouth #UnitedKingdom http://t.co/JR9L5Z7VXE Fish & Chips & Mashed Peas #fishchip #chris #cod http://t.co/WvKpLuvscR Beautiful Plymouth Sea #plymouth #sea #uk http://t.co/O5fnTA8eee British pork belly, apple sauce & mashed potato. Too much. But so good #tasty #ukfood http://t.co/dBwTEy9oRd @username thanks Wat moet ik doen in London? What should I do in London around Xmas? #Christmas #dtv #London #ChristmasLondon It's your girl #newspaper #asnonline #blog #yukieblog http://t.co/LwOVXJ2vZ4 @username then what?? ???? Quote: If I want something, I will get it Interessant artikel over Big data: "Big data and the end of theory?" http://t.co/3GB9gHECPP via @username “@username: The top 10 most Instagrammed restaurants in London... http://t.co/6IYbjeinrI http://t.co/fv3fVC4Mqk” @username Big problem: chips is op in huis ???? Money can't buy happiness but I can buy donuts ???? Vanavond Victoria Secret Fashion Show #net5 ???? @username is ze offline.. Loser Blog: Welcome to my book collection: http://t.co/bJPdZPyj8T #blog #loveletters #hetdiner “@username: Look at this face.  http://t.co/gvXuBE8nFh” @username Tomaten tomaten .. To to maten “Make a resolution to exercise more? Want an escape from the city? #Seoulfortress! http://t.co/lZGfPzUkz6 http://t.co/S9imWELB5C” @username Facebook film! Trey Songz, het was AAANNNNNN!!!! http://plixi.com/p/92735783 Ik hoor geklop.. *knock knock* is dat Trey?? #neighborsknowmyname @username rusland beter he met boy and girl... Utrecht holla! @username please return my call jerry hahaha @username thuis @username thankyou! still loving Musiq Soulchild music. New album 'MusiqintheMagiq' @username thuis? @username the way you shaking in those jeans @username mr wrong is mr right! Aha. You know what it is... It's weekenddddd @username Jasmine Palace! @username aight swaggg Black and yellow @username no money + too expensive! Who run the world? GIRLSSS. Beyoncé is a killaaa ? @username goedzo! Didn't knew that @username stress? @username haha marcom toch? Ik ben weer springlevend!!! Yeahh Eat like an animal @username thankssss :) @username thanksss chick! 