@username Ehh... Books on mythology, that is. I know I should have answered to a lot of hello tweets that included me and now not anymore. I was just too busy off late ???? #sorry @username I don't agree. 8 is nice, but 6 (SIXX) is cool!!! ?????????? @username @username @username My birthday is tomorrow (i.e. here), Dec. 4th @username I may not always answer (like the man of my life doesnt always), but (like him) I see it all! ???? @username @username @username You have a nice birthday too! “@username: New favorite Instagram. http://t.co/Gh06hJU4Ya    You have one?” I wish!!! So eternally in ?? with you.... ???????? There's a very thin line between fashion and fake. Check my instagram: http://t.co/9eg89x7TMK A nice pic of @username that I turned into an old style photograph. For the nicest #photographer out… http://t.co/yMlCWHphJX @username Good read! Your silence towards me is deafening... #ursilentuscream “@username: @username @username @username @username hope you get the stuff on time ????” Maybe today, maybe tomorrow... ???? #Bliss is the new magic word. Bliss is as old as the world. Bliss is within everyone of us. Look for it. Find it! ?????? 11:11 am right here right now. Make A Wish! ?????????? It's Beauty. It's Strength. It's Wisdom. @username #photoedit by @username ???? http://t.co/lYo9kPagVc “@username: @username @username this is one of the best m/” What about my latest edit? ???? Happy FCKN Birthday, @username ???????????? Tomorrow is my #birthday and just now, the post delivery man delivered a birthday present from… http://t.co/HmUB5T4R2m I am now following 1111 people, ???????????? @username Cool onstage photo of you, @username and @username ???? @username #RIPMotleyCrue http://t.co/eyIkB2mJhv @username @username @username @username could u create songs with this spiritual theme? #EspeciallyHope ???? http://t.co/1nW9J5hU5l @username Thank you! ???????? @username Are you getting inspiration for new music from Joseph Campbell, Nikki? @username It's still early into Dec. 4, but today is my birthday & I'm so happy to be alive! ???????? “@username: @username happy Birthday!” THANK YOU! ???????? “@username: @username YES” Mythology is part of my work. I'm a classicist.???? @username Today is my birthday. Getting a Happy Birthday from my fav musician & creative inspirator would be so nice! TY ???? “@username: @username Happy Birthday!” THANK YOU “@username: Happy Birthday! @username” THANK YOU!! “@username: @username @username "Hey Rose, happy Birthday to you!" http://t.co/FrX0EP4Rhh” THANK YOU! XO @username ?? Figs Vision! @username @username I wish you a good night. Today for me, Dec. 4 is my birthday. Can I get a "Happy Birthday" wish from you, please? “@username: @username Happy Birthday!” THANK YOU! ???? @username THANK YOU!! ???????? “@username: @username happy birthday????????????” THANK YOU! @username Thank you!! A Happy Birthday tweet from @username would be wonderful!! @username Please wish me a Happy Birthday, Nikki? It's today :) @username THANK YOU!! ???????? @username Thank you for your best wishes, Jamie!! Xoxo “@username: @username @username @username Happy Birthday Rose” THANK YOU! xx “@username: @username @username Happy birthday” THANK YOU!! @username Today is my birthday. I'm enjoying it. It would be outstanding if you posted a Happy Birthday tweet to me. Please? “@username: Life is not about who hurt you and broke you down. It's about who was always there and who made you smile agin"@username @username @username Funny. I can't load your post on my instagram. Is my instagram lagging? Hmm, must be... #wtf ???? “@username: @username Yes I think instGram is lagging ... Needs the ??”Yup yup!! ???????? It's my birthday and I smile if I want to.... @username Can I have a Happy B-day from you? #pleez @username @username THANK YOU!! @username Always interesting! Idk why I like the Terminator. Maybe because of the salvation thought that's always there @username Happy Holidays! Why I care? Because I love. @username @username @username I'm having an awesome birthday and I can't wait for the #sixxsense show today!!???? http://t.co/meFygm8I9z “@username: @username Happy birthday! Jay Z, Tyra Banks, and Jeff Bridges share a birthday with you!” Thanks again, hahaha! “@username: @username @username @username @username. Happy Birthday to you girl @username :-)” THANK YOU! “@username: @username HAPPY BIRTHDAY ! I hope it was awesome????????????????????” It was! ???????? My bday is today, but since this month is always one big party affair with the Holidays and many bdays, I'll stretch mine until Dec 31.. Lol @username @username @username @username Thank you, Dawn!! I want to thank all my friends online & offline for all their nice & best wishes for me on my birthday!!! #thankyou ?????????? @username Thank you! It's very VERY early into Dec. 5 and after some sleep I'm very much awake! #lol @username And the night before St. Nicholas' birthday people give eachother gifts in NL. It's called St. Nicholas' Eve & Gifts Eve! @username Dec. 5 that is. Especially for kids, this is one of the year's epic evenings! @username @username and this is 1 of the reasons why I love him: he's so passionate about what he loves to do! “@username: Life's problems wouldn't be called "hurdles" if there wasn't a way to get over them.” ???????? @username #photoedit by @username ???? @username @username @username @username @username http://t.co/sT4XRr4ZEJ “@username: @username Happy Birthday!!!” THANK YOU!! ?????????? “@username: @username When is your b day?” Dec 4. For me that's already yesterday “@username: @username @username I thought it was mighty attractive lol” It's a matter of opinion...But for me, ehhh...no. #lol @username @username Of course I do and I agree to that! Hahaha! ???????????? @username Is there something you still have to photograph? #AskSixx @username It's my birthday today. Please wish me a happy birthday? #AskSixx @username @username Never do steroids Nikki. They will kill you. @username Thank you! ?????? @username @username Thank you, Rodney!! @username @username It sure would be! ???????? I’ve been away for a while. Nothing personal. Today is my birthday & a special day 4 #NikkiTime w/@username http://t.co/Hfkg3UHg9I @username @username I'm a woman, Rodney. ???????? @username Good nighf and thank you for faving one of my birthday tweets ???? “@username: @username @username Hope you had a great Birthday!” Thank you, yes I did!!! @username @username I'm gonna get the new album soon! @username A #photoedit of you & #LeicaSixx and a @username lens. I thought you'd like the combination ???? http://t.co/o7YIttFREe “@username: Happiness doesn't result from what we get, but from what we give.” I'm not #FF -ing today, 'cause I got a lot to do, but there's of course one guy that always gets a #ShoutOut : ......???????? A big mega #ShoutOut for the one and only @username !!! ???? @username #photoedit by @username ????@username @username @username @username @username @username http://t.co/o9aYfnVWXS @username #photoedit by @username ????@username @username @username @username @username http://t.co/TGsrxjZU7z @username No @username #ModernVintage Are they crazy???? @username @username @username Awesome! Real guitar stuff!! ???????? “@username: @username @username @username @username @username @username @username This is a wonderful pic!!!!” Thank u Hahaha! When @username comes in and enters the party! #photoedit by @username ???? @username @username http://t.co/4f4NO9War5 @username @username Got it! #iTunes #CD #7"Single Just not yet: the #vinylalbum ???????? @username @username @username In my #WishList for #SixxMas !!! ???????? @username @username Between your birthday and Xmas! On my #wishlist ! ???? @username @username Nikki, can we pre-order the #vinyl #ModernVintage ?? When @username walks into a room... #photoedit by @username ???? @username @username @username @username http://t.co/gdc9OpKlk5 @username @username @username @username @username Send me the pic you want edited and I'll make it for you @username @username Can we pre-order the #vinyl version of #ModernVintage ? Will it be available on http://t.co/Tpk3bBznV6 ? @username You're welcome ???? @username #tagart #photoedit by @username ???? @username @username @username @username @username http://t.co/AGGCguLbqZ @username @username @username @username @username @username You're welcome! 