on m n my  my  my v y ve  ver very ery  ry l y la  las last ast  st n t ne  ner nerv erve rve! ve!  e! i ! i   i a i am  am  am n m no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng a g an  and and  nd i d i   i h i ha  hav have ave  ve n e no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng b g bu  but but  ut a t al  all alla llah lah! ah!  h! . ! ..  ... ...f ..fr .fro from rom  om t m th  the the  he c e co  cor corn orne rner ner  er o r of  of  of m f my  my  my d y dr  dre drea ream eams ams! ms!  s! m ! ma  mas mash asha sha  ha a a al  all alla llah lah! ah!  h! : ! :   : t : th  the then hen, en,  n, y , yo  you you  ou h u ha  hav have ave  ve e e ev  eve ever very eryt ryth ythi thin hing ing  ng . g .   . " . ":  ":  ": i : i   i a i am  am  am n m no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng a g an  and and  nd i d i   i h i ha  hav have ave  ve n e no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng b g bu  but but  ut a t al  all alla llah lah! ah!  h! s ! st  sta stay tay  ay r y re  rel rela elax laxe axed xed, ed,  d, b , be  be  be a e at  at  at p t pe  pea peac eace ace, ce,  e, w , wi  wit with itho thou hout out  ut a t an  anx anxi nxie xiet ieti etie ties ies, es,  s, b , be  be  be i e in  in  in c n co  con conv onve nver vers ersa rsat sati atio tion ions ons  ns t s th  tha that hat  at m t ma  mak make akes kes  es s s se  sen sens ense nse. se.  e. h . ha  hap happ appy ppy. py.. y... ...  .. w . we  we  we a e as  ask ask  sk f k fo  for for  or n r no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng b g bu  but but  ut w t wi  wil will ill  ll g l gi  giv give ive  ve e e ev  eve ever very eryt ryth ythi thin hing ing  ng i g if  if  if w f we  we  we h e ha  hav have ave  ve t e to  to. to.  o. b . be  be  be k e ki  kin kind ind, nd,  d, n , no  no  no m o ma  mat matt atte tter ter  er w r wh  wha what hat. at.. t... ...  .. i . it  it' it's t's  's a s a   a p a pr  pri pric rice icel cele eles less ess  ss l s le  leg lega egac gacy acy  cy t y to  to  to l o le  lea leav eave ave  ve b e be  beh behi ehin hind ind. nd.  d. w . wh  whe when hen  en t n th  the the  he w e wa  wav wave aves ves  es o s of  of  of t f tr  tro trou roub oubl uble ble  le l e lo  loo look ooks oks  ks b s be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul i l in  in  in t n th  the the  he s e sk  sky sky. ky.. y... ...  .. n . no  not not  ot a t a   a w a wi  wit witc itch tch. ch.. h... ...  .. m . me  mer mere erel rely ely  ly b y be  bew bewi ewit witc itch tchi chin hing ing. ng.. g... ...  .. l . lo  lol lol! ol!  l! : ! :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: w : wh  whe when hen  en t n th  the the  he w e wa  wav wave aves ves  es o s of  of  of t f tr  tro trou roub oubl uble ble  le l e lo  loo look ooks oks  ks b s be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul i l in  in  in t n th  the the  he s e sk  sky sky. ky.. y... ...‚ ..‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù to  toh toh  oh f h fa  fa, fa,k a,ka ,kaj kaji aji  ji z i za  zau zaur aura uran ranc ance nce  ce d e da  da  da t a tu  tur tura uran ranc anci nci. ci.‚ i.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù " ù "d  "di "dis disc isco scom comb ombo mbob bobu obul bula ulat late ated ted" ed"  d" ? " ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? t ? th  the the  he w e wo  wor word ord  rd i d it  its itse tsel self elf  lf g f go  got got  ot m t me  me  me d e di  dis disc isco scom comb ombo mbob bobu obul bula ulat late ated ted  ed ? d ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? l ? lm  lma lmao mao  ao i o i   i k i kn  kno know now  ow r w ri  rig righ ight ght  ht ? t ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : t : tu  tur tura uran ranc anci nci  ci ? i ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? " ? ":  ":  ": " : "d  "di "dis disc isco scom comb ombo mbob bobu obul bula ulat late ated ted" ed"  d" ? " ??  ??? ???? ???" ??"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lol lol! ol!  l! a ! ab  abo abou bout out? ut?  t? : ? :   : s : sa  sam same ame  me h e he  her here ere  re : e :   : " : "d  "di "dis disc isco scom comb ombo mbob bobu obul bula ulat late ated ted" ed"  d" ? " ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù h ù ha  hah haha ahah haha aha  ha : a :   : b : be  bei bein eing ing  ng d g di  dis disc isco scom comb ombo mbob bobu obul bula ulat late ated ted  ed : d :   : l : lo  lol lol! ol!  l! a ! ab  abo abou bout out? ut?  t? : ? :   : s : sa  sam same ame  me h e he  her here ere  re : e :   : " : "d  "di "dis disc isco scom comb ombo mbob bobu obul bula ulat late ated ted" ed"  d" ? " ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù b ù bu  but but  ut i t i   i s i sa  sai said aid  id m d me  me  me ? e ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : l : le  let let' et's t's  's s s sw  swi swit witc itch tch? ch?? h??? ???? ???  ?? " ? ":  ":  ": w : wo  wou woul ould uld  ld l d lo  lov love ove  ve t e to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a m a ma  mal male ale  le v e ve  ver vers ersi rsio sion ion  on o n of  of  of m f me  me  me f e fo  for for  or a r a   a w a we  wee week eeks eks  ks ? s ??  ??? ???? ???" ??"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lol lol  ol : l :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: w : wo  wou woul ould uld  ld l d lo  lov love ove  ve t e to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a m a ma  mal male ale  le v e ve  ver vers ersi rsio sion ion  on o n of  of  of m f me  me  me f e fo  for for  or a r a   a w a we  wee week eeks eks  ks ? s ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äùa Äùas ùas  as i s in  inf infi nfir fird irda rdau daus ausi usiy siyi iyi? yi?‚ i?‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù : ù :   : w : wo  wou woul ould uld  ld l d lo  lov love ove  ve t e to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a m a ma  mal male ale  le v e ve  ver vers ersi rsio sion ion  on o n of  of  of m f me  me  me f e fo  for for  or a r a   a w a we  wee week eek  ek ? k ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? i ? i   i k i kn  kno know now  ow r w ri  rig righ ight ght  ht ? t ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : " : "s  "sm "smh smh! mh!  h! i ! im  ima imag magi agin gina inat nati atio tion ions ons  ns : s :   : : : :   : w : wo  wou woul ould uld  ld l d lo  lov love ove  ve t e to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a m a ma  mal male ale  le v e ve  ver vers ersi rsio sion ion  on o n of  of  of m f me  me  me f e fo  for for  or a r a   a w a we  wee week eek  ek ? k ??  ??? ???? ???" ??"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???: ??:  ?: a : ab  abu abuj buja uja  ja b a bo  boy boys oys. ys.  s. a . ak  aka aka  ka w a wh  whi whit hite ite  te t e tr  tra trad rad  ad g d ga  gan gang ang. ng.  g. m . me  mer merc erce rced cede edes des  es d s dr  dri driv rivi ivin ving ing. ng.  g. g . gu  guc gucc ucci cci  ci s i sl  sli slip lipp ippe pper pers ers  rs w s we  wea wear eari arin ring ing. ng.  g. o . ou  oud oud  ud s d sm  sme smel mell elli llin ling ing. ng.  g. n . no  no  no m o mo  mon mone oney ney  ey f y fo  for for  or p r po  poc pock ocke cket ket. et.  t. p . pa  pac pack acka ckag kagi agin ging ing. ng.  g. 1 . 15  15m 15mi 5min mins ins  ns ? s ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : h : ho  how how  ow l w lo  lon long ong  ng a g af  aft afte fter ter  er a r ar  arr arri rriv rivi ivin ving ing  ng a g at  at  at s t so  som some omeo meon eone one‚ ne‚Ä e‚Äô ‚Äôs Äôs  ôs h s ho  hou hous ouse use  se i e is  is  is i s it  it  it a t ap  app appr ppro prop ropr opri pria riat iate ate  te t e to  to  to a o as  ask ask  sk f k fo  for for  or t r th  the the  he w e wi  wif wifi ifi  fi p i pa  pas pass assw sswo swor word ord? rd?  d? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lm  lma lmao mao  ao m o m√  m√© m√©r √©rc ©rci rci  ci : i :   : s : st  sta star tart arte rter ter  er p r pa  pac pack ack, ck,  k, c , co  com come ome  me t e ta  tak take ake  ke m e my  my  my w y we  wea wear ears ars! rs!  s! " ! ":  ":  ": w : wo  wou woul ould uld  ld l d lo  lov love ove  ve t e to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a m a ma  mal male ale  le v e ve  ver vers ersi rsio sion ion  on o n of  of  of m f me  me  me f e fo  for for  or a r a   a w a we  wee week eeks eks  ks ? s ??  ??? ???? ???" ??"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù sa  sad sadl adly dly  ly ? y ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : w : we  we  we a e al  all all  ll a l ar  are are. re.  e. " . ":  ":  ": a : ad  add addi ddic dict icte cted ted  ed t d to  to  to m o my  my  my p y ph  pho phon hone one" ne"‚ e"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù it  it  it i t is  is  is : s :   : i : it  its its  ts r s re  rea real eall ally lly  ly a y an  ann anno nnoy noyi oyin ying ing  ng " g ":  ":  ": s : sa  sad sadl adly dly  ly ? y ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : w : we  we  we a e al  all all  ll a l ar  are are. re.  e. " . ":  ":  ": a : ad  add addi ddic dict icte cted ted  ed t d to  to  to m o my  my  my p y ph  pho phon hone one" ne"‚ e"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù" Äù"‚ ù"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù b ù bu  but but  ut i t i   i d i di  did did  id n d no  not not  ot s t se  see see  ee t e th  thi this his  is s s sc  sce scen cene ene  ne n e na  na  na ? a ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : d : di  div dive iver verg erge rgen gent ent. nt.  t. i . it  it  it i t is  is  is f s fo  for for  or m r me  me, me,  e, i , i   i w i wi  wis wish ish  sh i h i   i w i wa  was wasn asn' sn't n't. 't.  t. a . an  and and  nd y d ye  yes yes, es,  s, i , i   i p i pr  pra pray ray  ay t y th  tha that hat  at n t ne  nev neve ever ver  er h r ha  hap happ appe ppen pens ens  ns t s to  too too  oo ? o ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? l ? lm  lma lmao mao  ao : o :   : 3 : 3m  3mi 3min mins ins  ns : s :)  :)  :) " ) "   " 1 " 15  15m 15mi 5min mins ins  ns ? s ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? " ? ":  ":  ": h : ho  how how  ow l w lo  lon long ong  ng a g af  aft afte fter ter  er a r ar  arr arri rriv rivi ivin ving ing  ng a g at  at  at s t so  som some omeo meon eone one‚ ne‚Ä e‚Äô ‚Äôs Äôs  ôs h s ho  hou hous ouse use  se i e is  is  is i s it  it  it a t ap  app appr ppro prop ropr opri pria riat iate ate  te t e to  to  to a o as  ask ask  sk f k fo  for for  or t r th  the the  he w e wi  wif wifi ifi  fi y i yo  you you  ou m u ma  may may  ay h y ha  hav have ave  ve w e wr  wro wron rong ongl ngly gly  ly j y ju  jud judg udge dged ged  ed s d so  som some omeo meon eone one  ne b e ba  bas base ased sed  ed o d ot  oth othe ther hers ers  rs e s en  enc enco ncou coun ount unte nter ter  er w r wi  wit with ith  th t h th  the them hem  em b m bu  but but  ut w t wh  whe when hen  en y n yo  you you  ou e u en  enc enco ncou coun ount unte nter ter  er t r th  the them hem, em,  m, t , th  the they hey  ey a y ar  are are  re b e be  bet bett ette tter ter  er t r th  tha than han  an y n yo  you your our  ur e r ex  exp expe xpec pect ecta ctat tati atio tion ions ons. ns.  s. a . ab  abi abi  bi o i o   o ? o ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : t : th  the the  he l e lo  lon long onge nger ger  er t r th  the the  he w e wa  wai wait ait, it,  t, t , th  the the  he m e mo  mor more ore  re a e aw  awk awkw wkwa kwar ward ard  rd i d it  it  it b t be  bec beco ecom come omes mes. es.  s. h . ha  hah haha aha  ha j a ju  jus just ust  st a t as  ask ask‚ sk‚Ä k‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù d ù do  do  do t o th  the they hey  ey k y kn  kno know now  ow t w th  tha that hat  at " t "o  "on "one one  ne i e is  is  is t s to  too too  oo g o go  goo good ood" od"? d"?  "? : ? :i  :if :if  if s f sh  she she‚ he‚Ä e‚Äô ‚Äôs Äôs  ôs t s to  too too  oo g o go  goo good ood  od f d fo  for for  or y r yo  you you, ou,  u, m , my  my  my g y go  god god, od,  d, d , do  don don‚ on‚Ä n‚Äô ‚Äôt Äôt  ôt l t le  lea leav eave ave  ve h e he  her her. er.m r.ma .mak make ake  ke a e an  an  an e n ef  eff effo ffor fort ort  rt t t to  to  to b o be  be  be g e go  goo good ood  od e d en  eno enou noug ough ugh  gh i h in  ins inst nste stea tead ead  ad h d ho  how how  ow c w ca  can can  an p n pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le h e ha  hat hate ate  te t e th  the them hems emse msel selv elve lves ves  es s s so  so  so m o mu  muc much uch  ch t h to  to  to c o ca  cal call all  ll t l th  the thei heir eir  ir o r ow  own own  wn p n pe  per pers erso rson son  on u n ug  ugl ugly gly? ly?  y? i ? i   i h i ha  hat hate ate  te t e th  the the  he w e wo  wor word ord  rd u d ug  ugl ugly gly  ly o y on  on  on a n an  any any  ny o y of  of  of g f go  god gods ods  ds c s cr  cre crea reat eati atio tion ion. on.  n. g . go  god god' od's d's  's w s wo  wor work ork  rk i k is  is  is p s pe  per perf erfe rfec fect ecti ctio tion ion  on p n pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le c e ca  can can  an o n on  onl only nly  ly h y ha  hav have ave  ve " e "u  "ug "ugl ugly gly  ly p y pe  per pers erso rson sona onal nali alit liti itie ties ies" es"  s" m " mo  mos most ostl stly tly  ly c y cr  cre crea reat eate ated ted  ed b d by  by  by t y th  the them hems emse msel selv elve lves ves  es a s an  and and  nd i d in  in  in t n th  the thei heir eir  ir h r he  hea head ead! ad!  d! w ! we  we  we a e ar  are are  re a e al  all all  ll v l ve  ver very ery  ry p y pe  per perf erfe rfec fect ect! ct!  t! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : p : pr  pre prea reac each ach  ch m h my  my  my s y si  sis sist iste ster ter  er , r ,   , p , pr  pre prea reac each ach. ch.‚ h.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i d i do  don don' on't n't  't e t ev  eve even ven  en l n li  lik like ike  ke s e sc  sch scho choo hool ool  ol b l bu  but but  ut i t i   i l i lo  lov love ove  ve t e th  the the  he i e id  ide idea dea  ea o a of  of  of e f ex  exa exam xams ams, ms,  s, i , it  it' it's t's  's t s th  the the  he o e on  onl only nly  ly t y ti  tim time ime  me i e i   i w i wa  wan want ant  nt t t to  to  to k o kn  kno know now  ow e w ev  eve ever very eryt ryth ythi thin hing ing  ng i g in  in  in a n a   a f a fe  few few  ew m w mi  min minu inut nute utes tes  es ? s ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? i ? in  in  in b n bo  boa boar oard ardi rdin ding ing  ng h g ho  hou hous ouse uses ses  es w s we  we  we w e wi  wil will ill  ll s l sa  say say  ay b y bu  bus bush ush  sh b h ba  bab babi abie bies ies  es ? s ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : s : st  stu stup tupi upid pid  id c d ca  cat cats ats  ts w s wo  won won' on't n't  't s t st  sto stop top  op w p wa  wai wail aili ilin ling ing  ng o g or  or  or w r wh  wha what hate atev teve ever ver  er i r it  it  it i t is  is  is t s th  the they hey  ey d y do  do. do.  o. k . km  kmt kmt‚ mt‚Ä t‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i c i ca  can can  an i n im  ima imag magi agin gine ine! ne!  e! w ! we  we  we a e at  att attr ttri trib ribu ibut bute uted ted  ed e d ev  eve ever very ery  ry s y st  str stra tran rang ange nge  ge s e so  sou soun ound unds nds  ds t s to  to  to w o wi  wit witc itch tche ches hes  es & s &   & b & bu  bus bush ush  sh b h ba  bab babi abie bies ies  es = s =)  =)) =))  )) : ) :'  :'( :'(  '( e ( ev  evu evu  vu p u pi  pip pipo ipo  po ? o ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : c : ch  chi chin hina ina  na i a in  inv inve nven vent ente nted ted  ed e d ex  exa exam xams ams. ms.‚ s.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù k ù ka  kai kai, ai,  i, s , so  sor sorr orry rry  ry o y o!  o!  o! s ! sh  she she  he s e sh  shl shld hld  ld h d ha  hav have ave  ve a e al  all allo llow lowe owed wed  ed u d u   u f u fo  for for  or a r a   a y a yr  yr  yr = r =)  =)) =))  )) : ) :   : i : i   i w i wa  wan want ante nted ted  ed t d th  tha that hat  at e t ex  exp expe xper peri erie rien ienc ence nce  ce b e bu  but but  ut m t my  my  my m y mu  mum mum  um w m wa  was wasn asn' sn't n't  't a t a   a f a fa  fan fan  an o n of  of  of b f bo  boa boar oard ardi rdin ding ing  ng s g sc  sch scho choo hool ools ols  ls ! s !!  !!! !!!  !! : ! :   : i : if  ifu ifun funa unan nany anya nya, ya,  a, m , mo  mor more ore  re t e th  tha than han  an a n a   a f a fr  fri frie rien iend end  nd i d is  is  is n s ne  nex next ext. xt.‚ t.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù y ù yo  you you  ou m u ma  mak make ake  ke i e it  it  it l t lo  loo look ook  ok i k it  it' it's t's  's m s ma  mag magi agic gic  ic ? c ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : e : ea  ear earn arne rned ned  ed i d it  it  it - t -   - t - th  the the  he w e we  wee week eekn eknd knd‚ nd‚Ä d‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù it  it' it's t's  's a s a   a s a so  son song ong  ng y g yo  you you  ou f u fa  fal fall all  ll i l in  in  in l n lo  lov love ove  ve w e wi  wit with ith  th t h th  the the  he f e fi  fir firs irst rst  st t t ti  tim time ime  me y e yo  you you  ou l u li  lis list iste sten ten  en t n to  to  to i o it  it  it : t :   : c : ca  cau caus ause use  se i e i   i s i se  see see  ee n e no  nob nobo obod body ody, dy,  y, n , no  nob nobo obod body ody  dy b y bu  but but  ut y t yo  you you, ou,  u, y , yo  you you, ou,  u, y , yo  you you. ou.‚ u.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i k i kn  kno know now  ow ? w ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : s : so  so  so i o in  in  in l n lo  lov love ove  ve ? e ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i t i th  tho thou houg ough ught ght  ht t t th  the the  he b e bi  bib bibl ible ble  le a e al  als also lso  so p o pr  pro proh rohi ohib hibi ibit bits its  ts i s it  it? it?  t? : ? :   : w : we  wel well ell  ll h l he  he  he i e is  is  is a s a   a g a go  goo good ood  od m d mu  mus musl usli slim lim  im a m an  and and  nd i d ia  iam iam  am s m su  sur sure ure  re h e he  he  he w e wo  wou woul ould uldn ldn' dn't n't  't w t wa  wan want ant  nt m t me  me  me t e to  to  to d o dr  dri drin rink ink  nk a k al  alc alco lcoh coho ohol hol  ol : l :(  :(  :( . ( ..  ..  .. o . on  one one  ne r e re  rea reas eas  as s s so  som some omet meth ethi thin hing ing  ng a g ab  abo abou bout out  ut t t th  thi this his  is f s fa  fac face ace  ce m e ma  mak make akes kes  es m s me  me  me v e ve  ver very ery  ry h y ha  hap happ appy ppy  py ? y ??  ??  ?? l ? lo  lol lol  ol : l :   : a : ad  add add  dd m d me  me  me o e on  on  on b n bb  bbm bbm  bm p m pi  pin pin  in 7 n 7f  7ff 7ff0 ff0f f0f2 0f2c f2cb 2cb. cb.  b. o . on  on  on w n wh  wha what hats atsa tsap sapp app  pp 0 p 08  081 0816 8165 1652 6528 5289 2897 8977 9773 773‚ 73‚Ä 3‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lov love ove  ve i e is  is  is a s a   a c a co  con cont onti ntin tinu inuo nuou uous ous  us p s pr  pro proc roce oces cess ess. ss.  s. ? . ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : # : #t  #tr #tru true rue  ue " e ":  ":  ": l : lo  lov love ove  ve i e is  is  is a s a   a c a co  con cont onti ntin tinu inuo nuou uous ous  us p s pr  pro proc roce oces cess ess. ss." s."‚ ."‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù y ù ye  yes yess esss ssss ssss ssss sss  ss ? s ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : i : i   i w i wi  wil will ill  ll l l lo  loo look ook  ok f k fo  for for  or y r yo  you you, ou,  u, i , i   i w i wi  wil will ill  ll f l fi  fin find ind  nd y d yo  you you, ou,  u, a , an  and and  nd i d i   i w i wi  wil will ill  ll e l ea  eat eat  at y t yo  you you‚ ou‚Ä u‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  the ther here ere  re i e is  is  is b s be  bea beau eaut auty uty  ty i y in  in  in t n th  the the  he s e sm  sma smal mall alle lles lest est  st o t of  of  of t f th  thi thin hing ings ngs  gs o s on  onl only nly  ly i y if  if  if w f we  we  we l e lo  loo look ook  ok c k cl  clo clos lose ose  se e e en  eno enou noug ough ugh. gh.. h... ...  .. c . co  col coll olle llec lect ecti ctin ting ing  ng m g mo  mom mome omen ment ents nts  ts a s an  and and  nd n d ne  nev neve ever ver  er g r gi  giv givi ivin ving ing  ng u g up  up  up o p on  on  on m n my  my  my d y dr  dre drea ream eams ams. ms.. s..  .. i . i   i d i do  don don' on't n't  't e t ev  eve even ven  en k n kn  kno know now  ow i w if  if  if i f i   i w i wi  wil will ill  ll l l lo  loo look ook  ok g k go  goo good ood  od f d fo  for for  or m r my  my  my w y we  wed wedd eddi ddin ding ing  ng o g or  or  or n r no  not not, ot,  t, u , un  unt unti ntil til  il t l th  the then hen  en ? n ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? i ? i   i m i mu  mus must ust  st s t sa  say say  ay s y so  som some ome  me o e of  of  of t f th  the thes hese ese  se b e br  bri brid ride ides des  es l s lo  loo look ook  ok s k so  so  so b o bu  bus busy usy  sy ? y ?   ? # ? #s  #so #sor sorr orry rry! ry!  y! a ! al  all alla llah lah  ah y h ya  ya  ya t a ts  tsa tsar sare are, re,  e, a , am  ame amee meen een  en : n :   : i : i   i h i ha  hav have ave  ve b e be  bee been een  en h n ha  hav havi avin ving ing  ng w g we  wei weir eird ird  rd d d dr  dre drea ream eams ams  ms a s ab  abo abou bout out  ut b t bo  bok boko oko  ko h o ha  har hara aram ram  am l m la  lat late atel tely ely. ly.‚ y.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù n ù no  no  no o o or  ord ordi rdin dina inar nary ary  ry l y lo  lov love ove  ve - e -   - s - sa  sad sade ade  de a e ad  adu adu  du m u ma  man mana anag nagi agin ging ing  ng a g an  and and  nd f d fi  fin fina inan nanc anci ncin cing ing  ng u g ur  urb urba rban ban  an i n in  inf infr nfra fras rast astr stru truc ruct uctu ctur ture ure  re - e -   - y - yo  you yout outu utub tube ube  be ? e ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : v : ve  ver very ery  ry m y mu  muc much uch  ch s h so  so! so!  o! ‚ ! ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: s : sa  sad sade ade  de a e ad  adu adu  du i u is  is  is v s ve  ver very ery  ry b y be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful‚ ul‚Ä l‚Ä¶ ‚Ä¶‚ Ä¶‚Ä ¶‚Äù ‚Äù‚ Äù‚Ä ù‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù y ù yo  you you  ou g u gi  giv give ive  ve m e me  me  me t e th  tha that hat  at s t sw  swe swee weet eete etes test est  st t t ta  tab tabo aboo boo  oo ? o ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? a ? ab  abi abi  bi o i o   o : o :   : i : it  ith ithi thin hink ink  nk s k sh  she she' he's e's  's a s al  als also lso  so f o fo  fou foun ound und  nd t d th  the the  he f e fo  fou foun ount unta ntai tain ain  in o n of  of  of y f yo  you yout outh uth  th . h .   . " . ":  ":  ": h : ha  hah haha ahah haha aha  ha " a "b  "bo "boo booh ooha ohar hare aree ree: ee:  e: b : ba  bae bae  ae . e .   . " . ":  ":  ": s : sa  sad sade ade  de a e ad  adu adu  du i u is  is  is v s ve  ver very ery  ry b y be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul ! l !!  !!! !!!  !! : ! :   : t : th  the the  he r e re  rea real eal  al h l he  her hero eroe roes oes  es h s he  her here ere  re a e ar  are are  re t e th  the the  he o e on  one ones nes  es t s th  tha that hat  at s t st  sti stil till ill  ll a l an  ans answ nswe swer wer  er t r th  tha that hat  at b t bo  bob bobo obo  bo a o ay  aye ayed yede edee dee‚ ee‚Ä e‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù n ù na  naw nawa awa  wa o a o!  o!  o! : ! :   : w : we  we  we a e ar  are are  re s e so  sor sorr orry rry, ry,  y, s , si  sip sip  ip s p so  som some ome  me s e sa  sal salt alt  lt t t th  the the  he p e pa  pai pain ain  in : n :   : ! : !!  !!! !!!  !! : ! :   : t : th  the the  he r e re  rea real eal  al h l he  her hero eroe roes oes  es h s he  her here ere  re a e ar  are are  re t e th  the the  he o e on  one ones nes  es t s th  tha that hat  at s t st  sti stil till ill  ll a l an  ans answ nswe swer wer  er i r i   i d i do  don don' on't n't  't f t fo  fol foll ollo llow low  ow h w hi  him him  im a m an  and and  nd i d i   i j i ju  jus just ust  st d t do  don don' on't n't  't l t li  lik like ike  ke s e se  see seei eein eing ing  ng s g so  som some ome  me o e of  of  of y f yo  you you  ou r u rt  rt  rt h t hi  his his  is s s st  stu stup tupi upid pidi idit dity ity  ty o y on  on  on m n my  my  my t y tl  tl! tl!  l! i ! it  it' it's t's  's r s re  rea real eall ally lly  ly a y an  ann anno nnoy noyi oyin ying ing  ng ? g ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? a ? ab  abu abun bun  un h n hu  hua huas uash ashi shi  hi : i :   : y : yo  you you  ou s u sa  sab sabi abi  bi " i ":  ":  ": i : i   i d i do  don don' on't n't  't f t fo  fol foll ollo llow low  ow h w hi  him him  im a m an  and and  nd i d i   i j i ju  jus just ust  st d t do  don don' on't n't  't l t li  lik like ike  ke s e se  see seei eein eing ing  ng s g so  som some ome  me o e of  of  of y f yo  you you  ou r u rt  rt  rt h t hi  his his  is s s st  stu stup tupi upid pidi idit dity ity  ty o y on  on  on m n my  my  my t y tl  tl! tl!  l! l ! lm  lma lmao mao! ao!  o! w ! we  we  we w e wo  won won' on't n't  't e t ev  eve even ven  en t n ta  tak take ake  ke i e it  it  it t t th  the ther here ere  re t e to  tod toda oday day! ay!  y! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? ? ? ?   ? : ? :   : w : wh  who who? ho?  o? w ? wh  who who  ho ? o ?   ? d ? dm  dm  dm ? m ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù n ù no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng i g i   i k i kn  kno know now  ow o w of  of  of a f at  at  at t t th  the the  he m e mo  mo  mo o o o!  o!  o! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???: ??:  ?: w : wh  wha what hat  at h t ha  has has  as h s he  he  he d e do  don done one  ne a e ag  aga agai gain ain  in ? n ?‚  ?‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù c ù co  cos cos  os h s he  he' he's e's  's a s an  ann anno nnoy noyi oyin ying ing  ng ? g ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : e : ev  eve ever very eryo ryon yone one  ne i e is  is  is o s on  on  on h n hi  his his  is c s ca  cas case ase  se n e ne  ne. ne.  e. j . ju  jus just ust  st c t ch  che chec heck ecke cked ked  ed h d hi  his his  is t s tw  twe twee weet eets ets. ts.‚ s.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù ab  abe abeg begy egy! gy!  y! : ! :   : a : ay  aye ayee yeed eede edee dee  ee t e th  the the  he d e do  don don  on i n i   i d i do  don don' on't n't  't f t fo  fol foll ollo llow low  ow h w hi  him him  im a m an  and and  nd i d i   i j i ju  jus just ust  st d t do  don don' on't n't  't l t li  lik like ike  ke s e se  see seei eein eing ing  ng s g so  som some ome  me o e of  of  of y f yo  you you  ou r u rt  rt  rt h t hi  his his  is s s st  stu stup tupi upid pidi idit dity ity  ty o y on  on  on m n my  my  my t y tl  tl! tl!  l! i ! it  it' it's t's  's a s a   a l a lo  lot lot  ot o t of  of  of p f pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le d e do  don don' on't n't  't g t ge  get get  et j t ja  jaz jazz azz  zz m z mu  mus musi usic sic. ic.. c... ...  .. l . lm  lma lmao mao  ao t o th  the thes hese ese  se p e pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le h e ha  hat hate ate  te b e be  bei bein eing ing  ng b g bl  bla blac lack ack  ck s k so  so  so b o ba  bad badd addd ddd  dd ? d ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : v : ve  ver very ery  ry b y be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul ? l ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : w : wo  wow wow  ow c w cu  cut cute ute! te!! e!!  !! " ! ":  ":  ": t : tj  tjo tjo! jo!  o! r ! rt  rt  rt : t :   : m : mi  mis miss iss  ss s s so  sou sout outh uth  th s h su  sud suda udan dan  an ? n ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: a : a   a l a lo  lot lot  ot o t of  of  of p f pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le d e do  don don' on't n't  't g t ge  get get  et j t ja  jaz jazz azz  zz m z mu  mus musi usic sic. ic.. c... ...‚ ..‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù c ù cc  cc: cc:  c: ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù " ù "u  "un "uni uniq niqu ique quel uely ely  ly b y be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful" ul"  l" s " sh  she she  he i e is  is  is b s be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful, ul,  l, k , ka  kai kai  ai ? i ?:  ?:  ?: b : bl  bla blac lack ack  ck i k is  is  is b s be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul . l .   . b . bu  but but  ut n t no  not not  ot t t th  tha that hat  at k t ki  kin kind ind  nd o d of  of  of b f bl  bla blac lack ack  ck p k pl  ple plea leas ease ase  se . e .   . t . th  tha that hat' at's t's  's l s li  lik like ike  ke c e ch  cha char harc arco rcoa coal oal  al b l bl  bla blac lack ack  ck l k lo  lol lol! ol!  l! w ! we  we  we u e un  und unde nder ders erst rsta stan tand and  nd b d be  bea beau eaut auty uty  ty d y di  dif diff iffe ffer fere eren rent ent  nt i t i   i g i gu  gue gues uess ess  ss : s :   : i : if  if  if i f i   i s i se  see see  ee t e th  tha that hat  at k t ki  kin kind ind  nd o d of  of  of p f pe  per pers erso rson son  on i n in  in  in r n re  rea real eal  al l l li  lif life ife  fe , e ,   , i , i'  i'l i'll 'll  ll f l fr  fre frea reak eak  ak . k .   . k . ka  kai kai  ai n i no  no  no p o pl  ple plea leas ease ase  se t e th  the ther here ere' re's e's  's a s a   a l a lo  lot lot  ot o t of  of  of c f co  con conf onfi nfid fide iden denc ence nce  ce i e in  in  in t n th  thi this his  is f s fa  fac face ace! ce!  e! t ! th  tha that hat  at i t is  is  is c s ce  cer cert erta rtai tain ainl inly nly  ly b y be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul ? l ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : o : ob  obv obvi bvio viou ious ousl usly sly  ly . y .‚  .‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù sh  she she  he s e su  sur sure ure  re i e is  is  is : s :   : i : i   i a i ag  agr agre gree ree  ee w e wi  wit with ith  th y h yo  you you  ou s u sh  she she  he i e is  is. is.  s. i . i   i s i sa  saw saw  aw a w a   a c a cl  clo clos lose ose  se u e up  up  up p p pi  pic pict ictu ctur ture ure  re o e of  of  of h f he  her her  er a r an  and and  nd s d sh  she she  he l e lo  loo look ooks oks  ks g s gr  gre grea reat eat! at!! t!!‚ !!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù so  sos sosa osai sai  ai : i :   : t : th  the ther here ere' re's e's  's c s co  con conf onfi nfid fide iden denc ence nce! ce!  e! ‚ ! ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú  Äú t ú th  the ther here ere' re's e's  's a s a   a l a lo  lot lot  ot o t of  of  of c f co  con conf onfi nfid fide iden denc ence nce  ce i e in  in  in t n th  thi this his  is f s fa  fac face ace! ce!  e! t ! th  tha that hat  at i t is  is  is c s ce  cer cert erta rtai tain ainl inly nly  ly b y be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul ? l ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? y ? ye  yes yes  es i s in  in  in s n sh  sha sha  ha a a al  all alla llah lah  ah : h :   : w : wi  wil will ill  ll m l mu  muh muha uham hamm amma mmad madu adu  du b u bu  buh buha uhar hari ari  ri b i be  be  be n e ni  nig nige iger geri eria ria' ia's a's  's n s ne  nex next ext  xt p t pr  pre pres resi esid side iden dent ent? nt?  t? - ? -   - h - ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day! ay!  y! a ! al  all alla llah lah' ah's h's  's k s kh  kha khai hair air! ir!: r!:  !: h : ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay t y to  to  to m o me  me. me.. e..  .. ‚ . ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  the the  he t e th  tho thou houg ough ught ghts hts  ts i s in  in  in m n my  my  my h y he  hea head ead  ad a d ar  are are  re c e co  con cons onst nsta stan tant antl ntly tly  ly b y be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful. ul.. l..  .. i . it  it' it's t's  's a s a   a d a de  def defa efau faul ault ult  lt s t se  set sett etti ttin ting ing. ng.. g... ...  .. n . ne  nev neve ever ver  er g r ge  get gets ets  ts u s ug  ugl ugly gly  ly i y in  in  in t n th  the ther here ere  re ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? h ? he  he  he l e lo  loo look ooks oks  ks l s li  lik like ike  ke h e hu  hug hugh ugh  gh j h ja  jac jack ackm ckma kman man  an ? n ??  ??? ???? ???: ??:  ?: c : cl  cli clin lint int  nt e t ea  eas east astw stwo twoo wood ood, od,  d, r , ro  rom rome ome, me,  e, 1 , 19  196 1960 960s 60s‚ 0s‚Ä s‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù e ù en  eny enya nya  ya | a |   | i | in  in  in y n yo  you your our  ur s r sh  sho shor hore ore. re.. e..  .. h . ha  hah haha ahah haha aha  ha t a th  tha than hank anks nks  ks : s :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: e : en  eny enya nya  ya | a |   | i | in  in  in y n yo  you your our  ur s r sh  sho shor hore ore. re.. e..‚ ..‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i l i li  lik like ike  ke u e ur  ur  ur g r go  goo good ood  od t d ta  tas tast aste ste  te i e in  in  in m n mu  mus musi usic sic  ic ? c ??  ??? ???? ???" ??"  ?" o " oh  oh  oh r h re  rea real eall ally lly? ly?  y? n ? ni  nic nice ice! ce!  e! k ! ke  ken kenn enny nny  ny g y g   g i g is  is  is t s th  the the  he k e ki  kin king ing  ng o g of  of  of j f ja  jaz jazz azz  zz t z to  to  to m o me  me, me,l e,lo ,lol lol  ol h l he  he_ he_a e_af _afr afro froc roce ocen cent entr ntri tric ric: ic:  c: h : he  he  he u e un  und unde nder ders erst rsta stan tand ands nds  ds j s ja  jaz jazz azz  zz m z mu  mus musi usic sic, ic,  c, k , ke  ken kenn enny nny  ny g y g'  g's g's  's p s pr  pr  pr t r th  the the  he m e mo  mom mome omen ment ent  nt | t |   | k | ke  ken kenn enny nny  ny r y re  rem remi emin mind inds nds  ds m s me  me  me a e a   a l a lo  lot lot  ot o t of  of  of m f my  my  my c y ch  chi chil hild ildh ldho dhoo hood ood. od.. d..  .. i . it  it  it w t wa  was was  as i s in  int inte nter tere eres rest esti stin ting ing. ng.. g..  .. f . fo  for fore orev reve ever ver  er i r in  in  in l n lo  lov love ove  ve | e |   | k | ke  ken kenn enny nny  ny g y g   g n g ni  nic nice ice! ce!  e! " ! "m  "ma "may may  ay i y it  it  it b t be  be" be"  e" t " to  top tops ops  ps m s my  my  my l y li  lis list ist  st : t :   : o : on  one one  ne o e of  of  of m f my  my  my f y fa  fav favo avor vori orit rite ites tes. es.  s. a . af  aft afte fter ter  er d r de  deo deor eora ora  ra a a ar  ar  ar m r mo  moi moi  oi c i ch  chr chro hroi roi  oi a i an  and and  nd o d or  ori orin rino inoc noco oco  co f o fl  flo flow low. ow.. w... ...  .. r . rt  rt  rt e t en  eny enya nya  ya | a |   | w | wi  wil wild ild  ld c d ch  chi chil hild ild" ld"  d" n " ni  nic nice icee ceee eeee eee! ee!  e! s ! sa  sam same ame  me h e he  her here ere  re : e :   : i : i   i l i lo  lov love ove  ve l e la  laz lazy azy  zy d y da  day days ays, ys,  s, a , am  ama amar mara aran rant anti ntin tine ine, ne,  e, s , su  sum sumi umir mire ireg regu egus gusa usa, sa,  a, m , ma  mar marc arch rch  ch o h of  of  of t f th  the the  he c e ce  cel celt elts lts, ts,  s, w , wh  wha what hat  at c t ch  chi chil hild ild  ld i d is  is  is t s th  thi this his  is t s to  too too. oo.. o... ...  .. e . en  eny enya nya  ya | a |   | h | ho  hop hope ope  pe h e ha  has has  as a s a   a p a pl  pla plac lace ace  ce i e it  it' it's t's  's d s de  dem demn emn  mn h n ho  hou hour ours urs  rs d s de  dem demn emn  mn i n it  it! it!  t! t ! ti  tir tire ired red  ed o d of  of  of w f wa  wat watc atch tchi chin hing ing  ng s g se  sef sef. ef.. f..  .. l . lo  lol lol, ol,  l, s , so  sou soun ound unds nds  ds s s sc  sca scar cary ary! ry!  y! : ! :   : p : pl  ple plea leas ease ase, se,a e,an ,any anyo nyon yone one  ne k e kn  kno know nows ows  ws w s wh  whe wher here ere  re i e i   i c i ca  can can  an f n fi  fin find ind  nd a d a   a m a ma  man man  an l n li  lik like ike  ke j e je  jes jess esse sse  se w e wa  war ward ard? rd?  d? p ? ps  psy psyc sych ycho chot hoti otic tica ical call ally lly  ly j y je  jea jeal ealo alou lous ous  us a s an  and and  nd n d ne  neu neur euro urot roti otic tica ical call ally lly  ly c y co  con cont ontr ntro trol rol  ol f l fr  fr  fr w r wh  why why  hy a y am  am  am i m i   i u i up  up  up a p at  at  at 6 t 6a  6am 6am? am?  m? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? a ? ay  aye aye! ye!  e! a ! ah  ah  ah a h ah  ahn ahn! hn!  n! n ! no  no  no t o th  tha than hank anks nks  ks ? s ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : t : tr  tru trus rust ust  st m t me  me  me y e yo  you you' ou'd u'd  'd l d lo  lov love ove  ve i e it  it? it?? t??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú  Äú l ú lo  lol lol, ol,  l, s , so  sou soun ound unds nds  ds s s sc  sca scar cary ary! ry!  y! p ! pl  ple plea leas ease ase, se,a e,an ,any anyo nyon yone one  ne k e kn  kno know nows ows  ws w s wh  whe wher here ere  re i e i   i c i ca  can can  an f n fi  fin find ind  nd a d a   a s a so  so  so w o we  we  we n e no  no  no b o bo  bot both oth  th g h ge  get get  et l t li  lif life ife  fe e e ey  ey? ey?  y? a ? ab  abe abeg beg  eg o g o!  o!  o! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???: ??:  ?: u : u   u n u no  no  no k o kn  kno know now  ow b w be  bet bett ette tter ter  er t r th  thi thin hing ing  ng s g se  sef sef? ef?? f??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: a : ay  aye aye! ye!  e! a ! ah  ah  ah a h ah  ahn ahn! hn!  n! n ! no  no  no t o th  tha than hank anks nks  ks ? s ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : t : tr  tru trus rust ust  st m t me  me  me s e se  see see  ee e e eh  ehn ehn! hn!  n! s ! sn  sna snap nap  ap o p ou  out outt utta tta  ta t a th  tha that hat  at n t no  nov nove ovel vel  el a l al  alr alre lrea read eady ady  dy ? y ??  ??? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : a : ay  aye ayee yeee eee? ee?? e??? ???? ???  ?? t ? ty  typ typi ypic pica ical cal  al n l ni  nig nige iger geri eria rian ian  an l n la  lad lady ady? dy?? y??? ???? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú  Äú s ú so  so  so w o we  we  we n e no  no  no b o bo  bot both oth  th g h ge  get get  et l t li  lif life ife  fe e e ey  ey? ey?  y? a ? ab  abe abeg beg  eg o g o!  o!  o! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???: ??:  ?: n : no  no  no n o no  no! no!  o! i ! i   i a i am  am  am a m a   a g a go  goo good ood  od f d fr  fri frie rien iend end  nd o d o.  o.  o. i . i   i w i wa  wan want ant  nt y t yo  you you  ou t u to  to  to d o dr  dre drea ream eam  am r m re  rea reas easo ason sona onab nabl ably bly, ly,  y, w , wi  wit with ithi thin hin  in t n th  the the  he e e ex  exp expe xpec pect ecta ctat tati atio tion ions ons  ns o s of  of  of a f an  an  an " n "n  "no "nor norm orma rmal mal  al m l ma  man man" an"  n" n " no  not not  ot m t me  med medi edio dioc iocr ocre cre  re b e bu  but but. ut.. t... ...  .. ? . ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? su  sur sure ure  re m e mo  mov move oved ved  ed m d me  me, me,w e,wh ,whe when hen  en " n "i  "i  "i r i re  rea read ead" ad"  d" o " or  or  or m r mo  mos most ostl stly tly  ly w y wa  wat watc atch tch  ch s h su  suc such uch  ch l h li  lin line ines nes, es,m s,ma ,mak make akes kes  es m s me  me  me s e sm  smi smil mile ile. le.. e..  .. w . we  we  we g e ge  get get  et c t cl  clo clos lose ose  se t e to  to  to t o th  the them hem  em i m in  in  in r n re  rea real eali alit lity ity  ty b y bu  but but  ut r t re  rea real eali alit lity ity  ty n y na  na  na o a op  ope open pen  en e n ey  eye eye  ye ? e ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? l ? lm  lma lmao mao  ao a o am  ame amen men  en ? n ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???! ??!  ?! u ! u   u g u go  go  go g o gi  gir girl irl  rl ? l ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???: ??:  ?: j : ju  jus just ust  st g t go  go  go a o aw  awa away way? ay?? y??? ???? ???w ??wi ?wil will ill  ll g l ge  get get  et b t ba  bac back ack  ck a k at  at  at y t ya  ya  ya w a wh  whe when hen  en i n i   i f i fi  fin find ind  nd m d my  my  my i y im  imp impr mpro prov rovi ovis vise ised sed  ed ' d 'j  'je 'jes jess esse sse  se w e wa  war ward ard' rd'. d'.  '. c . ch  cha chas hasi asin sing ing  ng m g my  my  my d y dr  dre drea ream eams ams? ms?? s??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lw  lwk lwkm wkmd kmd! md!  d! m ! ma  mas mash asha shaa haal aall alla llah lah! ah!  h! h ! he  he  he i e is  is  is t s th  the the  he m e ma  man man  an i n if  if  if m f my  my  my b y be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul r l re  rea real eali alit lity ity  ty ? y ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : i : i   i s i se  see see  ee w e wh  why why  hy y y yo  you you  ou n u no  not not  ot b t bo  bot both othe ther here ered red? ed?? d??? ???? ???u ??u  ?u h u ha  hav have ave  ve a e a   a n a ne  nea near ear  ar p r pe  per perf erfe rfec fect ect  ct n t ni  nig nigg igga gga, ga,s a,sh ,shi shif hift ift? ft?? t??? ???? ???? ???  ?? i ? i   i j i ju  jus just ust  st l t la  lan land and  nd i d in  in  in e n eu  eur euro urop rope ope  pe n e ni  nig nigg igga gga  ga ? a ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???: ??:  ?: c : ca  cap capt apti ptio tion ion  on t n th  thi this his. is.. s..  .. ‚ . ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù it  it' it's t's  's n s no  not not  ot l t li  lik like ike  ke i e it  it' it's t's  's e s ev  eve even ven  en a n a   a s a sh  sha shar haru aruk ruk  uk k k kh  kha khan han  an m n mo  mov movi ovie vie  ie o e o   o ? o ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? a ? ak  aks aksh ksha shay hay  ay k y ku  kum kuma umar mar  ar i r is  is  is j s ju  jus just ust  st o t ok  oka okay kay  ay ? y ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? t ? th  the the  he l e lo  lov love ove  ve & e &   & r & re  rem reme emem memb embr mbra bran ranc ance nce  ce o e of  of  of a f al  all alla llah lah  ah ( h (s  (sw (swt swt) wt)  t) k ) ke  kee keep eeps eps  ps y s yo  you your our  ur h r he  hea hear eart art  rt l t li  lig ligh ight ghte hter ter, er,  r, p , pe  pea peac eace acef cefu eful ful  ul a l an  and and  nd v d ve  ver very ery  ry h y ha  hap happ appy ppy. py.  y. a . al  alh alha lham hamd amdu mdul duli ulil lill illa llah lah  ah a h al  ala ala  la n a ni  nii niim iima imat matu atul tul  ul i l is  isl isla slam lam. am.  m.  .    