aft fte ter er  r w  wr wri rit iti tin ing ng  g v  vo vol olu lum ume mes es  s o  of of  f "  "m "my my  y w  wa wat atc tch ch" h"  " o  on one ne  e w  wo wou oul uld ld  d t  th thi hin ink nk  k h  he he  e n  ne nev eve ver er  r w  wa wan ant nts ts  s t  to to  o s  se see ee  e g  ge gej ej  j e  ev eve ver er  r c  co cos os  s h  he he' e's 's  s t  th the he  e d  de dev evi vil il, l,  , b  bu but ut  t a  al ala las as. s.. ... ..  . "  "i "in int nte ter ere res est st" t"  " =  =  = p  po pol oli lit iti tic ics cs! s!  ! s  si sig igh gh! h!  ! :  :  : b  bi big ig  g h  hy hyp ypo poc ocr cri rit ite te  e k  ku kuw uwa wa. a.r .rt rt  t :  :  : o  ob obj bj, j,  , s  su suc uch ch  h a  a  a h  hy hyp ypo poc ocr cri rit ite te! e!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù s  su suc uch ch  h a  an an  n e  ev evi vil il  l a  an and nd  d v  vi vil ile le  e m  ma man an  n w  wh who ho  o t  th thi hin ink nks ks  s h  he he  e c  ca can an  n l  li liv ive ve  e f  fo for ore rev eve ver er! r!  ! s  sm smh mh  h a  an and nd  d s  se sen ens nse sel ele les ess ss! s!  ! s  sm smh mh  h :  :  : g  ge gej ej  j a  an and nd  d h  hi his is  s p  po poi oin int ntl tle les ess ss  s c  ca cam amp mpa pai aig ign gns ns. s.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  in ind nde dee eed ed! d!  ! :  :  : j  ju jus ust st  t a  a  a p  po pol oli lit iti tic ici cia ian an. n.  . a  as as  s a  an any ny  y o  ot oth the her er. r.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù a  am ame mee een en  n a  am ame mee een en! n!  ! h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y b  br bro rot oth the her er! r!  ! a  al all lla lah ah' h's 's  s k  kh kha hai air ir  r :  :  : i  i' i'm 'm  m o  of off ffi fic ici cia ial all lly ly  y y  ye yea ear ars rs  s o  ol old ld. d.  . a  al all lla lah ah  h y  ya ya  a r  ra ray aya ya  a n  ni ni  i d  da da  a k  ko kow owa wa. a.  . i  i  i n  ne nee eed ed  d f  fe feb ebr bru rua uar ary ry  y t  to to  o e  en end nd! d!  ! :  :  : u  u  u n  ne nee eed ed  d n  ne nex ext xt  t w  we wee eek ek  k t  to to  o e  en end nd. d.  . u  u  u s  sa say ay? y?  ? :  :  : a  am am  m a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s c  ca car are res es  s w  wi wit ith th  h g  gi gir irl rls ls  s b  be bec eca cau aus use se  e o  of of  f t  th the he  e p  pa pai ain ins ns  s t  th the hey ey  y s  su suf uff ffe fer er  r f  fr fro rom om  m ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù m  me mee een ena na  a w  we wel eld ldo don one ne  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : b  bu but ut  t w  wh why hy? y?  ? ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??" ?": ":  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha har ard rd  d g  gu guy uy  y b  bu but ut  t y  yo you ou  u d  de dey ey  y p  pl pla lay ay  y c  ca can and ndy dy  y c  cr cru rus ush sh. h.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù "  "‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lm lma mao ao  o :  :  : t  te te. e.. ... ..r .re re. e.. ... ..b .bl ble le  e r  rt rt  t :  :  : u  u  u s  sa say ay? y?  ? :  :  : a  am am  m a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s c  ca car are res es  s w  wi wit ith th  h g  gi gir irl rls ls  s b  be bec eca cau aus use se  e o  of of  f t  th the he  e p  pa pai ain ins ns  s t  th the hey ey  y s  su suf uff ffe fer er  r f  fr fro rom om  m ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù‚ ù‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i  i m  mu mus ust st  t a  as asw swe wea ear ar! r!  ! m  mo mov ove vee eee eee eee eee eee ee  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??: ?:  : h  ha har ard rd  d g  gu guy uy  y b  bu buh uh  h y  yo you ou  u k  kn kno now ow  w g  ge get et  t b  be bea ear ard rds ds  s .  .  . d  do don on' n't 't  t m  me me  e :  :| :|  | s  so som ome me  e o  of of  f y  yo you ou  u a  ar are re  e s  su sub ubb bbi bin ing ng  g y  yo you our urs rse sel elv lve ves es  s s  sh sha ha. a.. ..  . ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : ?  ?? ??? ??? ??" ?": ":  : s  so som ome me  e o  of of  f y  yo you ou  u a  ar are re  e s  su sub ubb bbi bin ing ng  g y  yo you our urs rse sel elv lve ves es  s s  sh sha ha. a.. .." ."‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù !  !! !!! !!  ! :  :  : e  en end nd  d o  of of  f d  di dis isc scu cus uss ssi sio ion on! n!! !!  ! r  rt rt  t :  :  : r  rt rt  t :  :  : e  ev eve ven en  n t  th the he  e h  ha har ard rde des est st  t o  of of  f g  gu guy uys ys  s a  ar are re  e s  so sof oft ft  t f  fo for or  r s  so som ome meo eon one ne. e.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lo lov ove ve  e y  yo you ou  u m  mo mor ore re  e d  da dar arl rl  l ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : j  ju jus ust st  t m  ma mad ade de  e m  my my  y d  da day ay. y.  . i  i  i l  lo lov ove ve  e y  yo you ou  u d  da dar arl rli lin ing ng  g ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù g  go god od! d!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??" ?": ":  : b  bo bos oss ss  s c  ch chi hic ick ck  k b  bo bos oss ss  s c  ch chi hic ick ck  k b  bu but ut  t u  u  u s  st sti til ill ll  l d  de dey ey  y g  ge get et  t m  me men ens nst str tru rua ual al  l c  cr cra ram amp mps ps  s :  :p :p" p"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i  i a  ai ain in' n't 't  t n  no no  o b  bo bos oss ss  s c  ch chi hic ick ck  k o  or or  r b  bo bos oss ss  s l  la lad ady dy, y,  , n  ne nev eve ver er  r b  be bee een en  n a  ab abe beg eg! g!  ! n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g w  wr wro ron ong ng  g w  wi wit ith th  h s  so sof oft ft. t.. ..  . e  ev eve ven en  n i  if if  f n  na na  a s  so sof oft ft  t g  gu guy uy, y,  , n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g w  wr wro ron ong ng  g w  wi wit ith th  h t  th tha hat at  t ?  ?? ??? ??  ? s  sm smh mh  h :  :  : h  ha har ard rd  d g  gu guy uy  y b  bu but ut  t y  yo you ou  u n  no no  o f  fi fit it  t p  pl pla lay ay  y t  tw two wo  o c  ch chi hic ics cs‚ s‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lo lol ol! l!  ! s  st sti til ill ll  l n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g w  wr wro ron ong ng  g w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the hem em  m :  :  : ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? s  so sof oft ft  t g  gu guy uys ys  s a  ar are re  e j  ju jus ust st  t s  so so  o .  .. ... ... ... ... ... ... ..  . s  so sof oft ft  t ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù a  ah ah! h!  ! :  :  : t  th the hey ey  y s  sp spe pea eak ak  k l  li lik ike ke  e g  gi gir irl rls ls  s o  on on  n p  ph pho hon one ne  e ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù s  so som ome me  e g  gu guy uy  y j  ju jus ust st  t s  su sub ub' b'd 'd  d s  so som ome meo eon one ne  e w  wi wit ith th  h o  on one ne  e o  of of  f t  th the hes ese se  e h  ha har ard rd  d g  gu guy uy  y t  tw twe wee eet et  t &  &  & d  de del ele let ete ted ed  d i  it it  t b  be bef efo for ore re  e t  th the he  e o  ot oth the her er  r g  gu guy uy  y c  co cou oul uld ld  d s  se see ee. e.. ..  . h  ha har ard rd  d g  gu guy uy  y i  in ind nde dee eed ed! d!  ! w  we we  e d  de dey ey  y o  ob obs bse ser erv rve ve  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? o  or or  r n  ni nig ige ger eri ria ia! a!  ! :  :  : w  wo wor orl rld ld  d l  le lea ead ade der ers rs  s m  ma mar arc rch ch  h a  af aft fte ter er  r k  ki kil ill lli lin ing ng  g o  of of  f a  a  a c  co cou oup upl ple le  e o  of of  f r  ra rac aci cis ist st  t c  ca car art rto too oon oni nis ist sts ts  s i  in in  n f  fr fra ran anc nce ce  e b  bu but ut  t n  no not ot  t f  fo for or  r k  ki kil ill lli lin ing ng  g o  of of  f 1  10 100 000 00s 0s  s o  of of  f i  i  i i  i  i t  ti tir ire re  e :  :  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha har ard rd  d b  ba bab abe be  e b  bu but ut  t n  no not ot  t a  a  a s  si sin ing ngl gle le  e t  to toa oas ast ste ter er. r.  . .  .  . .  .‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù n  na na  a b  br bre rea ead ad? d?‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  li lik ike ke  e s  sm smh mh  h :  :  : ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??" ?": ":  : g  go god od! d!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??" ?": ":  : b  bo bos oss ss  s c  ch chi hic ick ck  k b  bo bos oss ss  s c  ch chi hic ick ck  k b  bu but ut  t u  u  u s  st sti til ill ll  l d  de dey ey  y g  ge get et  t m  me men ens nst str tru rua ual al  l c  cr cra ram amp mps ps  s :  :p :p" p"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù" ù"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù g  gi giv ive ve  e m  me me  e l  lo lov ove ve  e l  li lik ike ke  e n  ne nev eve ver er  r b  be bef efo for ore re, e,  , c  co cos os  s l  la lat ate tel ely ly  y i  i' i'v 've ve  e b  be bee een en  n c  cr cra rav avi vin ing ng  g f  fo for or  r m  mo mor ore re  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? s  so som ome me  e m  me men en  n a  ar are re  e i  in int nte ter ere res est sti tin ing ng  g s  sh sha ha  a ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? q  qu qui uic ick ck  k q  qu que ues est sti tio ion on: n:  : w  wh why hy  y c  ca can an' n't 't  t s  so som ome me  e m  me men en  n m  ma mar arr rry ry  y w  wi wiv ive ves es  s t  th the hey ey  y c  ca can an  n d  do do  o s  so som ome me  e o  ou out ut  t d  do doo oor or  r a  ac act cti tiv ivi vit iti tie ies es  s t  to tog oge get eth the her er  r b  bu but ut  t y  yo you ou  u c  ca can an  n w  wi wit ith th  h y  yo you our ur  r g  gf gf? f?  ? t  tf tf  f ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? a  am am  m d  di dis isg sgu gus ust ste ted ed  d r  re rea eal all lly ly! y!  ! n  no not ot  t a  a  a m  my mys yst ste ter ery ry, y,  , j  ju jus ust st  t n  nu nun una na  a i  is isa sa  a n  ne ne  e k  ka kaw awa wai ai  i f  fo for or  r s  so som ome me  e o  of of  f t  th the hem em  m :  :  : s  st sti til ill ll  l r  re rem ema mai ain ins ns  s a  a  a m  my mys yst ste ter ery ry‚ y‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù m  ma mar arr rry ry  y a  a  a w  wi wif ife fe  e y  yo you ou  u c  ca can an  n p  pr pre res ese sen ent nt  t t  to to  o e  ev eve ver ery ryb ybo bod ody dy! y!  ! p  pa par are ren ent nts ts, s,  , f  fa fam ami mil ily ly, y,  , f  fr fri rie ien end nds ds, s,  , b  bu bus usi sin ine nes ess ss  s a  as ass sso soc oci cia iat ate tes es  s &  &  & c  ca can an  n e  ev eve ven en  n s  st stu tun un  n e  en ene nem emi mie ies es! s!  ! y  ye yes es  s o  o! o!  ! :  :  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú  ú m  ma mar arr rry ry  y a  a  a w  wi wif ife fe  e y  yo you ou  u c  ca can an  n p  pr pre res ese sen ent nt  t t  to to  o e  ev eve ver ery ryb ybo bod ody dy! y!  ! p  pa par are ren ent nts ts, s,  , f  fa fam ami mil ily ly, y,  , f  fr fri rie ien end nds ds, s,  , b  bu bus usi sin ine nes ess ss  s a  as ass sso soc oci cia iat ate tes es  s &  &  & c  ca can an! n!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lo lou oud ud  d i  it it! t!! !!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù s  so sos osa sai ai  i k  ka kam am  m :  :  : m  mo mos ost st  t o  of of  f t  th the hem em  m d  do don on' n't 't  t u  un und nde der ers rst sta tan and nd  d t  th the he  e v  va val alu lue ue  e o  of of  f m  ma mar arr rri ria iag age ge  e t  th tha hat ats ts  s t  th the he  e m  ma maj ajo jor or  r p  pr pro rob obl ble lem em‚ m‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù a  a  a w  wi wif ife fe  e y  yo you ou  u c  ca can an  n p  pr pre res ese sen ent nt  t t  to to  o y  yo you our ur  r f  fa fam ami mil ily ly  y i  is is  s e  ex exc xce cel ell lle len ent nt  t o  oh oh. h.. ... ..  . b  bu but ut  t p  pl ple lea eas ase se  e g  go go  o a  ah ahe hea ead ad  d a  an and nd  d g  ge get et  t a  a  a w  wi wif ife fe  e t  th tha hat at  t c  ca can an  n s  se ser erv rve ve  e a  al all ll  l o  or or  r m  mo mos ost st  t o  of of  f y  yo you our ur  r p  pu pur urp rpo pos ose ses es! s!  ! d  do don on' n't 't  t k  ke kee eep ep  p y  yo you our ur  r w  wi wif ife fe  e a  at at  t h  ho hom ome me  e a  an and nd  d g  go go  o "  "b "bo bor orr rro row owi win ing ng" g"  " e  el elo loq oqu que uen ent nt  t o  or or  r a  as as  s t  th the hey ey  y s  sa say ay  y "  "p "po pol oli lis ish she hed ed" d"  " w  wo wom oma man an  n t  to to  o p  pr pre res ese sen ent nt  t t  to to  o t  th the he  e w  wo wor orl rld ld! d!  ! j  ju jus ust st  t s  st sto top op  p ?  ?  ? l  lo lol ol! l!  ! u  u  u h  ha hav ave ve  e m  mi mis iss sse sed ed  d t  th the he  e p  po poi oin int nt! t!  ! i  i  i m  me mea ean an  n a  a  a p  pr pre res ese sen ent nta tab abl ble le  e w  wi wif ife fe  e f  fo for or  r a  al all ll  l o  oc occ cca cas asi sio ion ons ns  s &  &  & s  so som ome met eti tim ime mes es  s m  mu mul ult lti tip ipu pur urp rpo pos ose se  e s  se sef ef  f :  :  : #  #w #wi wif ife fen eno not otm tmu mul ult lti tip ipu pur urp rpo pos ose set eto too oo  o i  i  i d  do don on' n't 't  t g  ge get et  t w  wh why hy  y t  th the hey ey  y s  st sti til ill ll  l t  th thi hin ink nk  k t  th tha hat at  t w  wa way ay  y w  wa wal all lla lah ahi hi! i!  ! i  if if  f t  th the hey ey  y r  re res esp spe pec ect ct  t t  th the hem ems mse sel elv lve ves es, s,  , a  a  a w  wo wom oma man an  n w  wi wil ill ll  l s  su sur ure re  e r  re res esp spe pec ect ct  t t  th the hem em  m n  no no  o m  ma mat att tte ter er  r w  wh wha hat at! t!  ! l  lm lma mao ao  o i  i  i k  kn kno now ow  w n  na na  a :  :p :p  p :  :  : l  lo loo ooo ool ol. l.  . i  i  i w  wa was as  s m  me mes ess ssi sin ing ng  g w  wi wit ith th  h y  ya ya  a ;  ;) ;)  ) ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù a  ag agr gre ree ee  e t  to to  o d  di dis isa sag agr gre ree ee  e r  re res esp spe pec ect ctf tfu ful ull lly ly! y!  ! o  on onl nly ly  y m  me men en  n w  wi wit ith th  h n  na nap apo pol ole leo eon on  n c  co com omp mpl ple lex ex  x t  th tha hat at  t w  wa wan ant nt  t t  th the hei eir ir  r e  eg ego go  o w  wo wor ors rsh shi hip ipe ped ed  d w  wi wil ill ll  l t  te tel ell ll  l y  yo you ou  u a  a  a w  wo wom oma man an  n i  is is  s "  "t "to too oo  o p  po pol oli lis ish she hed ed" d"  " #  #b #be beg ego gon one ne  e j  ju jus ust st  t h  ha had ad  d t  to to  o r  ra ran ant nt  t t  th tha hat at  t o  ou out ut  t ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? a  al all ll  l i  i  i w  wa wan ant nt  t i  is is  s t  th the he  e t  ta tas ast ste te  e t  th tha hat at  t y  yo you our ur  r l  li lip ips ps  s a  al all llo low ow  w ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? l  lm lma mao ao  o t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou  u k  ko ko  o ?  ?? ??  ? :  :  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : j  ju jus ust st  t h  ha had ad  d t  to to  o r  ra ran ant nt  t t  th tha hat at  t o  ou out ut  t ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù *  *h *ha han and nds ds  s h  he her er  r a  a  a g  gl gla las ass ss  s o  of of  f c  ch chi hil ill lle led ed  d w  wa wat ate ter er* r*‚ *‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù ?  ?? ??  ? :  :  : e  ed ed  d ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : a  al all ll  l i  i  i w  wa wan ant nt  t i  is is  s t  th the he  e t  ta tas ast ste te  e t  th tha hat at  t y  yo you our ur  r l  li lip ips ps  s a  al all llo low ow  w ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù‚ ù‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lo lol ol  l :  :  : a  a' a'a 'a  a b  ba ban ans nsa san an  n w  wa was asa sa  a ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? "  ": ":  : a  al all ll  l i  i  i w  wa wan ant nt  t i  is is  s t  th the he  e t  ta tas ast ste te  e t  th tha hat at  t y  yo you our ur  r l  li lip ips ps  s a  al all llo low ow  w ?  ?? ??? ??? ??" ?"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th the her ere re' e's 's  s a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s a  a  a t  tw twe wee eet et  t o  or or  r a  a  a s  so son ong ng  g t  th tha hat at  t g  go goe oes es  s w  wi wit ith th  h h  ho how ow  w a  am am  m f  fe fee eel eli lin ing ng  g e  ev eve ver ery ry  y t  ti tim ime me. e.  . g  go got ot  t y  yo you ou  u s  st stu tuc uck ck  k o  on on  n m  my my  y b  bo bod ody dy, y,  , o  on on  n m  my my  y b  bo bod ody dy, y,  , l  li lik ike ke  e a  a  a t  ta tat att tto too oo  o ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  tr try ry  y t  to to  o t  te tel ell ll  l y  yo you ou  u "  "n "no no" o"  " b  bu but ut  t m  my my  y b  bo bod ody dy  y k  ke kee eep eps ps  s o  on on  n t  te tel ell lli lin ing ng  g y  yo you ou  u "  "y "ye yes es" s"  " ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  tr try ry  y t  to to  o t  te tel ell ll  l y  yo you ou  u "  "s "st sto top op" p", ",  , b  bu but ut  t y  yo you our ur  r l  li lip ips pst sti tic ick ck  k g  go got ot  t m  me me  e s  so so  o o  ou out ut  t o  of of  f b  br bre rea eat ath th  h ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : a  am amm mma ma  a m  ma mak ake ke  e y  yo you ou  u b  be beg eg  g t  ti til ill ll  l y  yo you ou  u s  sc scr cre rea eam am  m n  na nag ago god ode de  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù a  am ame men en  n :  :  : d  de dea ear ar  r g  go god od, d,  , d  de del eli liv ive ver er  r #  #n #ni nig ige ger eri ria ia  a f  fr fro rom om  m p  ps psy syc ych cho hop opa pat ath ths hs, s,  , e  eg ego got oti tis ist sts ts  s a  an and nd  d s  sc sch chi hiz izo zop oph phr hre ren eni nic ics cs  s ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th the he  e m  mo mom ome men ent nt  t |  |  | k  ke ken enn nny ny  y g  g  g ?  ?? ??  ? t  th tha hat at  t s  so som ome meb ebo bod ody dy  y w  wa was as  s y  yo you ou  u ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? c  co col olo lor orl rle les ess ss  s :  :  : w  wh wha hat at  t c  co col olo lor or  r i  is is  s l  lo lov ove ve? e?‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i  i a  am am  m ?  ?? ??  ? :  :  : y  yo you ou  u m  mu mus ust st  t b  be be  e a  a  a r  ro rom oma man ant nti tic ic  c ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : p  po pou out ut  t n  na na  a f  fi fig igh ght ht? t?? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lr lrt rt  t w  wh why hy  y a  ar are re  e h  he her er  r e  ey eye yes es  s o  op ope pen ene ned ed  d t  th tho ho  o ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? s  sh she he  e s  st sta tay ays ys  s s  sh sha har arp rp  p :  :  : m  me mei ei  i q  qi qir iri ri  i q  qi qir iri ri  i k  ke ken ena nan an  n ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??" ?": ":  : l  lr lrt rt  t w  wh why hy  y a  ar are re  e h  he her er  r e  ey eye yes es  s o  op ope pen ene ned ed  d t  th tho ho  o ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??" ?"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù s  si sil ile len enc nce ce  e t  tr tra ran ans nsl sla lat ate ted ed. d.. ... ..  . h  ha has as  s t  to to  o b  be be  e a  a  a s  sq squ qua uar are re  e r  ro roo oot ot  t o  of of  f n  ne neg ega gat ati tiv ive ve  e z  ze zer ero ro  o ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? i  if if  f w  we we  e o  on onl nly ly  y h  he hea ear ar  r t  th the he  e t  th thi hin ing ngs gs  s w  we we  e w  wa wan ant nt  t t  to to  o h  he hea ear ar, r,  , w  we we  e w  wi wil ill ll  l n  ne nev eve ver er  r k  kn kno now ow  w t  th the he  e t  tr tru rut uth th. h.  . t  ta tab ab! b!  ! l  la lal ala lai ai  i ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha has as  s t  to to  o b  be be  e a  a  a s  sq squ qua uar are re  e r  ro roo oot ot  t o  of of  f n  ne neg ega gat ati tiv ive ve  e z  ze zer ero ro  o ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù n  ne ner erd rd  d ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù d  de des esi sir ire res es  s a  an and nd  d s  se sec ecr cre ret ets ts, s,  , a  ar are ren en' n't 't  t e  ea eas asi sil ily ly  y s  sh sha har are red ed. d.  . i  it it' t's 's  s a  a  a s  sp spe pec eci cia ial al  l f  fe fee eel eli lin ing ng  g w  wh whe hen en  n y  yo you ou  u f  fi fin ind nd  d s  so som ome meo eon one ne  e w  wh who ho  o d  de des ese ser erv rve ves es  s t  th the hem em. m.  . t  th the he  e s  se sec ecr cre ret et  t i  in in  n y  yo you our ur  r s  sm smi mil ile le, e,  , l  lo lou oud ud, d,  , y  ye yet et  t s  so so  o s  si sil ile len ent nt. t.. ... ..  . v  ve ver ery ry  y w  wr wro ron ong ng  g o  o  o ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : ?  ?? ??? ??? ??, ?,  , w  wr wro ron ong ng  g a  as ass ssu sum ump mpt pti tio ion on‚ n‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th the he  e s  sl sli lig igh ght hte tes est st  t o  of of  f w  wh whi his isp spe per ers rs  s c  ca can an  n f  fl flo lou our uri ris ish sh  h n  ne neg ega gat ati tiv ivi vit ity ty, y,  , b  be be  e m  mi min ind ndf dfu ful ul  l o  of of  f w  wh wha hat at  t y  yo you ou  u l  li lis ist ste ten en  n t  to to. o.  . b  bu but ut  t e  eh ehn hn  n ?  ?? ??? ??? ??. ?.. ... ..  . :  :  : e  ei eit ith the her er  r a  a  a n  ne ner erd rd  d o  or or  r a  an an  n i  in int nte tel ell lle lec ect ctu tua ual al, l,  , u  u  u g  go got ott tta ta  a c  ch cho hoo oos ose se  e o  on one ne  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù s  so som ome met eti tim ime mes es  s i  i  i g  gi giv ive ve  e m  my mys yse sel elf lf  f t  th the he  e s  si sil ile len ent nt  t t  tr tre rea eat atm tme men ent nt  t j  ju jus ust st  t b  be bec eca cau aus use se  e w  we we  e c  ca can an  n b  be be  e o  ou our ur  r o  ow own wn  n e  en ene nem emy my  y s  so som ome met eti tim ime mes es. s.  . t  th the he  e n  ni nig igh ght ht  t i  is is  s n  no not ot  t c  cl cle lea ear ar, r,  , t  th the he  e s  st sta tar ars rs  s s  se see eem em  m s  so so  o f  fa far ar  r a  aw awa way ay. y.  . a  ab abi bi  i :  :  : #  #d #de dee eep ep  p "  ": ":  : t  th the he  e s  se sec ecr cre ret et  t i  in in  n y  yo you our ur  r s  sm smi mil ile le, e,  , l  lo lou oud ud, d,  , y  ye yet et  t s  so so  o s  si sil ile len ent nt. t.. ... .." ."‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù ?  ?? ??  ? :  :  : #  #g #gb gba bam am  m "  ": ":  : i  if if  f w  we we  e o  on onl nly ly  y h  he hea ear ar  r t  th the he  e t  th thi hin ing ngs gs  s w  we we  e w  wa wan ant nt  t t  to to  o h  he hea ear ar, r,  , w  we we  e w  wi wil ill ll  l n  ne nev eve ver er  r k  kn kno now ow  w t  th the he  e t  tr tru rut uth th. h." ."‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù o  on on  n c  cl cle lea ear ar  r n  ni nig igh ght hts ts, s,  , t  th the hey ey  y s  se see eem em  m s  so so  o c  cl clo los ose se  e t  to to  o u  us us. s.. ..  . w  we we  e s  sh sho hou oul uld ld  d d  de def efi fin ine ne  e o  ou our ur  r f  fl fla law aws ws  s i  in ins nst ste tea ead ad  d o  of of  f h  hi hid idi din ing ng  g t  th the hem em, m,  , i  it it  t i  is is  s m  mo mor ore re  e l  li lib ibe ber era rat ati tin ing ng. g.  . n  no not ot  t a  a  a p  pr pri rin inc nce ces ess ss  s o  or or  r a  al all ll  l t  th tha hat at  t b  bu but ut  t w  wo wor ort rth thy hy  y o  of of  f a  a  a k  ki kin ing ngs gs  s l  lo lov ove ve  e ?  ?? ??  ? z  ze zer ero ro  o e  ex exp xpe pec ect cta tat ati tio ion ons ns  s h  he hel elp lp! p!  ! :  :  : i  ir iro ron oni nic ic  c h  ho how ow  w i  i  i k  ke kee eep ep  p t  ta tal alk lki kin ing ng  g a  ab abo bou out ut  t p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e l  le let ett tti tin ing ng  g m  me me  e d  do dow own wn, n,  , a  an and nd  d i  i  i k  ke kee eep ep  p l  le let ett tti tin ing ng  g t  th the hem em  m l  le let et  t m  me me  e d  do dow own wn. n.  . t  th tha hat at' t's 's  s h  ho how ow  w "  "i "i  i l  li liv ive ve" e"  " :  :  : t  th tha hat at' t's 's  s h  ho how ow  w i  i  i a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s c  co con ons nso sol ole le  e m  my mys yse sel elf lf‚ f‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù w  we we  e a  ar are re  e o  on onl nly ly  y h  hu hum uma man an, n,  , w  we we  e c  ca can an' n't 't  t h  he hel elp lp  p i  it it  t s  so som ome met eti tim ime mes es  s ?  ?? ??  ? :  :  : m  me me  e t  to too oo! o!  ! d  du dun unn nno no  o w  wh why hy  y i  i  i l  le let et  t i  it it  t b  bo bot oth the her er  r m  me me  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lo lol ol, l,  , n  no not ot  t l  li lit ite ter era ral all lly ly  y :  :  : *  *c *ch cha han ang nge ges es  s n  na nam ame me  e t  to to  o s  sa san anu nus usi si  i j  jn jnr nr, r,y ,yo you ou  u c  ca cal all lle led ed? d?  ? r  rt rt  t n  no not ot  t a  a  a p  pr pri rin inc nce ces ess ss  s o  or or  r a  al all ll  l t  th tha hat at  t b  bu but ut  t w  wo wor ort rth thy hy  y o  of of  f a  a  a k  ki kin ing ngs gs  s l  lo lov ove ve  e ?  ?? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù a  am ame men en! n!  ! t  th tha han ank nks ks  s :  :  : r  rt rt  t i  i  i w  wi wis ish sh  h y  yo you ou  u t  th tha hat at  t :  :  : n  no not ot  t a  a  a p  pr pri rin inc nce ces ess ss  s o  or or  r a  al all ll  l t  th tha hat at  t b  bu but ut  t w  wo wor ort rth thy hy  y o  of of  f a  a  a k  ki kin ing ngs gs  s l  lo lov ove ve  e ?  ?? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù a  a  a m  ma man an  n d  do doe oes esn sn' n't 't  t n  ne nee eed ed  d a  a  a t  th thr hro ron one ne  e t  to to  o b  be be  e a  a  a k  ki kin ing ng, g,  , e  ev eve ver ery ry  y g  go goo ood od  d m  ma man an  n i  is is  s a  a  a k  ki kin ing ng! g!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  ti tim ime me  e i  in inv nve ves est ste ted ed  d i  in in  n t  th the he  e r  ri rig igh ght ht  t p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e i  is is  s f  fa far ar  r m  mo mor ore re  e p  pr pro rof ofi fit ita tab abl ble le  e t  th tha han an  n m  ma mat ate ter eri ria ial al  l i  in inv nve ves est stm tme men ent nt. t.  . y  ye yes es  s f  fa fa! a!  ! :  :  : a  ab abi bi? i?  ? :  :  : a  a  a m  ma man an  n d  do doe oes esn sn' n't 't  t n  ne nee eed ed  d a  a  a t  th thr hro ron one ne  e t  to to  o b  be be  e a  a  a k  ki kin ing ng, g,  , e  ev eve ver ery ry  y g  go goo ood od  d m  ma man an  n i  is is  s a  a  a k  ki kin ing ng! g!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù‚ ù‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù ?  ?? ??  ? :  :  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : t  ti tim ime me  e i  in inv nve ves est ste ted ed  d i  in in  n t  th the he  e r  ri rig igh ght ht  t p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e i  is is  s f  fa far ar  r m  mo mor ore re  e p  pr pro rof ofi fit ita tab abl ble le  e t  th tha han an  n m  ma mat ate ter eri ria ial al  l i  in inv nve ves est stm tme men ent nt. t.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i  i l  le lea ear arn rn  n t  th thi his is  s e  ev eve ver ery ryd yda day ay  y n  ne nev eve ver er  r s  st sto top op  p g  gi giv ivi vin ing ng  g y  yo you our ur  r b  br bri rig igh ght ht  t s  sm smi mil ile le. e.  . e  ev eve ven en  n i  if if  f y  ya ya  a t  te tee eet eth th  h i  is is  s b  br bro row own wn  n ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e w  wh who ho  o s  st sti tic ick ck  k w  wi wit ith th  h y  yo you ou  u r  re reg ega gar ard rdl dle les ess ss  s o  of of  f h  ho how ow  w d  di dif iff ffi fic icu cul ult lt  t y  yo you ou  u a  ar are re  e w  wo wor ort rth th  h k  ke kee eep epi pin ing ng. g.  . n  no not ot  t a  at at  t a  al all ll  l :  :  : s  sh sha ha  a n  no not ot  t a  a  a r  re rea eas aso son on  n t  to to  o b  be be  e d  di dif iff ffi fic icu cul ult lt  t ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú  ú p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e w  wh who ho  o s  st sti tic ick ck  k w  wi wit ith th  h y  yo you ou  u r  re reg ega gar ard rdl dle les ess ss  s o  of of  f h  ho how ow  w d  di dif iff ffi fic icu cul ult lt  t y  yo you ou  u a  ar are re  e w  wo wor ort rth th  h s  so som ome met eti tim ime mes es  s e  ex exp xpl pla lan ana nat ati tio ion ons ns  s a  ar are re  e w  wo wor ort rth thl hle les ess ss, s,  , w  we we  e h  he hea ear ar  r w  wh wha hat at  t w  we we  e w  wa wan ant nt  t t  to to  o h  he hea ear ar. r.  . p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e w  wh who ho  o m  ma mak ake ke  e u  us us  s s  sm smi mil ile le  e w  wi wit ith tho hou out ut  t s  sa say ayi yin ing ng  g a  a  a w  wo wor ord rd. d.  . i  i  i m  ma man ana nag age ge  e t  to to  o s  st sta tay ay  y g  ge gen ene ner era ral all lly ly  y h  ha hap app ppy py  y e  ev eve ven en  n w  wh whe hen en  n l  li lif ife fe  e g  ge get ets ts  s s  sh shi hit itt tty ty. y.. ... ..  . i  it it' t's 's  s k  ki kin ind nda da  a a  aw awe wes eso som ome me  e a  at at  t t  th the he  e m  mo mom ome men ent nt. t.. ... ..  . u  ur urb rba ban an  n w  wa wat ate ter er  r f  fr fro ron ont nts ts  s a  as as  s t  ti tic ick cki kin ing ng  g t  ti tim ime me  e b  bo bom omb mbs bs  s l  li lis ist ste ten eni nin ing ng  g t  to to  o m  mu mus usi sic ic  c w  wi wit ith th  h l  ly lyr yri ric ics cs  s w  we we  e a  ar are re  e a  af afr fra rai aid id  d t  to to  o s  sa say ay. y.. ... ..  . m  mi min ind nd  d f  fu ful ull ll  l o  of of  f w  wo won ond nde der er. r.. ..  . t  th the he  e e  el ela las ast sti tic ici cit ity ty  y o  of of  f m  my my  y s  so sou oul ul. l.. ..  . l  lo lol ol! l!  ! :  :  : s  su suc uch ch  h p  pr pro rof ofo fou oun und nd  d w  wi wis isd sdo dom om  m "  ": ":  : o  on onc nce ce  e a  a  a h  ha hau aus usa sa  a a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s a  an an  n i  il ill lli lit ite ter era rat ate te" e"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lo lol ol  l :  :  : "  ": ":  : t  th the he  e e  el ela las ast sti tic ici cit ity ty  y o  of of  f m  my my  y s  so sou oul ul. l.. .." ."  " h  hm hmm mmm mmm mm‚ m‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù b  ba bar ari ri  i k  ka kaw awa wai ai  i ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : "  "m "my my  y p  pe pep epp ppo po  o m  my my  y p  pe pep epp ppo po" o"  " ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? i  in in  n h  hi his is  s z  zo zon one ne  e t  to tod oda day ay‚ y‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù s  so so  o g  gm gmb mb' b's 's  s g  gr gre rea eat at  t g  gr gra ran and nd  d m  mo mot oth the her er  r w  wa was as  s f  fr fro rom om  m i  im imo mo  o s  st sta tat ate te  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? s  sa san ann nnu nu  u r  ro roc och cha has as  s ?  ?  ? ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : r  ro rot otl tlm lma mao ao  o "  ": ":  : s  so so  o g  gm gmb mb' b's 's  s g  gr gre rea eat at  t g  gr gra ran and nd  d m  mo mot oth the her er  r w  wa was as  s f  fr fro rom om  m i  im imo mo  o s  st sta tat ate te  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? s  sa san ann nnu nu  u r  ro roc och cha has as  s ?  ?" ?"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù k  ka kaw awa wai ai  i b  ba ba  a ?  ?? ??? ??? ??l ?lm lma mao ao  o :  :  : l  lo lol ol! l!  ! m  mu muh uha ham amm mma mad adu du  u o  ok oke kec ech chu huk ukw kwu wu  u b  bu buh uha har ari ri  i .  .  . "  "  " s  so so  o g  gm gmb mb' b's 's  s g  gr gre rea eat at  t g  gr gra ran and nd  d m  mo mot oth the her er  r w  wa was as  s f  fr fro rom om  m i  im imo mo  o s  st sta tat ate te  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? s  sa san ann nnu nu  u r  ro roc och cha has as  s ?  ?" ?"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lm lma mao ao  o :  :  : l  lo lol ol! l!  ! m  mu muh uha ham amm mma mad adu du  u o  ok oke kec ech chu huk ukw kwu wu  u b  bu buh uha har ari ri  i .  .  . "  ": ":  : s  so so  o g  gm gmb mb' b's 's  s g  gr gre rea eat at  t g  gr gra ran and nd  d m  mo mot oth the her er  r w  wa was as  s f  fr fro rom om  m i  im imo mo  o s  st sta tat ate te  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? s  sa san ann nnu nu  u r  ro roc och cha has as  s ?  ?" ?"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù c  ca cal alc lcu cul ula lat ati tin ing ng  g t  th the he  e t  tr tru rue ue  e c  co cos ost st  t o  of of  f e  en ene ner erg rgy gy  y s  st sto tor ora rag age ge  e b  by by  y t  ti tim im  m h  he hen enn nne nes ess sse sey ey. y.  . s  su sus ust sta tai ain ina nab abl ble le  e c  ci cit iti tie ies es: s:  : i  in inf nfr fra ras ast str tru ruc uct ctu tur ure re  e c  co cos ost sts ts  s +  +  + u  ur urb rba ban an  n g  gr gro row owt wth th  h m  ma man ana nag age gem eme men ent nt  t l  lo lol ol! l!  ! w  we we  e a  al all ll  l s  se see ee  e e  el ele leg ega gan anc nce ce  e d  di dif iff ffe fer ere ren ent ntl tly ly  y i  i  i g  gu gue ues ess ss. s.. ... ..  . l  lu lup upi pit ita ta  a l  lo loo ook oks ks  s f  fu fun unn nny ny! y!  ! c  co cos os  s u  u  u f  fo for ore rev eve ver er  r m  my my  y l  la lad ady dy, y,  , f  fo for ore rev eve ver er  r m  my my  y b  ba bab aby by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ?? ? afte fter ter  er w r wr  wri writ riti itin ting ing  ng v g vo  vol volu olum lume umes mes  es o s of  of  of " f "m  "my "my  my w y wa  wat watc atch tch" ch"  h" o " on  one one  ne w e wo  wou woul ould uld  ld t d th  thi thin hink ink  nk h k he  he  he n e ne  nev neve ever ver  er w r wa  wan want ants nts  ts t s to  to  to s o se  see see  ee g e ge  gej gej  ej e j ev  eve ever ver  er c r co  cos cos  os h s he  he' he's e's  's t s th  the the  he d e de  dev devi evil vil, il,  l, b , bu  but but  ut a t al  ala alas las. as.. s... ...  .. " . "i  "in "int inte nter tere eres rest est" st"  t" = " =   = p = po  pol poli olit liti itic tics ics! cs!  s! s ! si  sig sigh igh! gh!  h! : ! :   : b : bi  big big  ig h g hy  hyp hypo ypoc pocr ocri crit rite ite  te k e ku  kuw kuwa uwa. wa.r a.rt .rt  rt : t :   : o : ob  obj obj, bj,  j, s , su  suc such uch  ch a h a   a h a hy  hyp hypo ypoc pocr ocri crit rite ite! te!‚ e!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù su  suc such uch  ch a h an  an  an e n ev  evi evil vil  il a l an  and and  nd v d vi  vil vile ile  le m e ma  man man  an w n wh  who who  ho t o th  thi thin hink inks nks  ks h s he  he  he c e ca  can can  an l n li  liv live ive  ve f e fo  for fore orev reve ever ver! er!  r! s ! sm  smh smh  mh a h an  and and  nd s d se  sen sens ense nsel sele eles less ess! ss!  s! s ! sm  smh smh  mh : h :   : g : ge  gej gej  ej a j an  and and  nd h d hi  his his  is p s po  poi poin oint intl ntle tles less ess  ss c s ca  cam camp ampa mpai paig aign igns gns. ns.‚ s.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù in  ind inde ndee deed eed! ed!  d! : ! :   : j : ju  jus just ust  st a t a   a p a po  pol poli olit liti itic tici icia cian ian. an.  n. a . as  as  as a s an  any any  ny o y ot  oth othe ther her. er.‚ r.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù am  ame amee meen een  en a n am  ame amee meen een! en!  n! h ! ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay b y br  bro brot roth othe ther her! er!  r! a ! al  all alla llah lah' ah's h's  's k s kh  kha khai hair air  ir : r :   : i : i'  i'm i'm  'm o m of  off offi ffic fici icia cial iall ally lly  ly y y ye  yea year ears ars  rs o s ol  old old. ld.  d. a . al  all alla llah lah  ah y h ya  ya  ya r a ra  ray raya aya  ya n a ni  ni  ni d i da  da  da k a ko  kow kowa owa. wa.  a. i . i   i n i ne  nee need eed  ed f d fe  feb febr ebru brua ruar uary ary  ry t y to  to  to e o en  end end! nd!  d! : ! :   : u : u   u n u ne  nee need eed  ed n d ne  nex next ext  xt w t we  wee week eek  ek t k to  to  to e o en  end end. nd.  d. u . u   u s u sa  say say? ay?  y? : ? :   : a : am  am  am a m al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys c s ca  car care ares res  es w s wi  wit with ith  th g h gi  gir girl irls rls  ls b s be  bec beca ecau caus ause use  se o e of  of  of t f th  the the  he p e pa  pai pain ains ins  ns t s th  the they hey  ey s y su  suf suff uffe ffer fer  er f r fr  fro from rom  om ? m ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù m ù me  mee meen eena ena  na w a we  wel weld eldo ldon done one  ne ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : b : bu  but but  ut w t wh  why why? hy?  y? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  har hard ard  rd g d gu  guy guy  uy b y bu  but but  ut y t yo  you you  ou d u de  dey dey  ey p y pl  pla play lay  ay c y ca  can cand andy ndy  dy c y cr  cru crus rush ush. sh.‚ h.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù " ù "‚  "‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lm  lma lmao mao  ao : o :   : t : te  te. te.. e... ...r ..re .re. re.. e... ...b ..bl .ble ble  le r e rt  rt  rt : t :   : u : u   u s u sa  say say? ay?  y? : ? :   : a : am  am  am a m al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys c s ca  car care ares res  es w s wi  wit with ith  th g h gi  gir girl irls rls  ls b s be  bec beca ecau caus ause use  se o e of  of  of t f th  the the  he p e pa  pai pain ains ins  ns t s th  the they hey  ey s y su  suf suff uffe ffer fer  er f r fr  fro from rom  om ? m ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù‚ Äù‚Ä ù‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i m i mu  mus must ust  st a t as  asw aswe swea wear ear! ar!  r! m ! mo  mov move ovee veee eeee eeee eeee eeee eee  ee ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???: ??:  ?: h : ha  har hard ard  rd g d gu  guy guy  uy b y bu  buh buh  uh y h yo  you you  ou k u kn  kno know now  ow g w ge  get get  et b t be  bea bear eard ards rds  ds . s .   . d . do  don don' on't n't  't m t me  me  me : e :|  :|  :| s | so  som some ome  me o e of  of  of y f yo  you you  ou a u ar  are are  re s e su  sub subb ubbi bbin bing ing  ng y g yo  you your ours urse rsel selv elve lves ves  es s s sh  sha sha. ha.. a..  .. ? . ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": s : so  som some ome  me o e of  of  of y f yo  you you  ou a u ar  are are  re s e su  sub subb ubbi bbin bing ing  ng y g yo  you your ours urse rsel selv elve lves ves  es s s sh  sha sha. ha.. a.." .."‚ ."‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ! ù !!  !!! !!!  !! : ! :   : e : en  end end  nd o d of  of  of d f di  dis disc iscu scus cuss ussi ssio sion ion! on!! n!!  !! r ! rt  rt  rt : t :   : r : rt  rt  rt : t :   : e : ev  eve even ven  en t n th  the the  he h e ha  har hard arde rdes dest est  st o t of  of  of g f gu  guy guys uys  ys a s ar  are are  re s e so  sof soft oft  ft f t fo  for for  or s r so  som some omeo meon eone one. ne.‚ e.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lov love ove  ve y e yo  you you  ou m u mo  mor more ore  re d e da  dar darl arl  rl ? l ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : j : ju  jus just ust  st m t ma  mad made ade  de m e my  my  my d y da  day day. ay.  y. i . i   i l i lo  lov love ove  ve y e yo  you you  ou d u da  dar darl arli rlin ling ing  ng ? g ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù g ù go  god god! od!  d! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": b : bo  bos boss oss  ss c s ch  chi chic hick ick  ck b k bo  bos boss oss  ss c s ch  chi chic hick ick  ck b k bu  but but  ut u t u   u s u st  sti stil till ill  ll d l de  dey dey  ey g y ge  get get  et m t me  men mens enst nstr stru trua rual ual  al c l cr  cra cram ramp amps mps  ps : s :p  :p" :p"‚ p"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i a i ai  ain ain' in't n't  't n t no  no  no b o bo  bos boss oss  ss c s ch  chi chic hick ick  ck o k or  or  or b r bo  bos boss oss  ss l s la  lad lady ady, dy,  y, n , ne  nev neve ever ver  er b r be  bee been een  en a n ab  abe abeg beg! eg!  g! n ! no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng w g wr  wro wron rong ong  ng w g wi  wit with ith  th s h so  sof soft oft. ft.. t..  .. e . ev  eve even ven  en i n if  if  if n f na  na  na s a so  sof soft oft  ft g t gu  guy guy, uy,  y, n , no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng w g wr  wro wron rong ong  ng w g wi  wit with ith  th t h th  tha that hat  at ? t ??  ??? ???  ?? s ? sm  smh smh  mh : h :   : h : ha  har hard ard  rd g d gu  guy guy  uy b y bu  but but  ut y t yo  you you  ou n u no  no  no f o fi  fit fit  it p t pl  pla play lay  ay t y tw  two two  wo c o ch  chi chic hics ics‚ cs‚Ä s‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lol lol! ol!  l! s ! st  sti stil till ill  ll n l no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng w g wr  wro wron rong ong  ng w g wi  wit with ith  th t h th  the them hem  em : m :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? so  sof soft oft  ft g t gu  guy guys uys  ys a s ar  are are  re j e ju  jus just ust  st s t so  so  so . o ..  ... .... .... .... .... .... ...  .. s . so  sof soft oft  ft ‚ t ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù ah  ah! ah!  h! : ! :   : t : th  the they hey  ey s y sp  spe spea peak eak  ak l k li  lik like ike  ke g e gi  gir girl irls rls  ls o s on  on  on p n ph  pho phon hone one  ne ‚ e ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù so  som some ome  me g e gu  guy guy  uy j y ju  jus just ust  st s t su  sub sub' ub'd b'd  'd s d so  som some omeo meon eone one  ne w e wi  wit with ith  th o h on  one one  ne o e of  of  of t f th  the thes hese ese  se h e ha  har hard ard  rd g d gu  guy guy  uy t y tw  twe twee weet eet  et & t &   & d & de  del dele elet lete eted ted  ed i d it  it  it b t be  bef befo efor fore ore  re t e th  the the  he o e ot  oth othe ther her  er g r gu  guy guy  uy c y co  cou coul ould uld  ld s d se  see see. ee.. e..  .. h . ha  har hard ard  rd g d gu  guy guy  uy i y in  ind inde ndee deed eed! ed!  d! w ! we  we  we d e de  dey dey  ey o y ob  obs obse bser serv erve rve  ve ? e ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? o ? or  or  or n r ni  nig nige iger geri eria ria! ia!  a! : ! :   : w : wo  wor worl orld rld  ld l d le  lea lead eade ader ders ers  rs m s ma  mar marc arch rch  ch a h af  aft afte fter ter  er k r ki  kil kill illi llin ling ing  ng o g of  of  of a f a   a c a co  cou coup oupl uple ple  le o e of  of  of r f ra  rac raci acis cist ist  st c t ca  car cart arto rtoo toon ooni onis nist ists sts  ts i s in  in  in f n fr  fra fran ranc ance nce  ce b e bu  but but  ut n t no  not not  ot f t fo  for for  or k r ki  kil kill illi llin ling ing  ng o g of  of  of 1 f 10  100 1000 000s 00s  0s o s of  of  of i f i   i i i i   i t i ti  tir tire ire  re : e :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  har hard ard  rd b d ba  bab babe abe  be b e bu  but but  ut n t no  not not  ot a t a   a s a si  sin sing ingl ngle gle  le t e to  toa toas oast aste ster ter. er.  r. . . .   . . . .‚  .‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù n ù na  na  na b a br  bre brea read ead? ad?‚ d?‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù li  lik like ike  ke s e sm  smh smh  mh : h :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": g : go  god god! od!  d! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": b : bo  bos boss oss  ss c s ch  chi chic hick ick  ck b k bo  bos boss oss  ss c s ch  chi chic hick ick  ck b k bu  but but  ut u t u   u s u st  sti stil till ill  ll d l de  dey dey  ey g y ge  get get  et m t me  men mens enst nstr stru trua rual ual  al c l cr  cra cram ramp amps mps  ps : s :p  :p" :p"‚ p"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù" Äù"‚ ù"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù g ù gi  giv give ive  ve m e me  me  me l e lo  lov love ove  ve l e li  lik like ike  ke n e ne  nev neve ever ver  er b r be  bef befo efor fore ore, re,  e, c , co  cos cos  os l s la  lat late atel tely ely  ly i y i'  i'v i've 've  ve b e be  bee been een  en c n cr  cra crav ravi avin ving ing  ng f g fo  for for  or m r mo  mor more ore  re ? e ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? s ? so  som some ome  me m e me  men men  en a n ar  are are  re i e in  int inte nter tere eres rest esti stin ting ing  ng s g sh  sha sha  ha ? a ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? q ? qu  qui quic uick ick  ck q k qu  que ques uest esti stio tion ion: on:  n: w : wh  why why  hy c y ca  can can' an't n't  't s t so  som some ome  me m e me  men men  en m n ma  mar marr arry rry  ry w y wi  wiv wive ives ves  es t s th  the they hey  ey c y ca  can can  an d n do  do  do s o so  som some ome  me o e ou  out out  ut d t do  doo door oor  or a r ac  act acti ctiv tivi ivit viti itie ties ies  es t s to  tog toge oget geth ethe ther her  er b r bu  but but  ut y t yo  you you  ou c u ca  can can  an w n wi  wit with ith  th y h yo  you your our  ur g r gf  gf? gf?  f? t ? tf  tf  tf ? f ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? a ? am  am  am d m di  dis disg isgu sgus gust uste sted ted  ed r d re  rea real eall ally lly! ly!  y! n ! no  not not  ot a t a   a m a my  mys myst yste ster tery ery, ry,  y, j , ju  jus just ust  st n t nu  nun nuna una  na i a is  isa isa  sa n a ne  ne  ne k e ka  kaw kawa awai wai  ai f i fo  for for  or s r so  som some ome  me o e of  of  of t f th  the them hem  em : m :   : s : st  sti stil till ill  ll r l re  rem rema emai main ains ins  ns a s a   a m a my  mys myst yste ster tery ery‚ ry‚Ä y‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù m ù ma  mar marr arry rry  ry a y a   a w a wi  wif wife ife  fe y e yo  you you  ou c u ca  can can  an p n pr  pre pres rese esen sent ent  nt t t to  to  to e o ev  eve ever very eryb rybo ybod body ody! dy!  y! p ! pa  par pare aren rent ents nts, ts,  s, f , fa  fam fami amil mily ily, ly,  y, f , fr  fri frie rien iend ends nds, ds,  s, b , bu  bus busi usin sine ines ness ess  ss a s as  ass asso ssoc soci ocia ciat iate ates tes  es & s &   & c & ca  can can  an e n ev  eve even ven  en s n st  stu stun tun  un e n en  ene enem nemi emie mies ies! es!  s! y ! ye  yes yes  es o s o!  o!  o! : ! :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú  Äú m ú ma  mar marr arry rry  ry a y a   a w a wi  wif wife ife  fe y e yo  you you  ou c u ca  can can  an p n pr  pre pres rese esen sent ent  nt t t to  to  to e o ev  eve ever very eryb rybo ybod body ody! dy!  y! p ! pa  par pare aren rent ents nts, ts,  s, f , fa  fam fami amil mily ily, ly,  y, f , fr  fri frie rien iend ends nds, ds,  s, b , bu  bus busi usin sine ines ness ess  ss a s as  ass asso ssoc soci ocia ciat iate ates tes  es & s &   & c & ca  can can! an!‚ n!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lou loud oud  ud i d it  it! it!! t!!‚ !!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù so  sos sosa osai sai  ai k i ka  kam kam  am : m :   : m : mo  mos most ost  st o t of  of  of t f th  the them hem  em d m do  don don' on't n't  't u t un  und unde nder ders erst rsta stan tand and  nd t d th  the the  he v e va  val valu alue lue  ue o e of  of  of m f ma  mar marr arri rria riag iage age  ge t e th  tha that hats ats  ts t s th  the the  he m e ma  maj majo ajor jor  or p r pr  pro prob robl oble blem lem‚ em‚Ä m‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù a   a w a wi  wif wife ife  fe y e yo  you you  ou c u ca  can can  an p n pr  pre pres rese esen sent ent  nt t t to  to  to y o yo  you your our  ur f r fa  fam fami amil mily ily  ly i y is  is  is e s ex  exc exce xcel cell elle llen lent ent  nt o t oh  oh. oh.. h... ...  .. b . bu  but but  ut p t pl  ple plea leas ease ase  se g e go  go  go a o ah  ahe ahea head ead  ad a d an  and and  nd g d ge  get get  et a t a   a w a wi  wif wife ife  fe t e th  tha that hat  at c t ca  can can  an s n se  ser serv erve rve  ve a e al  all all  ll o l or  or  or m r mo  mos most ost  st o t of  of  of y f yo  you your our  ur p r pu  pur purp urpo rpos pose oses ses! es!  s! d ! do  don don' on't n't  't k t ke  kee keep eep  ep y p yo  you your our  ur w r wi  wif wife ife  fe a e at  at  at h t ho  hom home ome  me a e an  and and  nd g d go  go  go " o "b  "bo "bor borr orro rrow rowi owin wing ing" ng"  g" e " el  elo eloq loqu oque quen uent ent  nt o t or  or  or a r as  as  as t s th  the they hey  ey s y sa  say say  ay " y "p  "po "pol poli olis lish ishe shed hed" ed"  d" w " wo  wom woma oman man  an t n to  to  to p o pr  pre pres rese esen sent ent  nt t t to  to  to t o th  the the  he w e wo  wor worl orld rld! ld!  d! j ! ju  jus just ust  st s t st  sto stop top  op ? p ?   ? l ? lo  lol lol! ol!  l! u ! u   u h u ha  hav have ave  ve m e mi  mis miss isse ssed sed  ed t d th  the the  he p e po  poi poin oint int! nt!  t! i ! i   i m i me  mea mean ean  an a n a   a p a pr  pre pres rese esen sent enta ntab tabl able ble  le w e wi  wif wife ife  fe f e fo  for for  or a r al  all all  ll o l oc  occ occa ccas casi asio sion ions ons  ns & s &   & s & so  som some omet meti etim time imes mes  es m s mu  mul mult ulti ltip tipu ipur purp urpo rpos pose ose  se s e se  sef sef  ef : f :   : # : #w  #wi #wif wife ifen feno enot notm otmu tmul mult ulti ltip tipu ipur purp urpo rpos pose oset seto etoo too  oo i o i   i d i do  don don' on't n't  't g t ge  get get  et w t wh  why why  hy t y th  the they hey  ey s y st  sti stil till ill  ll t l th  thi thin hink ink  nk t k th  tha that hat  at w t wa  way way  ay w y wa  wal wall alla llah lahi ahi! hi!  i! i ! if  if  if t f th  the they hey  ey r y re  res resp espe spec pect ect  ct t t th  the them hems emse msel selv elve lves ves, es,  s, a , a   a w a wo  wom woma oman man  an w n wi  wil will ill  ll s l su  sur sure ure  re r e re  res resp espe spec pect ect  ct t t th  the them hem  em n m no  no  no m o ma  mat matt atte tter ter  er w r wh  wha what hat! at!  t! l ! lm  lma lmao mao  ao i o i   i k i kn  kno know now  ow n w na  na  na : a :p  :p  :p : p :   : l : lo  loo looo oool ool. ol.  l. i . i   i w i wa  was was  as m s me  mes mess essi ssin sing ing  ng w g wi  wit with ith  th y h ya  ya  ya ; a ;)  ;)  ;) ‚ ) ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù ag  agr agre gree ree  ee t e to  to  to d o di  dis disa isag sagr agre gree ree  ee r e re  res resp espe spec pect ectf ctfu tful full ully lly! ly!  y! o ! on  onl only nly  ly m y me  men men  en w n wi  wit with ith  th n h na  nap napo apol pole oleo leon eon  on c n co  com comp ompl mple plex lex  ex t x th  tha that hat  at w t wa  wan want ant  nt t t th  the thei heir eir  ir e r eg  ego ego  go w o wo  wor wors orsh rshi ship hipe iped ped  ed w d wi  wil will ill  ll t l te  tel tell ell  ll y l yo  you you  ou a u a   a w a wo  wom woma oman man  an i n is  is  is " s "t  "to "too too  oo p o po  pol poli olis lish ishe shed hed" ed"  d" # " #b  #be #beg bego egon gone one  ne j e ju  jus just ust  st h t ha  had had  ad t d to  to  to r o ra  ran rant ant  nt t t th  tha that hat  at o t ou  out out  ut ? t ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? a ? al  all all  ll i l i   i w i wa  wan want ant  nt i t is  is  is t s th  the the  he t e ta  tas tast aste ste  te t e th  tha that hat  at y t yo  you your our  ur l r li  lip lips ips  ps a s al  all allo llow low  ow ? w ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? l ? lm  lma lmao mao  ao t o th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you  ou k u ko  ko  ko ? o ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: j : ju  jus just ust  st h t ha  had had  ad t d to  to  to r o ra  ran rant ant  nt t t th  tha that hat  at o t ou  out out  ut ? t ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù * ù *h  *ha *han hand ands nds  ds h s he  her her  er a r a   a g a gl  gla glas lass ass  ss o s of  of  of c f ch  chi chil hill ille lled led  ed w d wa  wat wate ater ter* er*‚ r*‚Ä *‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : e : ed  ed  ed ? d ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: a : al  all all  ll i l i   i w i wa  wan want ant  nt i t is  is  is t s th  the the  he t e ta  tas tast aste ste  te t e th  tha that hat  at y t yo  you your our  ur l r li  lip lips ips  ps a s al  all allo llow low  ow ? w ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù‚ Äù‚Ä ù‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lol lol  ol : l :   : a : a'  a'a a'a  'a b a ba  ban bans ansa nsan san  an w n wa  was wasa asa  sa ? a ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? " ? ":  ":  ": a : al  all all  ll i l i   i w i wa  wan want ant  nt i t is  is  is t s th  the the  he t e ta  tas tast aste ste  te t e th  tha that hat  at y t yo  you your our  ur l r li  lip lips ips  ps a s al  all allo llow low  ow ? w ??  ??? ???? ???" ??"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  the ther here ere' re's e's  's a s al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys a s a   a t a tw  twe twee weet eet  et o t or  or  or a r a   a s a so  son song ong  ng t g th  tha that hat  at g t go  goe goes oes  es w s wi  wit with ith  th h h ho  how how  ow a w am  am  am f m fe  fee feel eeli elin ling ing  ng e g ev  eve ever very ery  ry t y ti  tim time ime. me.  e. g . go  got got  ot y t yo  you you  ou s u st  stu stuc tuck uck  ck o k on  on  on m n my  my  my b y bo  bod body ody, dy,  y, o , on  on  on m n my  my  my b y bo  bod body ody, dy,  y, l , li  lik like ike  ke a e a   a t a ta  tat tatt atto ttoo too  oo ? o ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? t ? tr  try try  ry t y to  to  to t o te  tel tell ell  ll y l yo  you you  ou " u "n  "no "no" no"  o" b " bu  but but  ut m t my  my  my b y bo  bod body ody  dy k y ke  kee keep eeps eps  ps o s on  on  on t n te  tel tell elli llin ling ing  ng y g yo  you you  ou " u "y  "ye "yes yes" es"  s" ? " ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? t ? tr  try try  ry t y to  to  to t o te  tel tell ell  ll y l yo  you you  ou " u "s  "st "sto stop top" op", p",  ", b , bu  but but  ut y t yo  you your our  ur l r li  lip lips ipst psti stic tick ick  ck g k go  got got  ot m t me  me  me s e so  so  so o o ou  out out  ut o t of  of  of b f br  bre brea reat eath ath  th ? h ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : a : am  amm amma mma  ma m a ma  mak make ake  ke y e yo  you you  ou b u be  beg beg  eg t g ti  til till ill  ll y l yo  you you  ou s u sc  scr scre crea ream eam  am n m na  nag nago agod gode ode  de ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù am  ame amen men  en : n :   : d : de  dea dear ear  ar g r go  god god, od,  d, d , de  del deli eliv live iver ver  er # r #n  #ni #nig nige iger geri eria ria  ia f a fr  fro from rom  om p m ps  psy psyc sych ycho chop hopa opat path aths ths, hs,  s, e , eg  ego egot goti otis tist ists sts  ts a s an  and and  nd s d sc  sch schi chiz hizo izop zoph ophr phre hren reni enic nics ics  cs ‚ s ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  the the  he m e mo  mom mome omen ment ent  nt | t |   | k | ke  ken kenn enny nny  ny g y g   g ? g ??  ??  ?? t ? th  tha that hat  at s t so  som some omeb mebo ebod body ody  dy w y wa  was was  as y s yo  you you  ou ? u ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? c ? co  col colo olor lorl orle rles less ess  ss : s :   : w : wh  wha what hat  at c t co  col colo olor lor  or i r is  is  is l s lo  lov love ove? ve?‚ e?‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i a i am  am  am ? m ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : y : yo  you you  ou m u mu  mus must ust  st b t be  be  be a e a   a r a ro  rom roma oman mant anti ntic tic  ic ? c ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : p : po  pou pout out  ut n t na  na  na f a fi  fig figh ight ght? ht?? t??? ???? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lr  lrt lrt  rt w t wh  why why  hy a y ar  are are  re h e he  her her  er e r ey  eye eyes yes  es o s op  ope open pene ened ned  ed t d th  tho tho  ho ? o ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? sh  she she  he s e st  sta stay tays ays  ys s s sh  sha shar harp arp  rp : p :   : m : me  mei mei  ei q i qi  qir qiri iri  ri q i qi  qir qiri iri  ri k i ke  ken kena enan nan  an ? n ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": l : lr  lrt lrt  rt w t wh  why why  hy a y ar  are are  re h e he  her her  er e r ey  eye eyes yes  es o s op  ope open pene ened ned  ed t d th  tho tho  ho ? o ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù si  sil sile ilen lenc ence nce  ce t e tr  tra tran rans ansl nsla slat late ated ted. ed.. d... ...  .. h . ha  has has  as t s to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a s a sq  squ squa quar uare are  re r e ro  roo root oot  ot o t of  of  of n f ne  neg nega egat gati ativ tive ive  ve z e ze  zer zero ero  ro ? o ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? i ? if  if  if w f we  we  we o e on  onl only nly  ly h y he  hea hear ear  ar t r th  the the  he t e th  thi thin hing ings ngs  gs w s we  we  we w e wa  wan want ant  nt t t to  to  to h o he  hea hear ear, ar,  r, w , we  we  we w e wi  wil will ill  ll n l ne  nev neve ever ver  er k r kn  kno know now  ow t w th  the the  he t e tr  tru trut ruth uth. th.  h. t . ta  tab tab! ab!  b! l ! la  lal lala alai lai  ai ? i ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  has has  as t s to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a s a sq  squ squa quar uare are  re r e ro  roo root oot  ot o t of  of  of n f ne  neg nega egat gati ativ tive ive  ve z e ze  zer zero ero  ro ? o ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù n ù ne  ner nerd erd  rd ? d ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù d ù de  des desi esir sire ires res  es a s an  and and  nd s d se  sec secr ecre cret rets ets, ts,  s, a , ar  are aren ren' en't n't  't e t ea  eas easi asil sily ily  ly s y sh  sha shar hare ared red. ed.  d. i . it  it' it's t's  's a s a   a s a sp  spe spec peci ecia cial ial  al f l fe  fee feel eeli elin ling ing  ng w g wh  whe when hen  en y n yo  you you  ou f u fi  fin find ind  nd s d so  som some omeo meon eone one  ne w e wh  who who  ho d o de  des dese eser serv erve rves ves  es t s th  the them hem. em.  m. t . th  the the  he s e se  sec secr ecre cret ret  et i t in  in  in y n yo  you your our  ur s r sm  smi smil mile ile, le,  e, l , lo  lou loud oud, ud,  d, y , ye  yet yet  et s t so  so  so s o si  sil sile ilen lent ent. nt.. t... ...  .. v . ve  ver very ery  ry w y wr  wro wron rong ong  ng o g o   o ? o ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???, ??,  ?, w , wr  wro wron rong ong  ng a g as  ass assu ssum sump umpt mpti ptio tion ion‚ on‚Ä n‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  the the  he s e sl  sli slig ligh ight ghte htes test est  st o t of  of  of w f wh  whi whis hisp ispe sper pers ers  rs c s ca  can can  an f n fl  flo flou lour ouri uris rish ish  sh n h ne  neg nega egat gati ativ tivi ivit vity ity, ty,  y, b , be  be  be m e mi  min mind indf ndfu dful ful  ul o l of  of  of w f wh  wha what hat  at y t yo  you you  ou l u li  lis list iste sten ten  en t n to  to. to.  o. b . bu  but but  ut e t eh  ehn ehn  hn ? n ??  ??? ???? ???. ??.. ?... ...  .. : . :   : e : ei  eit eith ithe ther her  er a r a   a n a ne  ner nerd erd  rd o d or  or  or a r an  an  an i n in  int inte ntel tell elle llec lect ectu ctua tual ual, al,  l, u , u   u g u go  got gott otta tta  ta c a ch  cho choo hoos oose ose  se o e on  one one  ne ? e ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù so  som some omet meti etim time imes mes  es i s i   i g i gi  giv give ive  ve m e my  mys myse ysel self elf  lf t f th  the the  he s e si  sil sile ilen lent ent  nt t t tr  tre trea reat eatm atme tmen ment ent  nt j t ju  jus just ust  st b t be  bec beca ecau caus ause use  se w e we  we  we c e ca  can can  an b n be  be  be o e ou  our our  ur o r ow  own own  wn e n en  ene enem nemy emy  my s y so  som some omet meti etim time imes mes. es.  s. t . th  the the  he n e ni  nig nigh ight ght  ht i t is  is  is n s no  not not  ot c t cl  cle clea lear ear, ar,  r, t , th  the the  he s e st  sta star tars ars  rs s s se  see seem eem  em s m so  so  so f o fa  far far  ar a r aw  awa away way. ay.  y. a . ab  abi abi  bi : i :   : # : #d  #de #dee deep eep  ep " p ":  ":  ": t : th  the the  he s e se  sec secr ecre cret ret  et i t in  in  in y n yo  you your our  ur s r sm  smi smil mile ile, le,  e, l , lo  lou loud oud, ud,  d, y , ye  yet yet  et s t so  so  so s o si  sil sile ilen lent ent. nt.. t... ..." .."‚ ."‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : # : #g  #gb #gba gbam bam  am " m ":  ":  ": i : if  if  if w f we  we  we o e on  onl only nly  ly h y he  hea hear ear  ar t r th  the the  he t e th  thi thin hing ings ngs  gs w s we  we  we w e wa  wan want ant  nt t t to  to  to h o he  hea hear ear, ar,  r, w , we  we  we w e wi  wil will ill  ll n l ne  nev neve ever ver  er k r kn  kno know now  ow t w th  the the  he t e tr  tru trut ruth uth. th." h."‚ ."‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù o ù on  on  on c n cl  cle clea lear ear  ar n r ni  nig nigh ight ghts hts, ts,  s, t , th  the they hey  ey s y se  see seem eem  em s m so  so  so c o cl  clo clos lose ose  se t e to  to  to u o us  us. us.. s..  .. w . we  we  we s e sh  sho shou houl ould uld  ld d d de  def defi efin fine ine  ne o e ou  our our  ur f r fl  fla flaw laws aws  ws i s in  ins inst nste stea tead ead  ad o d of  of  of h f hi  hid hidi idin ding ing  ng t g th  the them hem, em,  m, i , it  it  it i t is  is  is m s mo  mor more ore  re l e li  lib libe iber bera erat rati atin ting ing. ng.  g. n . no  not not  ot a t a   a p a pr  pri prin rinc ince nces cess ess  ss o s or  or  or a r al  all all  ll t l th  tha that hat  at b t bu  but but  ut w t wo  wor wort orth rthy thy  hy o y of  of  of a f a   a k a ki  kin king ings ngs  gs l s lo  lov love ove  ve ? e ??  ??  ?? z ? ze  zer zero ero  ro e o ex  exp expe xpec pect ecta ctat tati atio tion ions ons  ns h s he  hel help elp! lp!  p! : ! :   : i : ir  iro iron roni onic nic  ic h c ho  how how  ow i w i   i k i ke  kee keep eep  ep t p ta  tal talk alki lkin king ing  ng a g ab  abo abou bout out  ut p t pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le l e le  let lett etti ttin ting ing  ng m g me  me  me d e do  dow down own, wn,  n, a , an  and and  nd i d i   i k i ke  kee keep eep  ep l p le  let lett etti ttin ting ing  ng t g th  the them hem  em l m le  let let  et m t me  me  me d e do  dow down own. wn.  n. t . th  tha that hat' at's t's  's h s ho  how how  ow " w "i  "i  "i l i li  liv live ive" ve"  e" : " :   : t : th  tha that hat' at's t's  's h s ho  how how  ow i w i   i a i al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys c s co  con cons onso nsol sole ole  le m e my  mys myse ysel self elf‚ lf‚Ä f‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù w ù we  we  we a e ar  are are  re o e on  onl only nly  ly h y hu  hum huma uman man, an,  n, w , we  we  we c e ca  can can' an't n't  't h t he  hel help elp  lp i p it  it  it s t so  som some omet meti etim time imes mes  es ? s ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : m : me  me  me t e to  too too! oo!  o! d ! du  dun dunn unno nno  no w o wh  why why  hy i y i   i l i le  let let  et i t it  it  it b t bo  bot both othe ther her  er m r me  me  me ? e ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lol lol, ol,  l, n , no  not not  ot l t li  lit lite iter tera eral rall ally lly  ly : y :   : * : *c  *ch *cha chan hang ange nges ges  es n s na  nam name ame  me t e to  to  to s o sa  san sanu anus nusi usi  si j i jn  jnr jnr, nr,y r,yo ,you you  ou c u ca  cal call alle lled led? ed?  d? r ? rt  rt  rt n t no  not not  ot a t a   a p a pr  pri prin rinc ince nces cess ess  ss o s or  or  or a r al  all all  ll t l th  tha that hat  at b t bu  but but  ut w t wo  wor wort orth rthy thy  hy o y of  of  of a f a   a k a ki  kin king ings ngs  gs l s lo  lov love ove  ve ? e ??  ??‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù am  ame amen men! en!  n! t ! th  tha than hank anks nks  ks : s :   : r : rt  rt  rt i t i   i w i wi  wis wish ish  sh y h yo  you you  ou t u th  tha that hat  at : t :   : n : no  not not  ot a t a   a p a pr  pri prin rinc ince nces cess ess  ss o s or  or  or a r al  all all  ll t l th  tha that hat  at b t bu  but but  ut w t wo  wor wort orth rthy thy  hy o y of  of  of a f a   a k a ki  kin king ings ngs  gs l s lo  lov love ove  ve ? e ??  ??‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù a   a m a ma  man man  an d n do  doe does oesn esn' sn't n't  't n t ne  nee need eed  ed a d a   a t a th  thr thro hron rone one  ne t e to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a k a ki  kin king ing, ng,  g, e , ev  eve ever very ery  ry g y go  goo good ood  od m d ma  man man  an i n is  is  is a s a   a k a ki  kin king ing! ng!  g! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? t ? ti  tim time ime  me i e in  inv inve nves vest este sted ted  ed i d in  in  in t n th  the the  he r e ri  rig righ ight ght  ht p t pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le i e is  is  is f s fa  far far  ar m r mo  mor more ore  re p e pr  pro prof rofi ofit fita itab tabl able ble  le t e th  tha than han  an m n ma  mat mate ater teri eria rial ial  al i l in  inv inve nves vest estm stme tmen ment ent. nt.  t. y . ye  yes yes  es f s fa  fa! fa!  a! : ! :   : a : ab  abi abi? bi?  i? : ? :   : a : a   a m a ma  man man  an d n do  doe does oesn esn' sn't n't  't n t ne  nee need eed  ed a d a   a t a th  thr thro hron rone one  ne t e to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a k a ki  kin king ing, ng,  g, e , ev  eve ever very ery  ry g y go  goo good ood  od m d ma  man man  an i n is  is  is a s a   a k a ki  kin king ing! ng!  g! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù‚ Äù‚Ä ù‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: t : ti  tim time ime  me i e in  inv inve nves vest este sted ted  ed i d in  in  in t n th  the the  he r e ri  rig righ ight ght  ht p t pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le i e is  is  is f s fa  far far  ar m r mo  mor more ore  re p e pr  pro prof rofi ofit fita itab tabl able ble  le t e th  tha than han  an m n ma  mat mate ater teri eria rial ial  al i l in  inv inve nves vest estm stme tmen ment ent. nt.‚ t.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i l i le  lea lear earn arn  rn t n th  thi this his  is e s ev  eve ever very eryd ryda yday day  ay n y ne  nev neve ever ver  er s r st  sto stop top  op g p gi  giv givi ivin ving ing  ng y g yo  you your our  ur b r br  bri brig righ ight ght  ht s t sm  smi smil mile ile. le.  e. e . ev  eve even ven  en i n if  if  if y f ya  ya  ya t a te  tee teet eeth eth  th i h is  is  is b s br  bro brow rown own  wn ? n ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? p ? pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le w e wh  who who  ho s o st  sti stic tick ick  ck w k wi  wit with ith  th y h yo  you you  ou r u re  reg rega egar gard ardl rdle dles less ess  ss o s of  of  of h f ho  how how  ow d w di  dif diff iffi ffic ficu icul cult ult  lt y t yo  you you  ou a u ar  are are  re w e wo  wor wort orth rth  th k h ke  kee keep eepi epin ping ing. ng.  g. n . no  not not  ot a t at  at  at a t al  all all  ll : l :   : s : sh  sha sha  ha n a no  not not  ot a t a   a r a re  rea reas easo ason son  on t n to  to  to b o be  be  be d e di  dif diff iffi ffic ficu icul cult ult  lt ‚ t ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú  Äú p ú pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le w e wh  who who  ho s o st  sti stic tick ick  ck w k wi  wit with ith  th y h yo  you you  ou r u re  reg rega egar gard ardl rdle dles less ess  ss o s of  of  of h f ho  how how  ow d w di  dif diff iffi ffic ficu icul cult ult  lt y t yo  you you  ou a u ar  are are  re w e wo  wor wort orth rth  th s h so  som some omet meti etim time imes mes  es e s ex  exp expl xpla plan lana anat nati atio tion ions ons  ns a s ar  are are  re w e wo  wor wort orth rthl thle hles less ess, ss,  s, w , we  we  we h e he  hea hear ear  ar w r wh  wha what hat  at w t we  we  we w e wa  wan want ant  nt t t to  to  to h o he  hea hear ear. ar.  r. p . pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le w e wh  who who  ho m o ma  mak make ake  ke u e us  us  us s s sm  smi smil mile ile  le w e wi  wit with itho thou hout out  ut s t sa  say sayi ayin ying ing  ng a g a   a w a wo  wor word ord. rd.  d. i . i   i m i ma  man mana anag nage age  ge t e to  to  to s o st  sta stay tay  ay g y ge  gen gene ener nera eral rall ally lly  ly h y ha  hap happ appy ppy  py e y ev  eve even ven  en w n wh  whe when hen  en l n li  lif life ife  fe g e ge  get gets ets  ts s s sh  shi shit hitt itty tty. ty.. y... ...  .. i . it  it' it's t's  's k s ki  kin kind inda nda  da a a aw  awe awes weso esom some ome  me a e at  at  at t t th  the the  he m e mo  mom mome omen ment ent. nt.. t... ...  .. u . ur  urb urba rban ban  an w n wa  wat wate ater ter  er f r fr  fro fron ront onts nts  ts a s as  as  as t s ti  tic tick icki ckin king ing  ng t g ti  tim time ime  me b e bo  bom bomb ombs mbs  bs l s li  lis list iste sten teni enin ning ing  ng t g to  to  to m o mu  mus musi usic sic  ic w c wi  wit with ith  th l h ly  lyr lyri yric rics ics  cs w s we  we  we a e ar  are are  re a e af  afr afra frai raid aid  id t d to  to  to s o sa  say say. ay.. y... ...  .. m . mi  min mind ind  nd f d fu  ful full ull  ll o l of  of  of w f wo  won wond onde nder der. er.. r..  .. t . th  the the  he e e el  ela elas last asti stic tici icit city ity  ty o y of  of  of m f my  my  my s y so  sou soul oul. ul.. l..  .. l . lo  lol lol! ol!  l! : ! :   : s : su  suc such uch  ch p h pr  pro prof rofo ofou foun ound und  nd w d wi  wis wisd isdo sdom dom  om " m ":  ":  ": o : on  onc once nce  ce a e a   a h a ha  hau haus ausa usa  sa a a al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys a s an  an  an i n il  ill illi llit lite iter tera erat rate ate" te"‚ e"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lol lol  ol : l :   : " : ":  ":  ": t : th  the the  he e e el  ela elas last asti stic tici icit city ity  ty o y of  of  of m f my  my  my s y so  sou soul oul. ul.. l.." .."  ." h " hm  hmm hmmm mmmm mmm‚ mm‚Ä m‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù b ù ba  bar bari ari  ri k i ka  kaw kawa awai wai  ai ? i ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: " : "m  "my "my  my p y pe  pep pepp eppo ppo  po m o my  my  my p y pe  pep pepp eppo ppo" po"  o" ? " ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? i ? in  in  in h n hi  his his  is z s zo  zon zone one  ne t e to  tod toda oday day‚ ay‚Ä y‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù so  so  so g o gm  gmb gmb' mb's b's  's g s gr  gre grea reat eat  at g t gr  gra gran rand and  nd m d mo  mot moth othe ther her  er w r wa  was was  as f s fr  fro from rom  om i m im  imo imo  mo s o st  sta stat tate ate  te ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? sa  san sann annu nnu  nu r u ro  roc roch ocha chas has  as ? s ?   ? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : r : ro  rot rotl otlm tlma lmao mao  ao " o ":  ":  ": s : so  so  so g o gm  gmb gmb' mb's b's  's g s gr  gre grea reat eat  at g t gr  gra gran rand and  nd m d mo  mot moth othe ther her  er w r wa  was was  as f s fr  fro from rom  om i m im  imo imo  mo s o st  sta stat tate ate  te ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? sa  san sann annu nnu  nu r u ro  roc roch ocha chas has  as ? s ?"  ?"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù k ù ka  kaw kawa awai wai  ai b i ba  ba  ba ? a ??  ??? ???? ???l ??lm ?lma lmao mao  ao : o :   : l : lo  lol lol! ol!  l! m ! mu  muh muha uham hamm amma mmad madu adu  du o u ok  oke okec kech echu chuk hukw ukwu kwu  wu b u bu  buh buha uhar hari ari  ri . i .   . " . "   " s " so  so  so g o gm  gmb gmb' mb's b's  's g s gr  gre grea reat eat  at g t gr  gra gran rand and  nd m d mo  mot moth othe ther her  er w r wa  was was  as f s fr  fro from rom  om i m im  imo imo  mo s o st  sta stat tate ate  te ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? sa  san sann annu nnu  nu r u ro  roc roch ocha chas has  as ? s ?"  ?"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lm  lma lmao mao  ao : o :   : l : lo  lol lol! ol!  l! m ! mu  muh muha uham hamm amma mmad madu adu  du o u ok  oke okec kech echu chuk hukw ukwu kwu  wu b u bu  buh buha uhar hari ari  ri . i .   . " . ":  ":  ": s : so  so  so g o gm  gmb gmb' mb's b's  's g s gr  gre grea reat eat  at g t gr  gra gran rand and  nd m d mo  mot moth othe ther her  er w r wa  was was  as f s fr  fro from rom  om i m im  imo imo  mo s o st  sta stat tate ate  te ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? sa  san sann annu nnu  nu r u ro  roc roch ocha chas has  as ? s ?"  ?"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù c ù ca  cal calc alcu lcul cula ulat lati atin ting ing  ng t g th  the the  he t e tr  tru true rue  ue c e co  cos cost ost  st o t of  of  of e f en  ene ener nerg ergy rgy  gy s y st  sto stor tora orag rage age  ge b e by  by  by t y ti  tim tim  im h m he  hen henn enne nnes ness esse ssey sey. ey.  y. s . su  sus sust usta stai tain aina inab nabl able ble  le c e ci  cit citi itie ties ies: es:  s: i : in  inf infr nfra fras rast astr stru truc ruct uctu ctur ture ure  re c e co  cos cost osts sts  ts + s +   + u + ur  urb urba rban ban  an g n gr  gro grow rowt owth wth  th m h ma  man mana anag nage agem geme emen ment ent  nt l t lo  lol lol! ol!  l! w ! we  we  we a e al  all all  ll s l se  see see  ee e e el  ele eleg lega egan ganc ance nce  ce d e di  dif diff iffe ffer fere eren rent entl ntly tly  ly i y i   i g i gu  gue gues uess ess. ss.. s... ...  .. l . lu  lup lupi upit pita ita  ta l a lo  loo look ooks oks  ks f s fu  fun funn unny nny! ny!  y! c ! co  cos cos  os u s u   u f u fo  for fore orev reve ever ver  er m r my  my  my l y la  lad lady ady, dy,  y, f , fo  for fore orev reve ever ver  er m r my  my  my b y ba  bab baby aby  by ? y ??  ??? ???? ??? ?? ? 