on  n m  my my  y v  ve ver ery ry  y l  la las ast st  t n  ne ner erv rve ve! e!  ! i  i  i a  am am  m n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g a  an and nd  d i  i  i h  ha hav ave ve  e n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g b  bu but ut  t a  al all lla lah ah! h!  ! .  .. ... ..f .fr fro rom om  m t  th the he  e c  co cor orn rne ner er  r o  of of  f m  my my  y d  dr dre rea eam ams ms! s!  ! m  ma mas ash sha ha  a a  al all lla lah ah! h!  ! :  :  : t  th the hen en, n,  , y  yo you ou  u h  ha hav ave ve  e e  ev eve ver ery ryt yth thi hin ing ng  g .  .  . "  ": ":  : i  i  i a  am am  m n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g a  an and nd  d i  i  i h  ha hav ave ve  e n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g b  bu but ut  t a  al all lla lah ah! h!  ! s  st sta tay ay  y r  re rel ela lax axe xed ed, d,  , b  be be  e a  at at  t p  pe pea eac ace ce, e,  , w  wi wit ith tho hou out ut  t a  an anx nxi xie iet eti tie ies es, s,  , b  be be  e i  in in  n c  co con onv nve ver ers rsa sat ati tio ion ons ns  s t  th tha hat at  t m  ma mak ake kes es  s s  se sen ens nse se. e.  . h  ha hap app ppy py. y.. ... ..  . w  we we  e a  as ask sk  k f  fo for or  r n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g b  bu but ut  t w  wi wil ill ll  l g  gi giv ive ve  e e  ev eve ver ery ryt yth thi hin ing ng  g i  if if  f w  we we  e h  ha hav ave ve  e t  to to. o.  . b  be be  e k  ki kin ind nd, d,  , n  no no  o m  ma mat att tte ter er  r w  wh wha hat at. t.. ... ..  . i  it it' t's 's  s a  a  a p  pr pri ric ice cel ele les ess ss  s l  le leg ega gac acy cy  y t  to to  o l  le lea eav ave ve  e b  be beh ehi hin ind nd. d.  . w  wh whe hen en  n t  th the he  e w  wa wav ave ves es  s o  of of  f t  tr tro rou oub ubl ble le  e l  lo loo ook oks ks  s b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l i  in in  n t  th the he  e s  sk sky ky. y.. ... ..  . n  no not ot  t a  a  a w  wi wit itc tch ch. h.. ... ..  . m  me mer ere rel ely ly  y b  be bew ewi wit itc tch chi hin ing ng. g.. ... ..  . l  lo lol ol! l!  ! :  :  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : w  wh whe hen en  n t  th the he  e w  wa wav ave ves es  s o  of of  f t  tr tro rou oub ubl ble le  e l  lo loo ook oks ks  s b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l i  in in  n t  th the he  e s  sk sky ky. y.. ... ..‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  to toh oh  h f  fa fa, a,k ,ka kaj aji ji  i z  za zau aur ura ran anc nce ce  e d  da da  a t  tu tur ura ran anc nci ci. i.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù "  "d "di dis isc sco com omb mbo bob obu bul ula lat ate ted ed" d"  " ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th the he  e w  wo wor ord rd  d i  it its tse sel elf lf  f g  go got ot  t m  me me  e d  di dis isc sco com omb mbo bob obu bul ula lat ate ted ed  d ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? l  lm lma mao ao  o i  i  i k  kn kno now ow  w r  ri rig igh ght ht  t ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : t  tu tur ura ran anc nci ci  i ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? "  ": ":  : "  "d "di dis isc sco com omb mbo bob obu bul ula lat ate ted ed" d"  " ?  ?? ??? ??? ??" ?"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lo lol ol! l!  ! a  ab abo bou out ut? t?  ? :  :  : s  sa sam ame me  e h  he her ere re  e :  :  : "  "d "di dis isc sco com omb mbo bob obu bul ula lat ate ted ed" d"  " ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù h  ha hah aha hah aha ha  a :  :  : b  be bei ein ing ng  g d  di dis isc sco com omb mbo bob obu bul ula lat ate ted ed  d :  :  : l  lo lol ol! l!  ! a  ab abo bou out ut? t?  ? :  :  : s  sa sam ame me  e h  he her ere re  e :  :  : "  "d "di dis isc sco com omb mbo bob obu bul ula lat ate ted ed" d"  " ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù b  bu but ut  t i  i  i s  sa sai aid id  d m  me me  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : l  le let et' t's 's  s s  sw swi wit itc tch ch? h?? ??? ??? ??  ? "  ": ":  : w  wo wou oul uld ld  d l  lo lov ove ve  e t  to to  o b  be be  e a  a  a m  ma mal ale le  e v  ve ver ers rsi sio ion on  n o  of of  f m  me me  e f  fo for or  r a  a  a w  we wee eek eks ks  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??" ?"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lo lol ol  l :  :  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : w  wo wou oul uld ld  d l  lo lov ove ve  e t  to to  o b  be be  e a  a  a m  ma mal ale le  e v  ve ver ers rsi sio ion on  n o  of of  f m  me me  e f  fo for or  r a  a  a w  we wee eek eks ks  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äùa ùas as  s i  in inf nfi fir ird rda dau aus usi siy iyi yi? i?‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù :  :  : w  wo wou oul uld ld  d l  lo lov ove ve  e t  to to  o b  be be  e a  a  a m  ma mal ale le  e v  ve ver ers rsi sio ion on  n o  of of  f m  me me  e f  fo for or  r a  a  a w  we wee eek ek  k ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? i  i  i k  kn kno now ow  w r  ri rig igh ght ht  t ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : "  "s "sm smh mh! h!  ! i  im ima mag agi gin ina nat ati tio ion ons ns  s :  :  : :  :  : w  wo wou oul uld ld  d l  lo lov ove ve  e t  to to  o b  be be  e a  a  a m  ma mal ale le  e v  ve ver ers rsi sio ion on  n o  of of  f m  me me  e f  fo for or  r a  a  a w  we wee eek ek  k ?  ?? ??? ??? ??" ?"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??: ?:  : a  ab abu buj uja ja  a b  bo boy oys ys. s.  . a  ak aka ka  a w  wh whi hit ite te  e t  tr tra rad ad  d g  ga gan ang ng. g.  . m  me mer erc rce ced ede des es  s d  dr dri riv ivi vin ing ng. g.  . g  gu guc ucc cci ci  i s  sl sli lip ipp ppe per ers rs  s w  we wea ear ari rin ing ng. g.  . o  ou oud ud  d s  sm sme mel ell lli lin ing ng. g.  . n  no no  o m  mo mon one ney ey  y f  fo for or  r p  po poc ock cke ket et. t.  . p  pa pac ack cka kag agi gin ing ng. g.  . 1  15 15m 5mi min ins ns  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : h  ho how ow  w l  lo lon ong ng  g a  af aft fte ter er  r a  ar arr rri riv ivi vin ing ng  g a  at at  t s  so som ome meo eon one ne‚ e‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s h  ho hou ous use se  e i  is is  s i  it it  t a  ap app ppr pro rop opr pri ria iat ate te  e t  to to  o a  as ask sk  k f  fo for or  r t  th the he  e w  wi wif ifi fi  i p  pa pas ass ssw swo wor ord rd? d?  ? ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lm lma mao ao  o m  m√ m√© √©r ©rc rci ci  i :  :  : s  st sta tar art rte ter er  r p  pa pac ack ck, k,  , c  co com ome me  e t  ta tak ake ke  e m  my my  y w  we wea ear ars rs! s!  ! "  ": ":  : w  wo wou oul uld ld  d l  lo lov ove ve  e t  to to  o b  be be  e a  a  a m  ma mal ale le  e v  ve ver ers rsi sio ion on  n o  of of  f m  me me  e f  fo for or  r a  a  a w  we wee eek eks ks  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??" ?"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù s  sa sad adl dly ly  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : w  we we  e a  al all ll  l a  ar are re. e.  . "  ": ":  : a  ad add ddi dic ict cte ted ed  d t  to to  o m  my my  y p  ph pho hon one ne" e"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  it it  t i  is is  s :  :  : i  it its ts  s r  re rea eal all lly ly  y a  an ann nno noy oyi yin ing ng  g "  ": ":  : s  sa sad adl dly ly  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : w  we we  e a  al all ll  l a  ar are re. e.  . "  ": ":  : a  ad add ddi dic ict cte ted ed  d t  to to  o m  my my  y p  ph pho hon one ne" e"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù" ù"‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù b  bu but ut  t i  i  i d  di did id  d n  no not ot  t s  se see ee  e t  th thi his is  s s  sc sce cen ene ne  e n  na na  a ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : d  di div ive ver erg rge gen ent nt. t.  . i  it it  t i  is is  s f  fo for or  r m  me me, e,  , i  i  i w  wi wis ish sh  h i  i  i w  wa was asn sn' n't 't. t.  . a  an and nd  d y  ye yes es, s,  , i  i  i p  pr pra ray ay  y t  th tha hat at  t n  ne nev eve ver er  r h  ha hap app ppe pen ens ns  s t  to too oo  o ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? l  lm lma mao ao  o :  :  : 3  3m 3mi min ins ns  s :  :) :)  ) "  "  " 1  15 15m 5mi min ins ns  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? "  ": ":  : h  ho how ow  w l  lo lon ong ng  g a  af aft fte ter er  r a  ar arr rri riv ivi vin ing ng  g a  at at  t s  so som ome meo eon one ne‚ e‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s h  ho hou ous use se  e i  is is  s i  it it  t a  ap app ppr pro rop opr pri ria iat ate te  e t  to to  o a  as ask sk  k f  fo for or  r t  th the he  e w  wi wif ifi fi  i y  yo you ou  u m  ma may ay  y h  ha hav ave ve  e w  wr wro ron ong ngl gly ly  y j  ju jud udg dge ged ed  d s  so som ome meo eon one ne  e b  ba bas ase sed ed  d o  ot oth the her ers rs  s e  en enc nco cou oun unt nte ter er  r w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the hem em  m b  bu but ut  t w  wh whe hen en  n y  yo you ou  u e  en enc nco cou oun unt nte ter er  r t  th the hem em, m,  , t  th the hey ey  y a  ar are re  e b  be bet ett tte ter er  r t  th tha han an  n y  yo you our ur  r e  ex exp xpe pec ect cta tat ati tio ion ons ns. s.  . a  ab abi bi  i o  o  o ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : t  th the he  e l  lo lon ong nge ger er  r t  th the he  e w  wa wai ait it, t,  , t  th the he  e m  mo mor ore re  e a  aw awk wkw kwa war ard rd  d i  it it  t b  be bec eco com ome mes es. s.  . h  ha hah aha ha  a j  ju jus ust st  t a  as ask sk‚ k‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù d  do do  o t  th the hey ey  y k  kn kno now ow  w t  th tha hat at  t "  "o "on one ne  e i  is is  s t  to too oo  o g  go goo ood od" d"? "?  ? :  :i :if if  f s  sh she he‚ e‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s t  to too oo  o g  go goo ood od  d f  fo for or  r y  yo you ou, u,  , m  my my  y g  go god od, d,  , d  do don on‚ n‚Ä ‚Äô Äôt ôt  t l  le lea eav ave ve  e h  he her er. r.m .ma mak ake ke  e a  an an  n e  ef eff ffo for ort rt  t t  to to  o b  be be  e g  go goo ood od  d e  en eno nou oug ugh gh  h i  in ins nst ste tea ead ad  d h  ho how ow  w c  ca can an  n p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e h  ha hat ate te  e t  th the hem ems mse sel elv lve ves es  s s  so so  o m  mu muc uch ch  h t  to to  o c  ca cal all ll  l t  th the hei eir ir  r o  ow own wn  n p  pe per ers rso son on  n u  ug ugl gly ly? y?  ? i  i  i h  ha hat ate te  e t  th the he  e w  wo wor ord rd  d u  ug ugl gly ly  y o  on on  n a  an any ny  y o  of of  f g  go god ods ds  s c  cr cre rea eat ati tio ion on. n.  . g  go god od' d's 's  s w  wo wor ork rk  k i  is is  s p  pe per erf rfe fec ect cti tio ion on  n p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e c  ca can an  n o  on onl nly ly  y h  ha hav ave ve  e "  "u "ug ugl gly ly  y p  pe per ers rso son ona nal ali lit iti tie ies es" s"  " m  mo mos ost stl tly ly  y c  cr cre rea eat ate ted ed  d b  by by  y t  th the hem ems mse sel elv lve ves es  s a  an and nd  d i  in in  n t  th the hei eir ir  r h  he hea ead ad! d!  ! w  we we  e a  ar are re  e a  al all ll  l v  ve ver ery ry  y p  pe per erf rfe fec ect ct! t!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : p  pr pre rea eac ach ch  h m  my my  y s  si sis ist ste ter er  r ,  ,  , p  pr pre rea eac ach ch. h.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i  i d  do don on' n't 't  t e  ev eve ven en  n l  li lik ike ke  e s  sc sch cho hoo ool ol  l b  bu but ut  t i  i  i l  lo lov ove ve  e t  th the he  e i  id ide dea ea  a o  of of  f e  ex exa xam ams ms, s,  , i  it it' t's 's  s t  th the he  e o  on onl nly ly  y t  ti tim ime me  e i  i  i w  wa wan ant nt  t t  to to  o k  kn kno now ow  w e  ev eve ver ery ryt yth thi hin ing ng  g i  in in  n a  a  a f  fe few ew  w m  mi min inu nut ute tes es  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  in in  n b  bo boa oar ard rdi din ing ng  g h  ho hou ous use ses es  s w  we we  e w  wi wil ill ll  l s  sa say ay  y b  bu bus ush sh  h b  ba bab abi bie ies es  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : s  st stu tup upi pid id  d c  ca cat ats ts  s w  wo won on' n't 't  t s  st sto top op  p w  wa wai ail ili lin ing ng  g o  or or  r w  wh wha hat ate tev eve ver er  r i  it it  t i  is is  s t  th the hey ey  y d  do do. o.  . k  km kmt mt‚ t‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i  i c  ca can an  n i  im ima mag agi gin ine ne! e!  ! w  we we  e a  at att ttr tri rib ibu but ute ted ed  d e  ev eve ver ery ry  y s  st str tra ran ang nge ge  e s  so sou oun und nds ds  s t  to to  o w  wi wit itc tch che hes es  s &  &  & b  bu bus ush sh  h b  ba bab abi bie ies es  s =  =) =)) ))  ) :  :' :'( '(  ( e  ev evu vu  u p  pi pip ipo po  o ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : c  ch chi hin ina na  a i  in inv nve ven ent nte ted ed  d e  ex exa xam ams ms. s.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù k  ka kai ai, i,  , s  so sor orr rry ry  y o  o! o!  ! s  sh she he  e s  sh shl hld ld  d h  ha hav ave ve  e a  al all llo low owe wed ed  d u  u  u f  fo for or  r a  a  a y  yr yr  r =  =) =)) ))  ) :  :  : i  i  i w  wa wan ant nte ted ed  d t  th tha hat at  t e  ex exp xpe per eri rie ien enc nce ce  e b  bu but ut  t m  my my  y m  mu mum um  m w  wa was asn sn' n't 't  t a  a  a f  fa fan an  n o  of of  f b  bo boa oar ard rdi din ing ng  g s  sc sch cho hoo ool ols ls  s !  !! !!! !!  ! :  :  : i  if ifu fun una nan any nya ya, a,  , m  mo mor ore re  e t  th tha han an  n a  a  a f  fr fri rie ien end nd  d i  is is  s n  ne nex ext xt. t.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù y  yo you ou  u m  ma mak ake ke  e i  it it  t l  lo loo ook ok  k i  it it' t's 's  s m  ma mag agi gic ic  c ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : e  ea ear arn rne ned ed  d i  it it  t -  -  - t  th the he  e w  we wee eek ekn knd nd‚ d‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  it it' t's 's  s a  a  a s  so son ong ng  g y  yo you ou  u f  fa fal all ll  l i  in in  n l  lo lov ove ve  e w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the he  e f  fi fir irs rst st  t t  ti tim ime me  e y  yo you ou  u l  li lis ist ste ten en  n t  to to  o i  it it  t :  :  : c  ca cau aus use se  e i  i  i s  se see ee  e n  no nob obo bod ody dy, y,  , n  no nob obo bod ody dy  y b  bu but ut  t y  yo you ou, u,  , y  yo you ou, u,  , y  yo you ou. u.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i  i k  kn kno now ow  w ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : s  so so  o i  in in  n l  lo lov ove ve  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i  i t  th tho hou oug ugh ght ht  t t  th the he  e b  bi bib ibl ble le  e a  al als lso so  o p  pr pro roh ohi hib ibi bit its ts  s i  it it? t?  ? :  :  : w  we wel ell ll  l h  he he  e i  is is  s a  a  a g  go goo ood od  d m  mu mus usl sli lim im  m a  an and nd  d i  ia iam am  m s  su sur ure re  e h  he he  e w  wo wou oul uld ldn dn' n't 't  t w  wa wan ant nt  t m  me me  e t  to to  o d  dr dri rin ink nk  k a  al alc lco coh oho hol ol  l :  :( :(  ( .  .. ..  . o  on one ne  e r  re rea eas as  s s  so som ome met eth thi hin ing ng  g a  ab abo bou out ut  t t  th thi his is  s f  fa fac ace ce  e m  ma mak ake kes es  s m  me me  e v  ve ver ery ry  y h  ha hap app ppy py  y ?  ?? ??  ? l  lo lol ol  l :  :  : a  ad add dd  d m  me me  e o  on on  n b  bb bbm bm  m p  pi pin in  n 7  7f 7ff ff0 f0f 0f2 f2c 2cb cb. b.  . o  on on  n w  wh wha hat ats tsa sap app pp  p 0  08 081 816 165 652 528 289 897 977 773 73‚ 3‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lo lov ove ve  e i  is is  s a  a  a c  co con ont nti tin inu nuo uou ous us  s p  pr pro roc oce ces ess ss. s.  . ?  ?? ??  ? :  :  : #  #t #tr tru rue ue  e "  ": ":  : l  lo lov ove ve  e i  is is  s a  a  a c  co con ont nti tin inu nuo uou ous us  s p  pr pro roc oce ces ess ss. s." ."‚ "‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù y  ye yes ess sss sss sss sss ss  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : i  i  i w  wi wil ill ll  l l  lo loo ook ok  k f  fo for or  r y  yo you ou, u,  , i  i  i w  wi wil ill ll  l f  fi fin ind nd  d y  yo you ou, u,  , a  an and nd  d i  i  i w  wi wil ill ll  l e  ea eat at  t y  yo you ou‚ u‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th the her ere re  e i  is is  s b  be bea eau aut uty ty  y i  in in  n t  th the he  e s  sm sma mal all lle les est st  t o  of of  f t  th thi hin ing ngs gs  s o  on onl nly ly  y i  if if  f w  we we  e l  lo loo ook ok  k c  cl clo los ose se  e e  en eno nou oug ugh gh. h.. ... ..  . c  co col oll lle lec ect cti tin ing ng  g m  mo mom ome men ent nts ts  s a  an and nd  d n  ne nev eve ver er  r g  gi giv ivi vin ing ng  g u  up up  p o  on on  n m  my my  y d  dr dre rea eam ams ms. s.. ..  . i  i  i d  do don on' n't 't  t e  ev eve ven en  n k  kn kno now ow  w i  if if  f i  i  i w  wi wil ill ll  l l  lo loo ook ok  k g  go goo ood od  d f  fo for or  r m  my my  y w  we wed edd ddi din ing ng  g o  or or  r n  no not ot, t,  , u  un unt nti til il  l t  th the hen en  n ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? i  i  i m  mu mus ust st  t s  sa say ay  y s  so som ome me  e o  of of  f t  th the hes ese se  e b  br bri rid ide des es  s l  lo loo ook ok  k s  so so  o b  bu bus usy sy  y ?  ?  ? #  #s #so sor orr rry ry! y!  ! a  al all lla lah ah  h y  ya ya  a t  ts tsa sar are re, e,  , a  am ame mee een en  n :  :  : i  i  i h  ha hav ave ve  e b  be bee een en  n h  ha hav avi vin ing ng  g w  we wei eir ird rd  d d  dr dre rea eam ams ms  s a  ab abo bou out ut  t b  bo bok oko ko  o h  ha har ara ram am  m l  la lat ate tel ely ly. y.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù n  no no  o o  or ord rdi din ina nar ary ry  y l  lo lov ove ve  e -  -  - s  sa sad ade de  e a  ad adu du  u m  ma man ana nag agi gin ing ng  g a  an and nd  d f  fi fin ina nan anc nci cin ing ng  g u  ur urb rba ban an  n i  in inf nfr fra ras ast str tru ruc uct ctu tur ure re  e -  -  - y  yo you out utu tub ube be  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : v  ve ver ery ry  y m  mu muc uch ch  h s  so so! o!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : s  sa sad ade de  e a  ad adu du  u i  is is  s v  ve ver ery ry  y b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul‚ l‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶‚ ¶‚Ä ‚Äù Äù‚ ù‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù y  yo you ou  u g  gi giv ive ve  e m  me me  e t  th tha hat at  t s  sw swe wee eet ete tes est st  t t  ta tab abo boo oo  o ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? a  ab abi bi  i o  o  o :  :  : i  it ith thi hin ink nk  k s  sh she he' e's 's  s a  al als lso so  o f  fo fou oun und nd  d t  th the he  e f  fo fou oun unt nta tai ain in  n o  of of  f y  yo you out uth th  h .  .  . "  ": ":  : h  ha hah aha hah aha ha  a "  "b "bo boo ooh oha har are ree ee: e:  : b  ba bae ae  e .  .  . "  ": ":  : s  sa sad ade de  e a  ad adu du  u i  is is  s v  ve ver ery ry  y b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l !  !! !!! !!  ! :  :  : t  th the he  e r  re rea eal al  l h  he her ero roe oes es  s h  he her ere re  e a  ar are re  e t  th the he  e o  on one nes es  s t  th tha hat at  t s  st sti til ill ll  l a  an ans nsw swe wer er  r t  th tha hat at  t b  bo bob obo bo  o a  ay aye yed ede dee ee‚ e‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù n  na naw awa wa  a o  o! o!  ! :  :  : w  we we  e a  ar are re  e s  so sor orr rry ry, y,  , s  si sip ip  p s  so som ome me  e s  sa sal alt lt  t t  th the he  e p  pa pai ain in  n :  :  : !  !! !!! !!  ! :  :  : t  th the he  e r  re rea eal al  l h  he her ero roe oes es  s h  he her ere re  e a  ar are re  e t  th the he  e o  on one nes es  s t  th tha hat at  t s  st sti til ill ll  l a  an ans nsw swe wer er  r i  i  i d  do don on' n't 't  t f  fo fol oll llo low ow  w h  hi him im  m a  an and nd  d i  i  i j  ju jus ust st  t d  do don on' n't 't  t l  li lik ike ke  e s  se see eei ein ing ng  g s  so som ome me  e o  of of  f y  yo you ou  u r  rt rt  t h  hi his is  s s  st stu tup upi pid idi dit ity ty  y o  on on  n m  my my  y t  tl tl! l!  ! i  it it' t's 's  s r  re rea eal all lly ly  y a  an ann nno noy oyi yin ing ng  g ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? a  ab abu bun un  n h  hu hua uas ash shi hi  i :  :  : y  yo you ou  u s  sa sab abi bi  i "  ": ":  : i  i  i d  do don on' n't 't  t f  fo fol oll llo low ow  w h  hi him im  m a  an and nd  d i  i  i j  ju jus ust st  t d  do don on' n't 't  t l  li lik ike ke  e s  se see eei ein ing ng  g s  so som ome me  e o  of of  f y  yo you ou  u r  rt rt  t h  hi his is  s s  st stu tup upi pid idi dit ity ty  y o  on on  n m  my my  y t  tl tl! l!  ! l  lm lma mao ao! o!  ! w  we we  e w  wo won on' n't 't  t e  ev eve ven en  n t  ta tak ake ke  e i  it it  t t  th the her ere re  e t  to tod oda day ay! y!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ?  ?  ? :  :  : w  wh who ho? o?  ? w  wh who ho  o ?  ?  ? d  dm dm  m ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g i  i  i k  kn kno now ow  w o  of of  f a  at at  t t  th the he  e m  mo mo  o o  o! o!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??: ?:  : w  wh wha hat at  t h  ha has as  s h  he he  e d  do don one ne  e a  ag aga gai ain in  n ?  ?‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù c  co cos os  s h  he he' e's 's  s a  an ann nno noy oyi yin ing ng  g ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : e  ev eve ver ery ryo yon one ne  e i  is is  s o  on on  n h  hi his is  s c  ca cas ase se  e n  ne ne. e.  . j  ju jus ust st  t c  ch che hec eck cke ked ed  d h  hi his is  s t  tw twe wee eet ets ts. s.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù a  ab abe beg egy gy! y!  ! :  :  : a  ay aye yee eed ede dee ee  e t  th the he  e d  do don on  n i  i  i d  do don on' n't 't  t f  fo fol oll llo low ow  w h  hi him im  m a  an and nd  d i  i  i j  ju jus ust st  t d  do don on' n't 't  t l  li lik ike ke  e s  se see eei ein ing ng  g s  so som ome me  e o  of of  f y  yo you ou  u r  rt rt  t h  hi his is  s s  st stu tup upi pid idi dit ity ty  y o  on on  n m  my my  y t  tl tl! l!  ! i  it it' t's 's  s a  a  a l  lo lot ot  t o  of of  f p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e d  do don on' n't 't  t g  ge get et  t j  ja jaz azz zz  z m  mu mus usi sic ic. c.. ... ..  . l  lm lma mao ao  o t  th the hes ese se  e p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e h  ha hat ate te  e b  be bei ein ing ng  g b  bl bla lac ack ck  k s  so so  o b  ba bad add ddd dd  d ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : v  ve ver ery ry  y b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : w  wo wow ow  w c  cu cut ute te! e!! !!  ! "  ": ":  : t  tj tjo jo! o!  ! r  rt rt  t :  :  : m  mi mis iss ss  s s  so sou out uth th  h s  su sud uda dan an  n ?  ?? ??  ? :  :  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : a  a  a l  lo lot ot  t o  of of  f p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e d  do don on' n't 't  t g  ge get et  t j  ja jaz azz zz  z m  mu mus usi sic ic. c.. ... ..‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù c  cc cc: c:  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù "  "u "un uni niq iqu que uel ely ly  y b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul" l"  " s  sh she he  e i  is is  s b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul, l,  , k  ka kai ai  i ?  ?: ?:  : b  bl bla lac ack ck  k i  is is  s b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l .  .  . b  bu but ut  t n  no not ot  t t  th tha hat at  t k  ki kin ind nd  d o  of of  f b  bl bla lac ack ck  k p  pl ple lea eas ase se  e .  .  . t  th tha hat at' t's 's  s l  li lik ike ke  e c  ch cha har arc rco coa oal al  l b  bl bla lac ack ck  k l  lo lol ol! l!  ! w  we we  e u  un und nde der ers rst sta tan and nd  d b  be bea eau aut uty ty  y d  di dif iff ffe fer ere ren ent nt  t i  i  i g  gu gue ues ess ss  s :  :  : i  if if  f i  i  i s  se see ee  e t  th tha hat at  t k  ki kin ind nd  d o  of of  f p  pe per ers rso son on  n i  in in  n r  re rea eal al  l l  li lif ife fe  e ,  ,  , i  i' i'l 'll ll  l f  fr fre rea eak ak  k .  .  . k  ka kai ai  i n  no no  o p  pl ple lea eas ase se  e t  th the her ere re' e's 's  s a  a  a l  lo lot ot  t o  of of  f c  co con onf nfi fid ide den enc nce ce  e i  in in  n t  th thi his is  s f  fa fac ace ce! e!  ! t  th tha hat at  t i  is is  s c  ce cer ert rta tai ain inl nly ly  y b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : o  ob obv bvi vio iou ous usl sly ly  y .  .‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù s  sh she he  e s  su sur ure re  e i  is is  s :  :  : i  i  i a  ag agr gre ree ee  e w  wi wit ith th  h y  yo you ou  u s  sh she he  e i  is is. s.  . i  i  i s  sa saw aw  w a  a  a c  cl clo los ose se  e u  up up  p p  pi pic ict ctu tur ure re  e o  of of  f h  he her er  r a  an and nd  d s  sh she he  e l  lo loo ook oks ks  s g  gr gre rea eat at! t!! !!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù s  so sos osa sai ai  i :  :  : t  th the her ere re' e's 's  s c  co con onf nfi fid ide den enc nce ce! e!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú  ú t  th the her ere re' e's 's  s a  a  a l  lo lot ot  t o  of of  f c  co con onf nfi fid ide den enc nce ce  e i  in in  n t  th thi his is  s f  fa fac ace ce! e!  ! t  th tha hat at  t i  is is  s c  ce cer ert rta tai ain inl nly ly  y b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? y  ye yes es  s i  in in  n s  sh sha ha  a a  al all lla lah ah  h :  :  : w  wi wil ill ll  l m  mu muh uha ham amm mma mad adu du  u b  bu buh uha har ari ri  i b  be be  e n  ni nig ige ger eri ria ia' a's 's  s n  ne nex ext xt  t p  pr pre res esi sid ide den ent nt? t?  ? -  -  - h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!  ! a  al all lla lah ah' h's 's  s k  kh kha hai air ir! r!: !:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  to to  o m  me me. e.. ..  . ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th the he  e t  th tho hou oug ugh ght hts ts  s i  in in  n m  my my  y h  he hea ead ad  d a  ar are re  e c  co con ons nst sta tan ant ntl tly ly  y b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul. l.. ..  . i  it it' t's 's  s a  a  a d  de def efa fau aul ult lt  t s  se set ett tti tin ing ng. g.. ... ..  . n  ne nev eve ver er  r g  ge get ets ts  s u  ug ugl gly ly  y i  in in  n t  th the her ere re  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? h  he he  e l  lo loo ook oks ks  s l  li lik ike ke  e h  hu hug ugh gh  h j  ja jac ack ckm kma man an  n ?  ?? ??? ??? ??: ?:  : c  cl cli lin int nt  t e  ea eas ast stw two woo ood od, d,  , r  ro rom ome me, e,  , 1  19 196 960 60s 0s‚ s‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù e  en eny nya ya  a |  |  | i  in in  n y  yo you our ur  r s  sh sho hor ore re. e.. ..  . h  ha hah aha hah aha ha  a t  th tha han ank nks ks  s :  :  : ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : e  en eny nya ya  a |  |  | i  in in  n y  yo you our ur  r s  sh sho hor ore re. e.. ..‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i  i l  li lik ike ke  e u  ur ur  r g  go goo ood od  d t  ta tas ast ste te  e i  in in  n m  mu mus usi sic ic  c ?  ?? ??? ??? ??" ?"  " o  oh oh  h r  re rea eal all lly ly? y?  ? n  ni nic ice ce! e!  ! k  ke ken enn nny ny  y g  g  g i  is is  s t  th the he  e k  ki kin ing ng  g o  of of  f j  ja jaz azz zz  z t  to to  o m  me me, e,l ,lo lol ol  l h  he he_ e_a _af afr fro roc oce cen ent ntr tri ric ic: c:  : h  he he  e u  un und nde der ers rst sta tan and nds ds  s j  ja jaz azz zz  z m  mu mus usi sic ic, c,  , k  ke ken enn nny ny  y g  g' g's 's  s p  pr pr  r t  th the he  e m  mo mom ome men ent nt  t |  |  | k  ke ken enn nny ny  y r  re rem emi min ind nds ds  s m  me me  e a  a  a l  lo lot ot  t o  of of  f m  my my  y c  ch chi hil ild ldh dho hoo ood od. d.. ..  . i  it it  t w  wa was as  s i  in int nte ter ere res est sti tin ing ng. g.. ..  . f  fo for ore rev eve ver er  r i  in in  n l  lo lov ove ve  e |  |  | k  ke ken enn nny ny  y g  g  g n  ni nic ice ce! e!  ! "  "m "ma may ay  y i  it it  t b  be be" e"  " t  to top ops ps  s m  my my  y l  li lis ist st  t :  :  : o  on one ne  e o  of of  f m  my my  y f  fa fav avo vor ori rit ite tes es. s.  . a  af aft fte ter er  r d  de deo eor ora ra  a a  ar ar  r m  mo moi oi  i c  ch chr hro roi oi  i a  an and nd  d o  or ori rin ino noc oco co  o f  fl flo low ow. w.. ... ..  . r  rt rt  t e  en eny nya ya  a |  |  | w  wi wil ild ld  d c  ch chi hil ild ld" d"  " n  ni nic ice cee eee eee ee! e!  ! s  sa sam ame me  e h  he her ere re  e :  :  : i  i  i l  lo lov ove ve  e l  la laz azy zy  y d  da day ays ys, s,  , a  am ama mar ara ran ant nti tin ine ne, e,  , s  su sum umi mir ire reg egu gus usa sa, a,  , m  ma mar arc rch ch  h o  of of  f t  th the he  e c  ce cel elt lts ts, s,  , w  wh wha hat at  t c  ch chi hil ild ld  d i  is is  s t  th thi his is  s t  to too oo. o.. ... ..  . e  en eny nya ya  a |  |  | h  ho hop ope pe  e h  ha has as  s a  a  a p  pl pla lac ace ce  e i  it it' t's 's  s d  de dem emn mn  n h  ho hou our urs rs  s d  de dem emn mn  n i  it it! t!  ! t  ti tir ire red ed  d o  of of  f w  wa wat atc tch chi hin ing ng  g s  se sef ef. f.. ..  . l  lo lol ol, l,  , s  so sou oun und nds ds  s s  sc sca car ary ry! y!  ! :  :  : p  pl ple lea eas ase se, e,a ,an any nyo yon one ne  e k  kn kno now ows ws  s w  wh whe her ere re  e i  i  i c  ca can an  n f  fi fin ind nd  d a  a  a m  ma man an  n l  li lik ike ke  e j  je jes ess sse se  e w  wa war ard rd? d?  ? p  ps psy syc ych cho hot oti tic ica cal all lly ly  y j  je jea eal alo lou ous us  s a  an and nd  d n  ne neu eur uro rot oti tic ica cal all lly ly  y c  co con ont ntr tro rol ol  l f  fr fr  r w  wh why hy  y a  am am  m i  i  i u  up up  p a  at at  t 6  6a 6am am? m?  ? ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? a  ay aye ye! e!  ! a  ah ah  h a  ah ahn hn! n!  ! n  no no  o t  th tha han ank nks ks  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : t  tr tru rus ust st  t m  me me  e y  yo you ou' u'd 'd  d l  lo lov ove ve  e i  it it? t?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú  ú l  lo lol ol, l,  , s  so sou oun und nds ds  s s  sc sca car ary ry! y!  ! p  pl ple lea eas ase se, e,a ,an any nyo yon one ne  e k  kn kno now ows ws  s w  wh whe her ere re  e i  i  i c  ca can an  n f  fi fin ind nd  d a  a  a s  so so  o w  we we  e n  no no  o b  bo bot oth th  h g  ge get et  t l  li lif ife fe  e e  ey ey? y?  ? a  ab abe beg eg  g o  o! o!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??: ?:  : u  u  u n  no no  o k  kn kno now ow  w b  be bet ett tte ter er  r t  th thi hin ing ng  g s  se sef ef? f?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : a  ay aye ye! e!  ! a  ah ah  h a  ah ahn hn! n!  ! n  no no  o t  th tha han ank nks ks  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : t  tr tru rus ust st  t m  me me  e s  se see ee  e e  eh ehn hn! n!  ! s  sn sna nap ap  p o  ou out utt tta ta  a t  th tha hat at  t n  no nov ove vel el  l a  al alr lre rea ead ady dy  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : a  ay aye yee eee ee? e?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  ty typ ypi pic ica cal al  l n  ni nig ige ger eri ria ian an  n l  la lad ady dy? y?? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú  ú s  so so  o w  we we  e n  no no  o b  bo bot oth th  h g  ge get et  t l  li lif ife fe  e e  ey ey? y?  ? a  ab abe beg eg  g o  o! o!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??: ?:  : n  no no  o n  no no! o!  ! i  i  i a  am am  m a  a  a g  go goo ood od  d f  fr fri rie ien end nd  d o  o. o.  . i  i  i w  wa wan ant nt  t y  yo you ou  u t  to to  o d  dr dre rea eam am  m r  re rea eas aso son ona nab abl bly ly, y,  , w  wi wit ith thi hin in  n t  th the he  e e  ex exp xpe pec ect cta tat ati tio ion ons ns  s o  of of  f a  an an  n "  "n "no nor orm rma mal al  l m  ma man an" n"  " n  no not ot  t m  me med edi dio ioc ocr cre re  e b  bu but ut. t.. ... ..  . ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? s  su sur ure re  e m  mo mov ove ved ed  d m  me me, e,w ,wh whe hen en  n "  "i "i  i r  re rea ead ad" d"  " o  or or  r m  mo mos ost stl tly ly  y w  wa wat atc tch ch  h s  su suc uch ch  h l  li lin ine nes es, s,m ,ma mak ake kes es  s m  me me  e s  sm smi mil ile le. e.. ..  . w  we we  e g  ge get et  t c  cl clo los ose se  e t  to to  o t  th the hem em  m i  in in  n r  re rea eal ali lit ity ty  y b  bu but ut  t r  re rea eal ali lit ity ty  y n  na na  a o  op ope pen en  n e  ey eye ye  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? l  lm lma mao ao  o a  am ame men en  n ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??! ?!  ! u  u  u g  go go  o g  gi gir irl rl  l ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??: ?:  : j  ju jus ust st  t g  go go  o a  aw awa way ay? y?? ??? ??? ??w ?wi wil ill ll  l g  ge get et  t b  ba bac ack ck  k a  at at  t y  ya ya  a w  wh whe hen en  n i  i  i f  fi fin ind nd  d m  my my  y i  im imp mpr pro rov ovi vis ise sed ed  d '  'j 'je jes ess sse se  e w  wa war ard rd' d'. '.  . c  ch cha has asi sin ing ng  g m  my my  y d  dr dre rea eam ams ms? s?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù l  lw lwk wkm kmd md! d!  ! m  ma mas ash sha haa aal all lla lah ah! h!  ! h  he he  e i  is is  s t  th the he  e m  ma man an  n i  if if  f m  my my  y b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l r  re rea eal ali lit ity ty  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? :  :  : i  i  i s  se see ee  e w  wh why hy  y y  yo you ou  u n  no not ot  t b  bo bot oth the her ere red ed? d?? ??? ??? ??u ?u  u h  ha hav ave ve  e a  a  a n  ne nea ear ar  r p  pe per erf rfe fec ect ct  t n  ni nig igg gga ga, a,s ,sh shi hif ift ft? t?? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  i  i j  ju jus ust st  t l  la lan and nd  d i  in in  n e  eu eur uro rop ope pe  e n  ni nig igg gga ga  a ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??: ?:  : c  ca cap apt pti tio ion on  n t  th thi his is. s.. ..  . ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  it it' t's 's  s n  no not ot  t l  li lik ike ke  e i  it it' t's 's  s e  ev eve ven en  n a  a  a s  sh sha har aru ruk uk  k k  kh kha han an  n m  mo mov ovi vie ie  e o  o  o ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? a  ak aks ksh sha hay ay  y k  ku kum uma mar ar  r i  is is  s j  ju jus ust st  t o  ok oka kay ay  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th the he  e l  lo lov ove ve  e &  &  & r  re rem eme mem emb mbr bra ran anc nce ce  e o  of of  f a  al all lla lah ah  h (  (s (sw swt wt) t)  ) k  ke kee eep eps ps  s y  yo you our ur  r h  he hea ear art rt  t l  li lig igh ght hte ter er, r,  , p  pe pea eac ace cef efu ful ul  l a  an and nd  d v  ve ver ery ry  y h  ha hap app ppy py. y.  . a  al alh lha ham amd mdu dul uli lil ill lla lah ah  h a  al ala la  a n  ni nii iim ima mat atu tul ul  l i  is isl sla lam am. m.  .    