Photo: http://t.co/CqqIWsKS TOROIDAL SPACE and the paradox of extra dimensional space. http://t.co/OHQbMcgE @username wait...  MATEO YA VA A LA PRIMARIA????? Let's Build a Goddamn Tesla Museum http://t.co/YHx2OQkj "Dionysius Thrax, or perhaps someone else (exact authorship being undestandably difficult to be sure of with text of this vintage)" ¿Quieren leer un artículo tendencioso?, lean éste: In Google’s Inner Circle, a Falling Number of Women http://t.co/Ak4E37CZ Que, by the way, entre todas, suman 15 campus. Y es rector de todas, leyó usted bien. robotcosmonaut: Coffee Is Always A Good Idea http://t.co/ZqNAtZEd Me andan toqueteando por facebook. Help! Snif. Photo:  http://t.co/sCOPqBye "This item will be released on November 20, 2012" *muere* Te odio mucho Shonda Rhimes. Cups http://t.co/8m8ppLhM robotcosmonaut: Miss October via mudwerks http://t.co/ultKdzYB I should peddle butterflies. Look at that! http://t.co/P2lPxesh Yes, I said it's fine before, but I don't think so no more... erase and rewind... And my timeline is more like a flatline. Dead. Women of Pinotepa de Don Luis, Oaxaca http://t.co/6Go5N6H1 Why are we here?  http://t.co/V2SI2rUx Cassette Rainbow <3 http://t.co/bmd5H81Z Flying Colors by Olivier Lutaud http://t.co/s3PUQvAA Dragonfly http://t.co/HhrNmjPD loteriart: la luna by illustrated ink http://t.co/dDwMEMUO Typode A simple font created by Santiago Ortiz with co-ordinates for creative coding eff… http://t.co/HCTaGx3h Photo:  http://t.co/LxunhdiJ Simple things are way more interesting than complicated ones. True story. "Thank you for paying your bill promptly... we have refunded your deposit and interest as a credit on this bill." ¿Todavía existe Twitter? I am alive, barely. Finally Google shut up and took my money. ((I know things)) Somebody there? I have a dream. http://t.co/SES930mO Once again, the 49ers who? Crazy people everywhere. Swish, smack! Whip crack! Batter and beat! Yammer and bleat! Work, work! Nor dare to shirk... Ok glass, make me a coffee. ?? coffee is pouring out my ears ?? Hello World! http://t.co/x92fmogZqt So, what's the plan and so? I didn't know that she has a PhD in mexican social history: http://t.co/A5gH56rz3Q It's May already? Good morning http://t.co/gwTXjuWRbM @username on my way :-) My dear, dear inexistent friends, how you're doing? and I'll send all my loving to you... @username hello Deb, that's a surprise. How are you? @username i know what you mean... *suda como Cinderella* Good morning humans... http://t.co/PpeeCp9VkG Home :) Beware the weeping angel. close your eyes and feel the movement... "Equidistant... so grown up!" And for my next trick...! I miss Amy and Rory. Watch A Computer Try To Learn How To Walk http://t.co/tc19BE8u8V via @username Photo: kenobi-wan-obi: Earthshine by Dani Caxete http://t.co/28GPQvbj0D Photoset: Bent Objects by Terry Border Ain’t it cool? http://t.co/Di14SC4ehr @username hey i just was listening welcome to the jungle :P Come and visit me while I'm in prison. "Science is a co-operative enterprise, spanning the generations. It's the passing of a torch from teacher to student to teacher..." "... A community of minds reaching back from antiquity and forward to the stars." We love you Tyrion. Stop it, #FRA Status: Installing system update... The coffee song ? https://t.co/BOsdZF4AVG "See first, think later, then test" White House responds to Tesla direct sales: We love Tesla, can't help http://t.co/e0QEySZsUU via @username That time will come, one day you'll see when we can all be friends... https://t.co/8tfPXue9Bq Anytime is coffee time http://t.co/H5TeMdypXw #omarsays PowerPoint doesn't work! Love the animals. @username as always Yep, winter is coming. Let's go to Mars, baby. @username hi, when will the Christmas special of Derek available on Netflix in Mexico? All my family is waiting for it. Bello: The Mexican morass http://t.co/UAhRF8jl3o via @username 