We knew this day would come, we knew it all along. The best part is anticipation. "Don't you dare leave me now, throw my heart on the ground..." One day we are best friends is because each day we forget the day before. Therefore there is no grudges and always something to talk about. I can fricken see! #thankgod :) Driving through jackson there is mor car places than fast food. -_- I hate my last name. Can I have yours ? "We both already a man." So I thout id say I miss you <3 There is frost on the ground. -_- One sexy man. :) That's tight, ignore me because you are walking with your boyfriend. #expected Two tests tommrow. #killmenow Whatever happened to us being like sisters? miss that duck :'( Tweeting when walking. @username Well this sucks... @username aw... that's sweet! My cats in the bathtub,i finally found my pants and its homecoming. Its bound to be a good day http://t.co/QfljotFr 40 days sounds a hell of a lot more than 39 days... 30 minutes till 39 days <3 Off key and don't care <3 If you don't know the moves to jump on it, the beat to Sandstorm or every lyric to "Don't Stop Believing", you don't go to Grass Lake. How I spent my Saturday "morning" http://t.co/ZKW9uucQ You can be crippled by fear, or motivated by it. Move toward it. Embrace it. As a way to make me feel like shit after a game... Ok, if we are arguing I am going to walk away. I'm not going to stand there and kepe doing what I was doing and be yelled at. @username haha it's not really a big deal. Text me though n ill t ell you! That frosting on her tummy... that's my doing.... :) @username @username http://t.co/1TDc4OzS "prostitution" "thats okay" Teacher: "menstruating" Student:" I'm out!" Ortho :/ Anywhere else but here please. #thingsidontmiss Picking out colors for braces. Baby come back to me! @username working on it! You have a really funny fac in one :) Cus' this is what we do when we dress up <3 http://t.co/VUZJieNg @username the are on Chica! @username what? I'm confused! Dm me! @username "Go For Gold!!!" Playing dress up #justkidding http://t.co/xxPV9x5S I would tell u to have fun, but that might be a little weird... Probably one of the best days in about 72 days <3 @username I thought id let you know you are a dumbass, I still luv ya though brother! ;) I need a night away from my house... I really need to get my mind out of the gutter... ???? Probably the next best thing to cuddling with you <3 Me: "peace out Beeotch" @username http://t.co/b1PKOh8c @username you can't say ew... It's #DavidBeckham! @username it was the Calvin Kline ad! Me: "Uh... Me too... I like, you know.... Umm" You: "I know what you mean." ^ And that's why I love you. How are you so good at goodbyes? "I finally found the words to say..." The sun went away :( 1/12th Of a year = 1 Month = 31 Days = 744 Hours = 44640 Minutes = <3 Damn watch out for those cars! That really attractive sleepy voice <3 I hope that first wasn't also a last <3 I have never smoked, never drank, I don't plan on doing either... & yes, other teens like me still do exist, they are called my friends. "I love his face... Uh I meant laugh not face, I don't know how that happened." LMAO @username I am a fighter <3 @username personally I think that's a terrible angle on me. ???? @username @username @username @username @username its a better angle!!! :) Sisters for life <3 @username http://t.co/MBDTKhaV A glass of milk, plate of pancakes and an ipad in my hands. I dropped my fork. Now tell me how in the hell am I suppose to pick it up?!? #thingsILove the fact that @username and I can wear each other's clothes and match, without planning it. No mom, not "hot babes" ... #tumblrboys "He made us matching belt buckels out of magnets, I can't wait to slow dance" -Kimmy Gibler #notakidsshow #fullhouse Pitbull sucks? You suck. "Tap mah goodies or something" @username Don't accidentally say have instead of thought.... It turns out bad. Don't wear your pants up high and your boxers higher. I thought this was cute ;) http://t.co/TzShKV0E Just another Saturday, kickin back and loving it! http://t.co/zhM52Uvb @username @username https://t.co/Bvte4OqT I love how we're crushing Haley :) I didn't even know she had put the needle in :) @username @username http://t.co/lGjpeSUJ @username what can I say? I'm sorry... My ring is like glory purple! No gems too heavy. @username can't promise nothing with sports and everybody's different though... *Drill Sargent in the background yells one minute* #ThingsIHate “@username: @username ELISSA -_-”  <----- That's my name!!! ???????????? @username no that's not your name that's mine! @username Was that to my 5 page text or my last tweet? :) @username "who when where?" Me: "Me. Why? How?" Andrea:"Wow." Had a blast tonight! @username @username @username @username :D http://t.co/DyNKz2K5 Do I really have to go to school today? #movieday Two letters today :) :) :) http://t.co/JXkSJ6zg I got 2 letters. I'm so excited I got them. I don't want to read them. They might be the last until you're home. 19 days, I can't wait! <3 Found her like this, SLEEPING, OVER MY IPAD. @username http://t.co/dQPhCxLX "Have a lining room with a big tv and still sleep on the couch..." #lyrictweet I forgot my f*cking teddybear! I think I might cry :'(... #lonleynight @username why a ]: ???? @username oh I know I'm so depressed! @username shawhatt? Shutter. ?The movie made me... well, shutter. Talking to him everyday is pretty much seems unrealistic right now... I want my hubby! ???? @username When I say something, I mean it. Summer, can you please come home? http://t.co/ttWGRR9A “@username: #10ArtistsIWantToMeet Pitbull @username” HolyHellyesssss! “@username: Tryouts Monday, #BallerStatus @username ???????????????? #TimetoDie ????????????” Pumped!!!!!!! ???? Gonna Die!!! ???? 