I can't stop watching this video http://t.co/w2QoLIU I'm completely aware  that my #macbook is gonna die  #shit #riot anywhere but #Italy #londonriots “@username: London turns to crowdsourcing to identify looters and clean up after riots | http://t.co/uja0jTM (via @username)” Showing rich people we would do what we want http://t.co/sWARXHm #riotlondon Unfair and sad http://t.co/PVbz6vK #londonriots #looters @username Seems that politics dont' want to deal it, the worst example are italian member of Parliament No books please we're rioters http://t.co/FyBks4j #Riots “@username: FLASH: Any coloured people out in Bermondsey beware. National Front are out beating anyone ethnic. #LondonRiots #StaySafe ” Really enjoyed The Hour episode III People are really fast with irony: here's a new Tumblr about looters http://t.co/jSnM86U #Riots I just became the mayor of Viale Roma on @username! http://4sq.com/cAaOa9 Just posted a photo  @username Viale Roma http://instagr.am/p/J2zDN/ “@username: Next, after the crisis: the eclipse of the arrogant fashion bloggers.” #Chile has something to riot for http://t.co/H1ug1Eh #riot An italian Tumblr for British ways to say... http://t.co/gKzsQay #tumblr #UK Gne@username: RT @username: Warp stock destroyed in fire at PIAS/SONY  London warehouse on Monday night - information: http://t.co/aDkABde Unhealthy, tasteless, high prices: food @username #Malpensa airport is a nightmare. They lose the chance to' showcase italian #food #culture Follow !“@username: Follow our 48-hour magazine at the South Bank Centre http://t.co/UtaEK0I  on #48hrmag” I'm at Alghero w/ 2 others http://t.co/Iw8aYjF Suggested #breakfast pecorino cheese and fichi d'india #yummy #weird #sardinia #food <3“@username: Chef and owner of the acclaimed D.O.M. restaurant,  Atala makes a home delivery with his signature dish http://t.co/EvjxlBJ” #Alghero is awesome but its politicians are not wise enough: dirty steets,60's decadent houses and no promotion of its #food #culture Same here #italy “@username: "There’s nothing wrong our country, there is something wrong w/ our politics"  #countrybeforeparty” “ikea non scherzare col fuoco ti bruciano eh! RT @username: Absolutely crazy @username ad from Australia: Have a gö http://t.co/FcJHnTP” stasera qui“@username: Tonight I'm going to play with Frankie Hi Nrg and my friend Brokenbrix on the beach, see you there! #Sardinia” @username brighton rules I'm at Spiaggia Le Bombarde (Fertilia) w/ 2 others http://t.co/q0pNJt0 Djset on the Bombarde beach  @username Spiaggia Le Bombarde http://t.co/RcIEn4P @username playing at bombarde beach #Alghero #Sardegna good vibes Going to #Sardinia east coast on air Full's Gold latest mix by @username I'm at Palau (via fonte vecchia, Italy) w/ 3 others http://t.co/mX2HFoy Just posted a photo  @username Palau http://t.co/XM1yF31 In the middle of nowhere in cala bunone #Sardinia Humans are destroying the most beatiful beaches in europe I'm at Via Michelangelo 2 (Alghero) http://t.co/Eqyymql Just back  from Sardinia #eastcoast jeez, what's goin on? #Pukkelpop #crisis #italyepicfail @username @username only bad news for Italy? “@username: stop fake luxury for cheap people! #boycottzara” better shout #stopfakedesires #justsaying “@username: MADRID ES COMO WOODSTOCK PERO SIN FOLLAR” @username now playing in Alghero downtown (@username Miramare) [pic]: http://t.co/YtEe75A I'm at Ramblas (Via Don Minzoni, Via Lido, Alghero) w/ 2 others http://t.co/d8uSPUn I just unlocked the "Swimmies" badge on @username! http://t.co/ASpK3uW I'm at Alghero Beach http://t.co/766do2I Wearing tha nipote http://t.co/EK2j1J9 @username have a good trip! Nice sounds yesterday “@username: Liam D on NTSradio.co.UK from 8pm. EXTENDED PLAY SESSIONS. All styles. TUNE IN! @username” “@username: Check this out: RT @username: #Nowplaying  @username : http://t.co/xCZlois via @username” Studying on the beach (@username Spiaggia Le Bombarde) http://t.co/lYYyc8F Laying on the beach is like living in a sociology essay (@username Spiaggia Le Bombarde) http://t.co/MT5HJ40 I just became the mayor of Via Michelangelo 2 on @username! http://t.co/y6iYWzD Just posted a photo  @username Catalunya Hotel http://t.co/8Y9AzBw The beauty is truth and truth is beuty  @username Spiaggia La Pelosa http://t.co/ZdTKbWT Early wake up, news time (@username Via Michelangelo 2) http://t.co/vFJvNiB I just ousted @username as the mayor of Parco Giochi on @username! http://t.co/IPLefYZ Playing with nephews (@username Parco Giochi) http://t.co/j7EaLoE Just posted a photo  @username Alghero Piazza Sulis http://t.co/3PoG4ju Early morning to work in an ancient vegetable garden #organic (@username Via Michelangelo 2) http://t.co/xxvRCon discovered last year they Are good“@username: ACQTASTE Issue 1 http://t.co/QeVahLe” #food #magazine @username @username mmm stop pretending to be' italian please. “@username: Life is about creating& living experiences that are worth sharing. A tribute to #SteveJobs http://t.co/t5nuXLZ@username” I'm at Beach of Saline http://t.co/SWaH6jk I just unlocked the "Super Mayor" badge on @username! http://t.co/74zJFEq I just became the mayor of Bastioni! on @username! http://t.co/0qKicua I just unlocked the "Wino" badge on @username! http://t.co/VXPtkT3 Risky business  @username Fertilia http://t.co/0dEuKO4 I really hope that this will be' my last fall in Milan (@username Linate Gate A17) http://t.co/fuTKcCY I just unlocked the "Overshare" badge on @username! http://t.co/vY7a1zO “@username: The #madfoodcamp area looks amazing. Tomorrow, two years of work, dedication and patience becomes reality. Wish us luck!” Stavo per scrivere io ma preferisco citare l' amico @username: Hear Four Tet's Beats in Space session http://t.co/w6AO137 #fourtet” @username easy baby :) belle le foto di 55dsl! “@username: Menu Design in America, 1850-1985 | Graphic Design A la Carte | Shedonism http://t.co/cxSM5jx” “@username: Great British Bake Off IS the best thing on the telly at the moment.” Hey take a look to my food&music interview with @username , a beautiful and talented italian dj http://t.co/yw9cWOel 10 brands that stopped to be cool“@username: Is Mc Donny still cool? Is being fat cool?  - http://t.co/uyiqbBnA” #Foodmagazine to buy: #Menu Magazine from Capetown http://t.co/aNKGB79e thanks @username Photo: Well, well. Capitalism http://t.co/TFl4UTPx Good old mag to read better than says obvious words about #SteveJobs  http://t.co/Zi8ljNr6 “@username: Azealia Banks – 212 | Good Friday Music | Shedonism http://t.co/4QYXv9nT” Trying to know some more about vegan http://t.co/EoE1chHR @username @username more content and more attention on managing categories, it don't seem an innovative application #cheers great video about #OccupyWallStreet.  well done recipe of micro community http://t.co/iu41178A “@username: In case you missed this over the weekend: Printout! returns: http://t.co/u5vrhDES” l “@username: Here is the official cover for Issue Two http://t.co/eHbtbet2 #ACQTASTE” @username well done, send some for retail in Italy. #ACQTASTE “@username: OCCUPY MADISON AVENUE! http://t.co/cwQF5JWH” Let's occupy, sleepy italians! @username @username It's that kind of culture beuaty that we have to preserve here in Italy, don't u think? Beautiful street food by National Geographic http://t.co/BZ1MzBZv via @username @username @username Well done. Better done if reported live from the street though. #streetfood @username I'll write down a short list, I'll write to the email provided by your site. Cheers! #ACQTASTE @username @username Arancini are lovely. they are simbols of traditions and habits.sure food and cooking are a great link @username I was just pointing out that it could b even better if pictured them in the street of Sicily. Your contents are great “@username: Out now: the third issue of @username  http://t.co/II4HoDue” magazine di illustrazione molto buono #earlymorning tip Lawrence Lessing spaeks at #OccupyWallSt http://t.co/G5oYMj9Y #earlymorningtip @username good choise Ho fatto due foto a #TheophilusLondon bel fieu (@username Tommy Hilfiger) http://t.co/11t2CUIj “@username: P spectacular for graphic designers out there: here  redesign IL  (Italy) http://t.co/s2bCYlvd design @username ILsole24ore” @username :( Hai visto ieri sera Theophilus? #wintertimesucks @username @username interesting. i wish there was more pics about #mistura @username Thanks! @username Sure I will! 