You're no legend, you're a myth. That means I'll listen to your stories without even acknowledging your existence. Snapback off to you sir. RT @username: If I want the fucking planet, I can have it Don't take lyrics too seriously, part 3 #oops #dont #hate http://t.co/z5TE9r47U8 @username C-C-COMBO BREAKER! See you there man! "A lot of cats hate thay, all I can say black, there's a city full of walls you can post complaints at" In de linkercorner: de ongeslagen machtige 'master of the world': ILLUMINATI! In the rechtercorner,  'King without an oscar': LEO DICAPRIO! Who gives a fuck about an Oscar, it's still the same trashcan he lives in. Madonna & Justin Timberlake - 25 minutes (to gtfout of this bullshit) There is no such thing as sharing. Only investing. I need those Infinity Gems. 'Fuck hookers pay child support' - Lil' Wayne "I never sleep, 'cause sleep is the cousin of death" - Nas Show love where love is earned. "If you go platinum, it's got nothing to do with luck, it just means that a million people are stupid as fuck" Beats By Drehydration #funny #sadistic http://t.co/1urRZ6vpC9 "It's a Malaysian airliner, Tyrone. It's not as if it's a packet of fucking peanuts, is it?" Week van albumrelease; 1 of 2 tracks dope. 1, 2 maanden later: complete album addiction. Love my life! Love it love it love it ???? Fuck Flappy Bird, als je van wat uitgebreidere, story based/RPG shit houdt, check Out There. Gefrustreerd to the max. Taylor Swiftly van 't podium gekicked @username Sun don't shine, then son don't shine 'Ball so hard mahfuckas wanna find me' - Malaysian Boeing 777 "Believe half of what you see, and nothing you hear" Voor anti-Illuminati nieuws (those bitches are everywhere): http://t.co/oMe4ZBhOKU @username Envy is beautiful. #Exofeed Spread the fucking word. RT @username: It's Steak & BJ Day,  Or if you are Vegetarian....  Veggie burger and a wank Step your music knowledge up! 10 underrated artists, check it op http://t.co/ivmYS4xBv7 @username Ey fockjou man is oplichting This. Is. So. Good. http://t.co/1WA0FJyFyO @username Hammer Dance van  WTOH ook man. "Knife work with me but the chrome is extra, case I'm in the same taxi as The Bone Collector" pff "Hope you got a powerful chin, 'cause they say, blowjobs are flowers for men" ???? "Even if you forget me and everything you left behind, I never lied, I love you in a place where there's no space and time" I give a goddamn what your name is OMFG SUSAN IS DE MOL OMFG IK WIST HET AL DIE TIJD #nee Islands - The xx @username Jaa man, out of sight but #neveroutofheart No Sleep 'Till Rome - Beastie Boys In Da Club (Woody's Produce Remix) - 50 Cent, vraag @username @username @username Touchay RT @username: http://t.co/EaJ5YMYlux has to be the most useful tool for twitter // ja he Wow, fail. @username @username HET IS DE ONTKENNINGSFASE MARCO, SNAP OUT OF IT! @username Aight then @username See whatcha did there RT @username: Coolio did a stage dive in 2009 and the audience beat him and stole his shoes. // got a taste of his own racial medicine Shoutout naar Nujabes, helping me do my homework and study since 2010. RIP. "My enemies know what's poppin', you get it, they know what's poppin'" Uit bed komen, I can do this. Run To The Sun - N*E*R*D "Any man who knows a thing, knows he knows not a damn thing at all" Innerspace - Cunninlynguists ft. Toby "It's like let 'em hate, stay calm and meditate, when life has the lemons it's time to elemonate" @username Pff BNN ho all day I love walking #home at #night http://t.co/d4QmhCAwwr "I'm not sure of what I see, Cupid don't fuck with me.." als je die nog steeds kan afmaken hahaha Always stand your ground. @username The Weeknd - XO* Run To The Sun op elk moment vd dag.. Pharrell van N*E*R*D > Pharrell als solo artiest, sawry. Fock 'prinsen op witte paarden', they either gay or cheating. I Want It All - Arctic Monkeys Massale Twitter boycot ofzo? Where's everyone? "Seventeen rocks gleam from one ring, yo, let me let y'all niggas know one thing, there's one life, one love, so there can only be one King" #DescribeYourStatusWithASong I Need A Dollar The day we found McLovin from #Superbad #throwback #swag #handsome http://t.co/GE6hI9ni93 Slaapritme: Missing In Action Blessed with a curse. No I know, I'm no Superman, ooowoooowoooooo #Clothes #Love #Shopping #NoHomo http://t.co/yO33lmd8Uj Grandma n gramps, tired #one #happy #family http://t.co/YApA5WQZ0C "You Shot Me Right In The Face With A Carcano "- John F. Kennedy Practice what you preach and capture what you reach. Nieuwe campagne voor Durex: "Make love, not whores." Class #boring #school #throwup #wednesday http://t.co/dZKyTH0Fq9 In For The Kill (Skream Remix) - La Roux @username @username Hodeee shots fired! Started from the lotto now we rich Freddie Joachim remix van Mos Defs Mathematics, pff https://t.co/zgrL80G6r6 The Boondocks >>> Ik moet me wat vaker houden aan de uitspraak "Never argue with a fool, people may not be able to see the difference" John with the short last name. Don't front Retro Hash van Asher Roth, In Death Reborn van Army of the Pharaohs, en omdat het toch iets heeft, Talk Dirty van Jason Derulo gedownload. Naast een shitlading aan trapremixes ofcourse. Wif my #love ? http://t.co/emwlPI3YrD Heartless - Kanye West RT @username: THIS BITCH SWALLOWED AN XBOX CONTROLLER http://t.co/Lr3U8sj1eG // BROKKOOOOOOO I miss my cocoa butter kisses ???? Violations - Talib Kweli ft. Raekwon "My niggas keep it pure while you cut with the baking soda, these rappers be stretching the truth like they taking yoga" @username ey dis shit mo confusin than Nick Vaynes taste in music "You delicate, softer than some baby thighs, drag you kids to the underground like I'm Pennywise" No I know, I'm no Superman, whooooOOOOOooooOOOOOooooo@username#LazloBane #Scrubz @username Wat als ik 'm tegenkom? 'When it's all said and done, more is always said than done.' @username Haha of course QuaC I felt hazy then #work #swaggy #eyes #tired http://t.co/RJbDCYRyzj Friends are the family you choose, but real family will be the friends who will always remain at your side. @username Haha thanks! App anders? Anders teringlange spams op tl's :p And when the ink dries, and the pages turn to dust, so will we, so will we.. #FrankOcean #Dust Black referees >>> 