Check Emma Goldman's speech on What is Patriotism? "Patriotism, sir, is the last resort of scoundrels," Samuel Johnson http://t.co/CGzIxtUu All the social buzz made me watch #SatyamevJayate. It is a fantastic initiative. agree with @username to make it bigger than just TV A new semester - Monsoon 2010 academic session begins today. Excited to fall in a routine. Hopefully life will be more structured :) Six No-Internet-Days is such a pleasure and productive. Prepared for 5 talks, reviewed a Journal paper, read 4 books & was still bored Frontiers, Challenges, and Opportunities for Information Retrieval: SWIRL 2012 Report http://t.co/UDKyKiIn Good report but expected more LinkedIn app for windows is so impressive. Best mobile app I dare say. Off to Zurich to attend #ICSE2012 Looking forward to experiencing Swiss hospitality. at #MSR12 - Keynote on Software Analytics. Interesting to see the emergence of cross-disciplines analytics+datamining+social+User Experience #ICSE2012 #MSR12 MacBooks/iPads everywhere. Struggling to find Windows :) Compare this to a few years ago. One may publish on rise of Macs #MSR12 SeCold is wikipedia of software repositories-facts from open software source code http://t.co/A7jMh11E - interesting resource for MSR New Ideas in Mining S/w Repositories "Green Mining: A Methodology of Relating Software Change to Power Consumption" paper at #MSR12 The era of social programmer and the emergence of "software ecosystems" and "communities of practice" Keynote by Peggy Storey #MSR12 Social media helping the developer move towards "architecture of participation" #MSR12 - wonderful observation and need of the hour. Peggy is making a wonderful case for social media in MSR using Marshal McLuhan's work in understanding media #MSR12 Source code Comments, Tags, Blogging, Micro blogging, QA websites, wikis, Reputation sites are the tools for social programmer #MSR12 Knowledgeable to Knowledge-able is new Mantra to find a good job. Cannot write great programs? be a great searcher/finder @username Sure. You can find it at http://t.co/7dHmVIuo Story and Structure-in-a-story is like cat and smile in Alice's wonderland... there by not being there. 10th day without the mobile phone. Three to go. I am able to hear sounds better :) #myDrona is at stall number 186 in Vijayawada Book Fair, one of the largest book fairs in this part of the world. Tweet abt it if you visit. RIP #MehdiHassan Thank you for filling my heart with such intense and deep emotions through your Ghazals all these years. "We shouldn't go overboard with personalisation in search because serendipity is really valuable" Amit Singhal http://t.co/5kCojM36 I really want #Surface to be successful. Apple became cautious and slow with no real competition. Healthy competition fuels innovation @username Plz RT: Looking for Language Resource Members at http://t.co/puQOPuMb who are Fluent in Telugu &English Contact siel@username.ac.in >3,000 languages that are at risk of disappearing in the next 100 years. Effort from Google and some Univs to same them http://t.co/vBqKyW0g 53 Indian languages are endangered http://t.co/vBqKyW0g If you know any of them, try document them for future generations using this website Proud to see a friend and colleague from Univ. of Hyderabad, Prof. Panchanan Mohanty advising this project http://t.co/vBqKyW0g http://t.co/qrUqtimx Wonderful presentations at @username to know the state of the art in Sentiment Analysis. Thank you @username Can NL parsing be viewed as an Information Retrieval problem? - my regular open question in IR course. Still waiting for satisfactory answer BhagvatGita says: You are the Problem and You are the solution. In my world, it translates to: You are the search engine and you are the SEO Dear Search Engine, If you cannot interpret a user query, try to understand what he does with the results. It is raining great talks today at #IIIT-H. Peri Bhaskar Rao, two #IIIT-H alumni currently at #MIT and #Stanford. Is Machine Learning (ML) for ML sake or to solve real world problems? Growing detachment of ML from real world  http://t.co/i00p9plX @username a disclaimer: I have nothing to do with robot snake project though I am as proud as any IIIT-H member :) #myDrona is mentioned in Sakshi News paper Vijayawada edition http://epaper.sakshi.com/apnews/Vijayawada_East/06012011/3 Wonderful interaction with Prof. Anil Gupta of IIM-A. Says, true catalyst for Innovation is "Samvedana", feeling others' pain as your own. New academic years begins at IIITH. Campus is vibrant and filled with excitement. Welcome new members of IIITH family. "Life is so beautiful that death has fallen in love with it" #Life_of_pi  (Thanks to @username for providing the pointer) I liked GMail's  "priority inbox" video - more than the feature itself. What a clever way to communicate to aam-aadmi. Back from DST Conclave on Innovation at #IIMA. Great to see several academic incubators doing good work. 50+ of them funded by Indian Govt More impressive is Modi's Gujarat. It is written "Progressive" everywhere. Missing Hyderabad/AP's old times :( @username sorry for responding late. No is not the answer. Parsing can be an IR Problem. Know what are your documents and how to rank. @username is the twitter account for Cloud Computing course at IIIT-H. Please follow if you are doing the course. Like http://t.co/fIyo4l4J on Facebook to receive updates about Cloud Computing course at IIIT Hyderabad Why are human beings violent? Mainly because of invisible violence adults unconsciously inflict on children. Nice post: http://t.co/OiYf24hI I am at Indo-US workshop on Cloud Computing and Web services (Coimbatore). Will be talking about Machine Learning & Cloud Computing tomorrow @username Unfortunately not. But we expect to share a lot of material in public forums like in Facebook and Twitter. Legendary linguist and father figure of Indian linguistics Prof. Bh. Krishamurthy passes away. http://t.co/PQndn92M Hype Cycle for Cloud Computing Shows Enterprises Finding Value in Big Data, Virtualization  http://t.co/6sb2Cs6f Exciting guest lectures at @username Speakers from VMWare and Facebook are on board Software Engineering Distilled http://t.co/kuBkg5jq On August 15th, FREE education portal #myDrona beta is launched for Indian students. Please check and spread the word http://t.co/2OFf0h6F myDrona is on twitter @username and on Facebook http://t.co/hAuunpfK I will be giving a talk at an ACM event Friday 17th, on Automatic Construction of Big Semantic Data on Cloud  https://t.co/agpREMc5 Our paper to figure out  twitter user behavior and mood transitions will appear in #CIKM workshop https://t.co/QHMOF8gb Congrats @username 4th Workshop for Students on Innovation, Design & User Experience at #IIIT-H #TechEase2012 http://t.co/dF6KqPCc. Sep 22-24. We will have fun Indian CLEF/TREC: Forum for Information Retrieval Evaluation (FIRE) Workshop at Kolkata, India 17-19 Dec 2012. http://t.co/dHBuMlSf #FIRE ICSE2013 technical paper submissions are over. But other tracks SEE/SEIP/NIER are still open http://t.co/EdmMLiUs till Nov 2nd. Don't miss. long time dream of visiting Thiruvayur & Tanjavur for Thyagaraja Aradhana is coming true this year. Super excited but waitlisted on trains. Wonderful to see 2000+ runners in today's Hyderabad Marathon. Very inspiring. Electrifying envt at Finishing pt - Gachibowli Stadium. @username I wish, I did :)  not ready yet. Went there to cheer a few friends who came from Goa. May be next marathon ;) 10 Things to do in Hyderabad video. I do not agree with all of it. But information is better than no information :)  http://t.co/rOTkyr4C How good a proxy is Social media for opinions of ALL people? How to come up with a right measure? Well, important questions. Answers? @username Check the Hadoop ecosystem article on CloudStory.in  http://t.co/vDVvRviE Tomorrow's lecture in @username class will be by @username giving a big picture of Big Data Vendors - http://t.co/8ILslNsF Last date for submissions to #COLING2012 to be held in India for the first time at #IITB. http://t.co/MLbEZkcj Cheap Startup advertising advice - most popular blog post on http://t.co/55CwLViU  http://t.co/Fjmjqc5i All ears and eyes .. waiting to be impressed by Nokia WP8 phone(s). Show us an alternative. Nokia Lumia 920 did not disappoint. Very positive buzz and great specs. Many decisions will be made Sep 12th I guess. 19th Annual ITsAP Product award nominations are open. Last date: 31st Jan 2011. http://bit.ly/dIRkA4 Main Event 1-2 Mar'11 with AdvantageAP World Wide Web is the biggest and best digital library. #myDrona is the most efficient and friendly librarian. Check: http://t.co/2OFf0h6F "Bing It On!" Bing Goes Toe-to-Toe Against Google  http://t.co/mPc4XDCG Start-up lessons from Peter Thiel: If you build a product, will they (users) come?  http://t.co/x8blKZUD Why context is so important http://t.co/HTEjjieR via @username 29 UX/UI tips for start-ups  http://t.co/NAtQtNOr Congratulations to Mahathi, Search and IE Lab student at #IIIT-H getting an ACM-W scholarship for attendance at #CIKM 2012 I gave keynote at IBM Regional technical Exchange Conference this morning on improving Hadoop using ML. Old elephant adopts new elephant :) Finally, iPhone5 disappoints. New iPod touch is great. Today's best apple product is earphones. My verdict: Nokia 920 is THE phone. @username I agree. ‘Second Generation’ of Social Media Analytics Uses Both Machine Learning and Natural Language Processing http://t.co/AWRxYZUH It takes a lot of maturity and vision to accept competitor's strengths  and make a compelling offer to compliment them. #WinningFormula Your brand is the sum of conversations about it #Socialmedia #BigData #Marketing Cloud Search engine for 5 Indian languages was released yesterday in New Delhi. IIIT Hyderabad was part of the consortium  http://t.co/vzQN7QOk Check out IEEE conference on Cloud Computing for Emerging Markets  #CCEM register now & 10% discount for academics. http://t.co/SSfFcP9s @username Plz RT: Check out IEEE conference on Cloud Computing for Emerging Markets #CCEM 10% discount for academics. http://t.co/SSfFcP9s NLP tools for twitter data  including PoS tagging from @username 's group http://t.co/Mx3fGdFV Tomorrow's discussion in @username will be on cloud architectures in the context of #bigdata and challenges for nextGen cloud systems Done with my deck for 2moro's class @username and looking forward to discuss recent cloud #bigdata #socialrevolution from #DF12 event Illinois Natural Language Processing suite of tools are available with an NLP pipeline management system  http://t.co/EUDuYOtF Where Sentiment Analysis Heads Next http://t.co/0N0mTxJh via @username Workshop on Social Computing at IITKGP Oct 5-6. Entry by Invitation only. Some interesting issues up for discussion.  http://t.co/ZCQNpylI "NOSQL data store" guest lecture by Vivek of Pramati in today's cloud computing class.learnt about new things - Mongo, cassandra & Dynamo. I will be giving a talk on "Cloud Computing - A Research Perspective" at ASCI (Admin Staff College of India) for JNTU faculty on 24 SEP 10 "The elevator to success is out of order. You'll have to use the stairs...one step at a time" Joe Girard #ExperiencePillOfTheDay @username @username 65% accuracy at tweet level sounds good. Is that state of the art? What is the best reported and verified accuracy nbr? How some ground breaking research papers were rejected caused by reviewer having a bad day - interesting read  http://t.co/6CvYR6Vm Read this nice quote today (reportedly said by Bryan Dyson, a former CEO of Coco cola): "Value has a value only if its value is valued" "The people who are making product decisions also understand all business tradeoffs" Gyan from Mark Zuckerberg at Startup School 2011 Done with my talk at WOSC on "Computing Brand Reputation in Social Media" elite audience and lively discussions. http://t.co/ZCQNpylI @username thank you. Happy to note the common interests. 