@username @username yes. so brilliantly disruptive to the frame of the whole stupid "debate". @username so banal, so thin, so not life affirming. So familiar. Don't know how I feel about the bus driver loudly congratulating girls for having "lovely smiles" as they get on the bus. Actually, I do. @username he is of that ilk. @username yup. He's skeevy as. @username who knows. There may be more than one. Reminds me of Wolf Creek a lot. #headonastick @username nearly time to say goodbye to cambridge? @username next, based on your 'friends'' mood @username much tears @username oh, devices already have moods too, don't they. recalcitrant, tired, stubborn, over-eager… MT @username "mood sensing can build a…digital ecosystem as devices automatically share their [users'] moods" http://t.co/DTYNqwtVsg Special issue of Theory, Culture & Society on The Social Life of Methods http://t.co/NbYqYAgIaV The robots are coming http://t.co/UXMymhNCS0 Is this a thing Y/N (I suspect N) RT @username: YouTube Co-Founders Unleash New Video App MixBit http://t.co/H3UbUBsZUE (! @username ) @username who's done what now Oh dear. #anyolddebatehashtag I was bored watching the debate so I thought I'd see what was happening on Twitter AM I SOME KIND OF IDIOT New article by José van Dijck & and Thomas Poell, “Understanding Social Media Logic", Media and Communication http://t.co/2dITGyVbr3 Our new Capacity Building Professor in Digital Media @username - inaugural address http://t.co/PqmzAuosFt @username my pleasure :) FIRST THE PAVLOVA NOW THIS via @username: New Zealand legalized same-sex marriage at 8:30 this morning http://t.co/ywFGkJ9zvZ New post at the @username blog: What We're Reading, August Edition http://t.co/Kvr6sKybcO ‘What’s On Your Mind?’ Writing On Facebook As A Tool For Self-Formation  http://t.co/CS3yuRQHCQ New post at the @username blog: “Football Fandom In The Brazilian Twitterland” by @username http://t.co/eMoTZAHKKQ @username neurobusiness, on the other hand, has 'more than 10 years' until plateau. @username giving advice JOB: ARC Research Fellow, Level B, working at UQ's CCCS with Gay Hawkins on the sociology of plastic packaging http://t.co/jq4uk4eWcX @username you betcha @username @username you know you can't help yourself ben I'm at that that other uni near the river for Mike Michael's Engaging the Public: Science, Technology and the Politics of Participation Ooh this is giving me project ideas. Must stop having new project ideas. @username or asleep. That might be quite helpful actually. Yeah maybe #awesome @username: #Awesome! The first ever film made entirely of #Vines http://t.co/iBYfaKZ5Ig (ping @username) @username good to see your compliance with the "always shoot middle aged ladies from above" rule. @username ...said the fortune cookie WHY DID NOBODY CONSULT ME ABOUT THIS @username The Dancing Bean Espresso Bar http://t.co/oYim53EYj5 Harnessing ‘generative friction’: can conflict actually improve quality in open systems? http://t.co/LL5wsb73o4 @username at @username blog I do not believe in God, and I am bored with atheism. http://t.co/hLpHqCRFeQ - thx @username @username YOU ARE RIGHT ANNE *hugs* @username @username @username too busy counting, not while sitting at the table obv @username mmm hmmmm *cough* @username G'day! Thank you for your email. Please choose from the following auto-replies: 1 "Looks great to me", 2 "Sorry", 3 "No". @username thanks Darryl! @username thanks Rowan Wanna complete your world-class PhD in media & communication, creative practice or design at QUT & get paid for it? http://t.co/aJJjr7kz5x @username love youse too @username ? It is? @username  I feel this. @username @username first even slightly rainy day in ages today. Loving that but otherwise yeah nah Yes I am aware I am just amplifying @username's #trollrage but why not it's lunchtime and it's spring and the world is ending. First open access issue of AJC, "Talking About Disasters", with articles on #eqnz, #qldfloods etc. http://t.co/6mZmKopPXU @username AFFECT SCHOLARS THAT'S WHO Journal of Material Culture special issue on Imaging Digital Lives feat. me & @username on photography & storytelling http://t.co/gBKXpRyapy @username @username thanks Rowan! @username based on a symposium held at UQ - was a very good day because there was materialism in media studies before STS or software studies or media archeology… http://t.co/vweSf1BCBe Abbott has run "a 'disciplined' campaign that placed his electoral interests over the interests of the electorate." http://t.co/0Ud9ofuw2f Preach, Raymond Williams aka my homie Raymond Williams. http://t.co/CKjhGGRP1i Have a nice weekend Australian voters! We who are about to be defunded salute you! @username I think that typeface is before my time BTW @username @username more speculation than investigation so far. @username & I will have more on this from interviews, someday. Good morning Australia! Welcome to the first day of the rest of @username  @username  [no spoilers but that shift may be of more interest to researchers than other people] People cutting in line in the voting queue presumably because there's important shopping to do. Better get used to it, since no society. NO SERVICE AT THE SAUSAGE SIZZLE HOW COULD THIS DAY GET WORSE http://t.co/q3joObDTzy @username Albany Ck Anglican. Well stocked cake stall though and they *are* cooking the sausages. I CAN SMELL THEM Where is the $103 m cut in ARC funding going to come from? Can't wait to find out. @username Futures or Centres - or FOR20 ;) @username oh you're right I forgot I'd heard that. That would be good - it's done its job but do we really need one in 2015? Doubtful. Wow @username: Fraternal group, The Improved Order of Redmen. Whites only. http://t.co/1mHomnPib9 http://t.co/wLMj6jbHA6 I note that the social media companies (FB, Twitter) are themselves releasing plenty of election analytics. Big shift since 2010. @username it would not only save the ARC money but huge expense for universities. I don't think there'd be huge protest. @username oh right. Yeah I guess we wait (probably after a freeze) to find out @username what's your guess? @username @username @username @username @username @username what are we a list of? @username ah well I am one of those, it's true Upcoming @username seminar feat @username & @username - Emerging Challenges in Digital Media Research  http://t.co/ryztTyAiDy Remember that the standard you walk past is the standard you accept, and share that meme! http://t.co/h4OPMhMt1s @username @username cool! one question: how does one decide the gender of an English phrase? @username Der Computational Turn ;) @username I love linguistics. @username @username @username absolutement! (That's French, right?) @username @username @username let us now turn to the subject of English vs German pronunciations of the word "produsage". Oh Apple. @username @username ok I didn't say "let's have German humour". Twitter files for IPO earlier than expected http://t.co/kJGmqbI5Eb Wow, YouTube, you're advertising Schoolies Week to me? You've harnessed the power of BIG DATA to pinpoint my identity EXACTLY. “"What happened to me pales in comparison to what’s happening to women online today," Sierra said.” http://t.co/79ZL6NcUfZ "Hindsight can give you insights about what went wrong. But only faith, reason and bravery can propel you forward." http://t.co/7j1vpyYmYF At least it's raining Call for PhD applications from the QUT Social Media Research Group - come play with us! @username http://t.co/aaTeGMlO6U @username keep your eyes peeled but nothing right now... @username MERGE AND CONQUER ;) Why is Harvest Festival cancelled? I was looking forward to that :( SAD FACES Happy @username everyone! Off to New Farm Park shortly to celebrate  rainbow families, fierce gender outlaws and puppy dogs. @username @username @username yeah you could sort of do it with frequently used words lists, or even cleverer corpus linguistics trickery @username @username @username exactly Do yourself a favour: @username is looking for a few good PhD students to push the boundaries of design research http://t.co/8AV3edlfhS Good advice from @username - start thinking about the book while writing the findings & conclusion of the thesis. http://t.co/VQBy0GJnFS @username where/when is/was this? 