@username i will never forget her either. She was so sweet! Thanks for let us met her. She was so strong... Miss her Thank you babe, for everything. ? http://t.co/scoEJ5k8Bm @username "you must be the change you want to see in the world" Cookie dough >>>>>>>>> RT "@username: Call me rude but this had to be said http://t.co/xdSgA7Io6U" preach" THIS. Cookie dough. YAY! ?????????? http://t.co/o9QGHlV5t2 “@username: @username @username GALLETAAAAAAAAAAS! http://t.co/0som0PS6Dd” awwww es amor ???? First day of University. ???????? “@username: Love you, thanks babys @username @username” you're welcome babe! @username happy birthday to you, happy birthday to youuu, happy birthday dear Noelia! Happy birthday to youuuu! I love you sist! ?????????????????? @username hi, i know it's been a while; i don't even know if you remember me, i just want to know if everything is alright. Kik me pls @username me too ?? I'm a fucking idiot. Almost is never enough. @username Palau Sant Jordi, Barcelona http://t.co/m5qEJCvsWu The Notebook ???? @username Jack! If I don't answer you on kik it's because my iPhone is being repaired.. On monday I'll have it back! talk to u then :) you're all that matters to me.. ain't worry about nobody else If it ain't you, I ain't myself You make… http://t.co/AC5Rg9P6jZ @username don't listen to what they think about u today. You were amazing yesterday, you're amazing today and you'll be amazing forever. Oreo cupcake for breakfast #yummy #oreo #cupcake http://t.co/9PrXbiXeqh Catch me. Three more days of class. Just three days and I'll be free! A promise that will last forever. I love you, lil sist. @username Palau Sant Jordi, Barcelona http://t.co/6AyZTRbiXr “@username: Is everyone vegan right now except for me? lol” me neither lol “@username: Explains alot tbh http://t.co/mk98bTsGxR” that's me ._. Happy birthday, @username from Spain! Enjoy your day!!! Love you, benzo ???? Today, I went to the cinema to watch Believe movie, and I still can't understand why people hate on… http://t.co/1JcRdavpke Hope y'all have a nice Christmas!!!! ???????? @username take the time you need... You deserved, but you have to promise us that you'll come back... We need you, you saved us Congrats to @username and the whole team; #BelieveMovie is perfect ???? http://t.co/xVC2KTUUKn There's nothing like us, there's nothing like you and me, together through the storm. http://t.co/nlN85v8Dpd Oh men... I hate this so much. Damn Obsessed with Honeymoon Avenue!! My new favorite song lol proud of you @username ???? Dear 2014, be good, please. @username Platja Cubelles http://t.co/xtSYV9QonC New Year's Eve was perf. ???? “@username: This deserves endless retweets. http://t.co/HDiIKf5y3Z” wow “@username: Quote this with your lock screen” :) http://t.co/0c3wZd2lfi @username i should do that too haha Here comes the sun ?????? @username so true! Guys, Spain is not that cool... “@username: when you go on someone's profile and you see they're not following you anymore http://t.co/187BYoHfsT” omfg haha exactly!:') “@username: THE WAY HE WALKS. DAMN https://t.co/I754M7PCaq” "bitch pls, I'm Justin Bieber" lol “@username: Hey hey its my birthday!” Happy Birthday Scrappy!!!!! Enjoy your day! ???? @username i have the same problem.. ???? First day driving!!!! Yay?? “@username: quote this with your lockscreen, idk why just do it im curious” http://t.co/blTzpqoAK4 I don't want to do my homework... @username sho shoro celiens ???? @username @username this picture is from Barcelona... I know it, 'cause I was there :/ @username okay... I was saying it to you in case you wanted to know it... Sorry if I offended you ???? ???? @username People MakeUp http://t.co/F3vQo39P6w Time to relax and read ?????? #TheFaultInOurStars #JohnGreen http://t.co/FxE7x86hZK Friday night with my girls ?????? #selfie #kebab #durum #salsablanca #gemma @username Cubelles http://t.co/y3WjQLowGF Welcome home!!!!!! ???????? #MiniMe #firstcar @username Platja Cubelles http://t.co/23uQO7XW2A Happy birthday Travis Maddox ???????? @username babyyyyy ???????? @username in da house ???? http://t.co/thPkYLFQyF Guess who can drive now? Yuuuuuuuuuuuup, ME. Happy siblings day to my little sister! I'm so proud of you baby girl. Love you to the moon and back ????… http://t.co/ehlPbE2yhR HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO THIS WONDERFUL GIRL!!!!! My best friend, my sister, the shoulder where I cry...… http://t.co/WUcQTW60xx Get fit for the summer with no exercise,I'm down 10 pounds! http://t.co/MVeG4a8Y96 @username i was reading Divergent yesterday ???????????? In the rose garden Where the rain is falling And the thorns are sharpened Rose garden, yeah Rose… http://t.co/o152w4tv6B On Wednesday we wear pink! #meangirls ???????????????? @username Passeig De Gràcia http://t.co/9YjGa6ltyT @username me tooooo; can't wait ???? “@username: That awkward moment. #TFIOS #Divergent http://t.co/IK6LKBbO9o” @username @username I already watched it 2 times on the cinema lol @username happy birthday to you, happy bday to you? Happy bday dear Brooke, happy birthday to yoooouuuu ?????? have a nice day ???? #StudyHard #German @username Horchateria SIRVENT http://t.co/e2UJTdr0wh From @username and me to @username; you guys deserve an A++ for your amazing project! You rock! ?????????????????? Look at me now, I'm falling I can't even talk, still stuttering This ground of mine keeps shaking Oh… http://t.co/mYGAHESyWw “@username: IDKNDMDKKDKDKS http://t.co/93BsuVrAHT” i want to go ???? but we don't have it in Spain yet ???????? We fucking need this perfect movie in Spain like RIGHT NOW!!!! @username http://t.co/DrbeCt5FZ4 On that 2014 bikini diet ???????? http://t.co/AMabT0zBO1 Re-reading #Divergent http://t.co/mj8mUgSOcf A relaxing cup of Café con leche in Plaza Mayor. http://t.co/9oKYvXK2JV @username you don't even kmow how long I've been waiting to see you! Thank you for the concert in… http://t.co/lqOsB0RGJo Happy birthday to you, happy birthday to you, happy birthday dear charleno!!!!!!! HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO… http://t.co/xyaxX0v8Wd “I’m gonna treat you so nice, you’re never gonna let me go.” - Vivian (Julia Roberts ????) http://t.co/OC2H2e1yX7 Studying (v): A term used in reference to doing school work. it also ends in the word "dying", and… http://t.co/n8y7hHX0hD Puppy Owen ???????? @username Cubelles http://t.co/pUrFZGO24r 