#67 - Fishes in face. (Courtesy of B. Del Nero) - Pesci in faccia http://t.co/uJ1nGeUc #68 - Do I have written giocondo on the forehead? (Courtesy of M. Zampollo) - Ho scritto giocondo in fronte? http://t.co/4LzqDaZF #69 - Who borns rounded, does not die squared. (Courtesy of P. Bilotti Feat. R. Rotti) - Chi nasce tondo, non… http://t.co/Fbf72EZf #70 - You have served that to me on a silver tea tray. - Me l'hai servita su un piatto d'argento http://t.co/9ck5eSuE #71 - On time like taxes. (Courtesy of P. Bilotti) - Puntuale come le tasse http://t.co/vNDJsfow #72 - At the evening lions, at the morning assholes. - Alla sera leoni, alla mattina coglioni http://t.co/p57muDHq #75 - You don't know never. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Non si sa mai http://t.co/SPcPcFOC #76 - Wispy is the leaf, long is the way, say the yours than I say the mine. (Courtesy of. B. Del Nero) - Stretta è… http://t.co/mTPAndZp #77 - Send everything at bitches. (Courtesy of L. Rimoldi) - Mandare tutto a puttane http://t.co/4MKyGhQE #78 - I'm not like they paint me. - Non sono come mi dipingono http://t.co/VIpSRGP3 #80 - Bread of gold. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Pandoro http://t.co/ogicOsLS #81 - Give to Cesare what is Cesare's. (Courtesy of M. Zampollo) - Dare a Cesare quel che è di Cesare http://t.co/iKoU6Y0w #83 - I've made the eye over it. - Ci ho fatto su l'occhio http://t.co/iy73f3cU #85 - One thing pull the other. (Courtesy of B. Del Nero) - Una cosa tira l'altra http://t.co/WfjFDA3o #87 - Dog who barks doesn't bite. - Can che abbaia non morde http://t.co/W3ORZL8x #88 - The occasion makes the man thief. - L'occasione rende l'uomo ladro http://t.co/6J9ZTp2N #89 - The truth naked and uncooked. - La verità nuda e cruda http://t.co/7umIHEiE #90 - Neither head nor tail. - Né capo né coda http://t.co/Te2gHlNy #91 - The morning has the gold in mouth. - Il mattino ha l'oro in bocca http://t.co/8ZFfSK8u #93 - You're looking at the hair. (Courtesy of M. Paravicini) - Stai a guardare il capello http://t.co/sIhmz6FS I just unlocked the "Shutterbug" badge on @username for adding photos to my check-ins. Say cheese! http://t.co/nWSedhh9 I just ousted @username as the mayor of Done! on @username! http://t.co/jusHxKlk #94 - The epiphany all the parties brings away. - L'epifania tutte le feste porta via http://t.co/CUl0lmrw #95 - Don't put the finger in the lesion. - Non mettere il dito nella piaga http://t.co/6ZrW269c #97 - That God scrimps and sets free to us. - Che Dio ce ne scampi e liberi http://t.co/RCKsQjVI #98 - Who makes it waits it. - Chi la fa l'aspetti http://t.co/UUmJAY9t #99 - The counts return. - I conti tornano http://t.co/Cs6T50Wa #100 - The tastes are not questionable. (Special edition celebrating the 100th post) - De gustibus non disput… http://t.co/L2YYIZvf I just unlocked the "Trainspotter" badge on @username for checking in at trains and subway stations! http://t.co/Zium66ql #102 - It have made me species. - Mi ha fatto specie http://t.co/duBJU8rr I just became the mayor of Done! Digital on @username! http://t.co/VEsttKH0 #103 - With a lot of hat. (Courtesy of S. Spreafico) - Con tanto di cappello http://t.co/j4dXxaDu #104 - The life is made of stairs. There is who goes up, and who goes down. - La vita è fatta a scale. C'è ch… http://t.co/P366ELnr #105 - Who breaks pays. - Chi rompe paga http://t.co/azTjJ5Tm #109 - You have pissed out of the vase. - Hai pisciato fuori dal vaso http://t.co/h7oYvgeD #110 - Who is cause of his bad, cry himself. - Chi è causa del suo mal pianga sé stesso http://t.co/5NoFcbiZ #112 - Idem with potatoes. - Idem con patate http://t.co/6FHj2f0b #113 - He saved himself for the broken of the headset. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Si è salvato per il rot… http://t.co/wAEzkAly #114 - At range of hand. - A portata di mano http://t.co/kRm3nFVP #115 - Sbank the moonary. - Sbancare il lunario http://t.co/shKpXlc2 #117 - Maria's daughters are the first that give it away. (Courtesy of M. Engolli) - Le figlie di Maria son l… http://t.co/M63rqo0c #119 - And now, at we two. - E ora, a noi due. http://t.co/PgYq5GHU #120 - Nownever. - Oramai http://t.co/4wBbtg0p #122 - You are saved in corner. - Ti sei salvato in corner http://t.co/739616kw #123 - Paper sings. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Carta canta http://t.co/c3sggezW #124 - Rechaptering. - Ricapitolando http://t.co/nji9KkEv #125 - If it's not soap, it's wet bread. (Courtesy of M. Engolli) - Se non è zuppa è pan bagnato http://t.co/w873AQFs #127 - It always rain on the wet. (Courtesy of M. Engolli) - Piove sempre sul bagnato http://t.co/e6YW9bHf #128 - From which pulpit! - Da qual pulpito! http://t.co/1zUhI8k5 #129 - Bad weed never dies. (Courtesy of L. Rimoldi) - L'erba cattiva non muore mai http://t.co/6FpC36AV #130 - Jokes at part. - Scherzi a parte http://t.co/BAYjPJMI #131 - Dead a Pope, another is made. - Morto un Papa, se ne fa un altro http://t.co/B3lH2ePN #133 - Bankbroken. (Courtesy of A. Catelletti) - Bancarotta http://t.co/22oGWlps #134 - But do me the pleasure! (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Ma mi faccia il piacere http://t.co/6EZpiRKm #135 - Package thrower. - Tirapacchi http://t.co/K4jTVFwA #139 - There would lack other! (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Ci mancherebbe altro! http://t.co/l3DamgtcuZ #140 - The want-weed does not grow even in the garden of the king. (Courtesy of L. Rimoldi) - L’erba voglio... http://t.co/fdcW1L5qr8 #143 - But close the beak! - Ma chiudi il becco! http://t.co/VmgOPaf6S4 #144 - Cabbage at tea break. (Courtesy of M. Alcano) - Cavoli a merenda http://t.co/tdPdsNXQK9 #145 - With the sense of after. - Col senno di poi http://t.co/MWlpISdJKM #146 - Nothing of that. - Niente di che http://t.co/UXXFKUJW04 #149 - “In the mouth of the wolf”, “Die!” (Feat. P. Bilotti) - “In bocca al lupo”, “Crepi!” http://t.co/6xXJkwzzHO #150 - The die is drawn. (Special Edition celebrating the 150th post) - Il dado è tratto http://t.co/W7pSiUUUqB #151 - That to say is wanted.  - Che a dir si voglia http://t.co/PVR5ZWEgbU #153 - He puts his hands ahead. - Ha messo le mani avanti http://t.co/sk78f7ap50 #155 - Smiling & Joking. (Courtesy of S. M. Summo) - Ridendo e scherzando http://t.co/1AUkZEA7ay #156 - Of point to white.  - Di punto in bianco http://t.co/u9aVNsJA9b #157 - He owled it to me. (Courtesy of S. Spreafico) - Me l’ha gufata http://t.co/WbKhmDXz62 #158 - Nothing of new. (Feat. A. Castelletti) - Niente di nuovo http://t.co/tPz4s7AJkM #159 - As God commands. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Come Dio comanda http://t.co/6X50bGAX2k #163 - Sayery. (Courtesy of C. Galeazzi) - Diceria http://t.co/eqqn27lzYw #164 - The rave and the fave. (Courtesy of C. Galeazzi) - La rava e la fava http://t.co/qSK8w3eTRH #167 - Comfort of use. - Comodato d’uso http://t.co/8f6gAjV5Bb #168 - A moment of chin catcher. (Courtesy of D. Annbjer) - Un momento di raccoglimento http://t.co/SlNfspsHkY #169 - A swallow not does spring. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Una rondine non fa primavera http://t.co/CweZFLmxDG #170 - With the hands in hand. - Con le mani in mano http://t.co/tkGt9xBgGG #171 - You make me come the milk at the knees. (Courtesy of M. Alcano) - Mi fai venire il latte alle... http://t.co/wMvomQu4pN #172 - Gives some airs. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Darsi delle arie http://t.co/wltKnaqlv6 pre-easter meeting http://t.co/a39U7SBGRQ #173 - To eye and cross. (Courtesy of M. Alcano and L. RImoldi) - A occhio e croce http://t.co/zsr4M86UDh #174 - He threw the sponge. - Ha gettato la spugna http://t.co/o3VUr6gVsd #175 - But are you daddy? (Courtesy of T. Yo) - Ma sei babbo? http://t.co/OQsLiiWHcC #177 - It doesn’t make a fold. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Non fa una piega http://t.co/pJgtiCzxs1 #178 - You’re breaking down a open door. (Courtesy of S. Spreafico) - Stai sfondando una porta aperta http://t.co/BM3Q4uZhLN #179 - I me coffee bad. (Courtesy of S. Spreafico) - Mi sono espresso male http://t.co/3o3edwRL72 #180 - But are you played?! (Courtesy of S. Spreafico) - Ma sei suonato?! http://t.co/E4UJbZBBRQ #181 - Thanks the same. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Grazie lo stesso http://t.co/bym0VLQBNK #182 - NSFW Squirting (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Schizzinoso http://t.co/eF2e63WYb4 #184 - All the world is country. - Tutto il mondo è paese http://t.co/abzuTq8K97 #185 - Said clear and rounded.  - Detto chiaro e tondo http://t.co/wBszuHLa3M #186 - I have the tiny water in the mouth. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Ho l’acquolina in bocca http://t.co/rnBP5MUVDn #189 - Put your self in my clothes. - Mettiti nei miei panni http://t.co/pEPPv9I5bs #190 - Giant salt of mobile. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Salone del mobile http://t.co/hOzeF9sC7r #191 - Nobody to us runs back. - Nessuno ci corre dietro http://t.co/cEXWLYP3zZ #192 - The dish cries. (Courtesy of M. Alcano) - Il piatto piange http://t.co/3rKrBqzkXr #193 - What the convent passes. - Quel che passo il convento http://t.co/s5M38chocX Where the sun doesn’t beat. (Courtesy of T. Yo) - Dove non batte il sole http://t.co/LAoKE1q1MS #199 - Deargeeses. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Karaoke http://t.co/jSfDpoafQW #200 - Verb flies, write lies.  (Special edition celebrating the 200th post) - Verba volant, scripta manent http://t.co/BDUnJvtAqQ #201 - They leave the weather they find.  - Lasciano il tempo che trovano http://t.co/aaqIwqaYqI 