@username let's make some mother fucking memories. Sore, nauseous, grumpy, achy, and exhausted #signsofanawesomeweekend :) First run in a week #hurtssogood My closet will be so embarrassing if sequins ever go out of style Thinking of @username :) Dance party with three-year-olds! #ilovemyjob #whendidlifegetsogood?  :) :) @username you're suppose to hashtag when you tweet! i want my phone back i want my phone back i want my phone back i want my phone back i want my phone back i want my phone back Oh man. Tonight went SO MUCH BETTER than I had expected #mayregretthisinthemorning #dontcare :) :) coffee, lovin, sleeping in. i'm so set to have the best day ever  #goooooooooodmood :) tanning! nails! shoe shopping! aoii! i love being a girl! I'm at #aoii for 12 hours just thinking of all the things I could be getting done,but I finally get home & forget my whole list! #lifeishard My temporary flip phone could've only been cool circa 2006. Also, it doesn't vibrate, it growls at me. #appreciatingmyoldphone @username seriously, it sounds like a caged animal. it's not even a short growl its a long, intimidating one @username chyeah well all i can do is hope NO ONE wants to text me haha :) Open-house round is for heartbreak :( @username no we had to rush girls that didn't even meet our gpa requirement so i liked 2 girls a lot that won't even be invited back @username you're so pumped about moving here and you know it! :) You know you're comfortable with someone when you whisper an entire 20 minute conversation & neither of you notice #1amconvos @username my roommate just walked me to my room and hugged me goodnight #hezbians #1am @username i can hear your iphone ring when i tag you in a tweet #beingobnoxiousnow @username whore. #stumbleupon just took me to three websites that list great breakup songs.... way to be, like, a month late haha #wtf A week of hard work will finally pay off today #bidday #AOIIrush2011 :) Seriously? BEST DAY EVER #newmembers #bbq #waterfight #zetalove :) @username I left my WALL-E at work remember?! This week, for sure. :) I can't tell if it's a cold, sinuses or allergies. I'll just take a bunch of meds and see what happens... #wantmyvoiceback #feelingshitty I ended up only keeping anything related to tanning and an Obama button #bigredwelcome #whatawaste #BarbieGirl came on the radio on my way to class. #thisisagoodsign :) Nothing, NOTHING is more irritating than when people go through the speedy check-out line with more than 20 items. Pretentious assholes. "Boring doesn't win nationals." @username Oreo jello, Dirty Dancing, Slut t-shirts. You know, #girlstuff i think people over-think lady gaga. they're like, who is she suppose to be? it's no one. she's just being.. a dumbass. -@username Narrowly avoided a speeding ticket from a speedtrap bc a stranger yelled "SLOW DOWN" as I drove by #seeingthegoodinpeople :) :) 3 hours of practicum, 2 hours of class, 4 hours of work. Fuuccckkkk Tuueessddaayyyss. PASSED THE PPST waddupppp #icandoanythinghungoverrr :) @username no i just want to speak and understand spanish really really really badly. i'm trying to immerse myself in the culture @username well we have extra wine if you'd like to move to nebraska and teach us spanish! :) @username don't be creepy. just watch our video @username calling yourself daddy is one of the creepiest things a guy can do. you might as well perm your chest hair and show it off I have a new grandpa. His name is Sebastian and he is 110% Italian. :) @username but then he'd wink and call me sweetie and it would be ok. then he'd get some figs :) Interviewing University Ambassador hopefuls. It's kind of like rushing, but better #keeptryingtoimpressme #ilovebeingintimidating you know what i hate? boys who think they're SO COOL but really they're SO NOT. #getselfesteem seriously stressed out i want to date @username. he's mean but cute and funny everyone is GONE #labordayweekendsucks slow changing of seasons= kelsie not feeling good, again.  can i catch a break and feel healthy for more than 2 weeks at a time? 7am walk in 44 degree weather, white mocha coffee, and this song http://t.co/EJ2x2fv :) #ohhellogoodday I look straight up hippie right now #wavyhair #feathers #bohotop I'M IN SUCH A WEIRD MOOOOOOD #TOOMUCHCOFFEE book of mormon. the entire play. on youtube........ #notstudying #queesespanol IM IN AN OK MOOD SO IM GOING TO GO TO WALMART AND SPEND ALL MY MONEY WITH MY BEST FRIEND BECAUSE IM SUPER NEUTRAL LA LA LA. I...rode a mechanical bull. #ropeemnrideem #perfectnight #zetalove :) :) :) IM SO PUMPED ABOUT MY PERSUADDEEEEEE #workweekend so not feeling it today. my persuade can write itself. #workweekend BackstreetBoys+Vanessa Carlton+Baha Men= girl night full of quality jam sessions with @username and Rachel :) man i'd kill for some juice stop right now I love running so much. It makes the stress in life seem more manageable I WANT TO FIND MY OLD XANGA #nostalgia FOUND MY XANGA OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG OMG i was such a loser when i was 15 Running at night is so convenient for me. No one can see me mouthing the words to songs and fist pumping Didn't check the schedule so I went into work today on my day off... and stayed. #fml #pushover Waste of time round 2. or 3... or 4, or 5. Spent 5 hours sitting on my couch tonight writing that fucking speech #suckadickpersude #ruffdraft @username 's prose is amazing :) Buzz Ouch! the bee stug my on the lage. And it was in the spring. #1stgradekelsie If I were a butterfly I wud fly around, and I mite land on peoples noses. #1stgradekelsie Homework is hard so hard that I wish I get a hole week to finsh it! #1stgradekelsie Mothers are nice when thay get you pop, candy, beny babys and maby a cat or a dog! and let you make a house out of candy #1stgradekelsie WHY CAN'T I WATCH GLEE #whathappenedtoyouhulu #youusedtobecool Vampire Diaries with Rachel? uhhh sure ok #notthatbad :) On this day 3 years ago, I was dressed up like a nun. #MercyDay #howtimechangesyou 3 hours of work. 7 hours of babysitting.#HHH left.... #headsgoingtoexplode #HungryHungryHuskers was a blast :) I'M NEVER NOT COMPETING FOR A WEEKEND AGAIN I'M #SOOOOLONELY I WANT MY SPEECH FAMILY BACK RIGHT NOW :( :( :( Got to spend time with ALL of my second family for Mon's birthday #lovemypflugs #greatday :) i hate unnecessarily awkward situations. if you pretent that it's not awkward, then the situation is significantly more comfortable. @username HAHAHHAHA IM SO SORRY it wasn't about you I promise!!! wake me up when october ends suck my dick persuade @username RT: "When I die, I'm haunting the FUCK out of people" ahahaha Reece you're the best! I HOPE @username COMES TO THE TEAM ROOM BEFORE 10:30 #hinthint #winkwink #necesitoayuda Listening to The Lion King soundtrack to start my day off right #canyoufeelthelovetonight? #hellyesican "Don't do drug" presentations used to scare the shit out of me. Now they just remind me of how awesome and successful I am What's a sorority girl to do when the #togaparty just got cancelled? #SGP #homaha with my sister :) @username I'M LEAVING NOW YOU'RE SUCH A WHORE STOP TWEETING ABOUT ME Just ROYGBIVed and finger-spaced my closet #obsessed @username I don't have your number! I'm going to Spain this summer, I'm going to Spain this summer, I'm going to Spain this summer and I really really really CAN'T WAIT :) I'd like to time my speech but some random guy is hovering over me in the hallway....... #unsureofwhattodo Worst/ best day ever. Also, 12 hours in tights and a skirt make me want to wear yoga pants and cotton tees for the rest of my life Supporting some awesome boys at a flag football game with Rachel :) @username @username @username I didn't have time to visit anyway! #perfect I left my house when it was dark and I came home when it was dark #14hourdays #depressed #ihatemylife #iswinterbreaksoon? Akon's #Lonely has been and will be on repeat for the next four days #missmyfamily :( #nottravelingblues :( #pityparty :( Stop tweeting about Chicago!!!! #jealousy Saturday goals: DON'T sleep in til 1pm. Spend 3 hours doing absolutely nothing. Get fucking cute for work. Wear many hats. :) Spending all day with Kay :) 