RT @username: RT @username: #MalditaEstrenaEnDel40al1 #LaRespuestaNoEsLaHuida TORTUGAS ¡QUE TENEMOS DOS TT's! http://t.co/gnXieXFx @username No... "Http/1.1 Service Unavailable" :D RT @username: QUE ATENTAS ESTABAN MIS TORTUGUITAS A @username @username @username @username @username http://t.co/sHb4sAiI Thanks! RT @username: Second #linktostartAW12 award goes to @username ... #viernesplaceband RT @username: Con todos ustedes: 'Oh, oui oui'! iTunes: https://t.co/rYvldFjyPT Spotify: http://t.co/hKfkl2Sw2D Practicamos el happy working. :) RT @username: Vamos, con alegría!! @username #work http://t.co/hXjW3fZiuc @username @username Thanks! :) @username Thanks! @username @username @username @username @username @username @username @username Placeband! http://t.co/vmTWL7aEiq #Top5 placeband: 1.@username 2.@username 3.@username 4.@username 5.@username  http://t.co/66zSDnBYbe ¡¿Conciertos ilimitados por $25 al mes?! RT @username: Introducing Jukely #UnlimitedConcerts. Sign up for early access: http://t.co/5xND1ngBMV Good morning.  RT @username: Bruce Springsteen, 1975  http://t.co/1AonLC1Fr0 Oh yeah!  RT @username: Are You ready? #BSide http://t.co/7mrvzGquza @username @username @username Thanks! @username Happy birthday, @username! We look forward to seeing you in Madrid. http://t.co/9GpSZGrAqF #happybirthdayanastacia Music is in the air, everywhere I look around! Esta noche, @username, @username, @username y más en http://t.co/spjTSLFq4x. “The only film produced about The Doors... by The Doors”. A partir del 11 de noviembre.  Trailer -> https://t.co/i77G6IETpe  #música #cine 58 years ago, Elvis dazzled the crowd at the Mississippi-Alabama State Fair.  #ElRey http://t.co/VAqWjHuYW0 Thom Yorke presenta nuevo álbum, distribuido por BitTorrent.  "Tomorrow's Modern Boxes"  http://t.co/gycFEIs3AJ @username @username @username @username @username @username ¡Un honor! Morning! "@username: Kurt Cobain and C.Love bathroom selfie.In their hotel during Nirvana’s 1992 Japanese tour http://t.co/hz3JjAkYqw" 550 Artists. 10 Years. 1 Question: ¿LENNON or McCARTNEY?  https://t.co/58oP1RTIjx @username … For we're like creatures of the wind, and wild is the wind. #LoveMeLoveMeLoveMeLoveMe You say love is a temple, love a higher law. Love is a temple, love the higher law. You ask me to enter, but then you make me crawl.  #U2 "I've got life, I've got my freedom, I've got the life". http://t.co/aUaBmoFhIJ When the days they seem to fall through you, well just let them go. (Blur - The Universal) #BuenasNoches  https://t.co/hgQIuaXIK9 Pete Doherty graba el single ‘Flags Of The Old Regime’ como homenaje a la que fuera su amiga, Amy Winehouse.  https://t.co/kzuzoUJNzJ 