I really need to put my fucking head in the sand for a while. So long internet.. I can't believe the news today, I can't close my eyes and make it go away, how long.. how long must we sing this fucking song #bloodysunday @username  because of course everyone in gazaa did build these tunnels? Poor 4 year old kids, forced to digg instead of going to school. @username  assuming you know quite right how to discriminate between Right and wrong. Sorry I can't, all I see is river of blood. @username you mean like in 2002 when they offered a truce of 25 years? Or when the PLO recognized Israel and signed with Ytzahk Rabin? même si je dois vivre 10 000 ans je suis pas prêt d'oublier "wake up, wake up, I bought you a toy" .. j'hallucine ma race putain. how come recommendations from a low self confidence reviewer counts more than those from higher ones?  #emnlp2014 @username #emnlp2014 great they don't read authors responses too. @username actually from his review, he couldn't make the difference between semantic role labeling and graph-based predicate-argument parsing @username  Maybe. Or when one is not part of a known clique, entering is much harder. benefice of the doubt so to speak. @username  I've raised that issue at the #emnlp 2013 org. meeting and no one seemed to care. Anyway, next ACL will be in China.. 1/2 @username I hope they'll consider Russia, Azerbaidjan or North Korea next time. Why not after all? great venue, low human right zone http://t.co/Z34dOXdEZh disgusting. how about peace damn ass? @username @username Sorry, that was one guy from a well known antisemitic group, what i've seen was http://t.co/yS0ksesXzc @username @username or that one, read "Jews and Arabs United for Justice" please don't believe all FUD http://t.co/bIXNupit5d @username @username serioulsy? they're running to save their lives, they have no electricity, almost no water and they should tweet? @username like those who voted for  Nethaniayu or Lieberman who think it's ok to  kill children on a beach, hospital,  a school #STFU @username talking about humain shields when gaza is the most dense zone of the world is like talking about being wet when drowning at sea @username by the way, they were the ones forcing kids entering houses so they won't get trapped first http://t.co/y541dZpESz @username help? what help ? they've been in an open air prison for 7 years. Having no control on their lives whatsoever. 1/2 @username anyway, you're right, I'm wrong. Let's just hope that you'll kill them all in one bombing, at least they won't suffer anymore. @username of course, like this hasn't been testified by the Israelis refuzniks before. Don't forget to fuck yourself after they all die @username you're losing your nerves or what? calm yourself down, go jerk off on some beheaded little kids believing they asked for it. @username funny, you're talking about evidences now. Where the ones proving Hamas killed these 3 young kids and so Gaza deserved it all? @username what argument? We were having an argument? Here I was I thinking you were a lame asshole telling that those people asked for it @username while I was supposed to argue with you. I'm not arguing with someone who thinks that those people deserved their sad fate. @username yes, sure. right, how many people died during the search and rescue operation? How many blown up houses? how many prisoners? @username @username fair enough. @username exactly damn ass. they don't. So stop saying that they got what they deserved because 8 years ago 42.9% voted Hamas. @username How about those voting for the Israeli far right?  pfff, you don't even see you're going circular on your own argumentation... @username is that a joke? I feel like being in the  hidden camera...  I can't believe you wrote this without laughing your ass off @username democracy, only if they chose the right ones, right? go tell that to Bibi when he said he won't talk to  Abbas anymore @username and by the way, go fuck yourself deep hard with your lame insults, you're that close to a pity point it's pathetic Hoping for the emergence of the next Mandela instead of the next intifada. #callmenaive http://t.co/8n37K8EtDe @username @username Is there a translation of that reportage somewhere? it starts spreading fire on French twitter. @username @username  D'après le journaliste auteur du reportage, "it is absolutely not true. Social media got their translation wrong" @username @username @username  it was there before the demonstration.  Get your facts, check the vid. Shame nobody covered it though @username @username @username no, apparently it has been done during the night or the morning. Shame, I agree. @username @username @username  such a shame.it was supposed to be a peaceful sitting and now Salafist flags, staviskas and riots #FML @username @username this is the dumbest argument i've ever read. Because they're young men, they're by default terrorist or fighter? @username  come on. don't embarrass yourself with that  "let's kill them all. We'll check after that. or not." argument @username yes, sure. said who? @username I hope you, your little sister and your family will be safe. Take care. @username @username can't stop following her tweets, wondering if.. not too horrible, I won't tell it out loud. Courage Farah, courage.. @username  Sadly, the past should probably used here "she WAS live tweeting". I deeply hope I'm wrong. @username @username I can't believe you're talking like that to a terrified young girl. WTF for god's sake! @username Dear Dr, are you related to @username? is she ok? her little sis as well? @username @username  oh thank god!! Please tell her father and everyone we're praying for you all. Can we send money or medics? @username oh thank god!!! i'm so happy you made it! How is your sister and your family? @username @username I've never been that happy to be wrong. I'd love to continue to be so wrong 'til the end of the time to  be honest @username @username Exactly what I was thinking too. Hope there will be a happy ending for everyone from both sides #callmenaive @username whatever. @username @username @username @username @username @username @username Because as in many other arab countries, men stay outside at day 1/2 @username @username @username @username @username @username @username (sorry to interfere,just saw the numbers and translated the question) @username @username @username @username @username @username @username  actually, yes I would. Same for children's death rate being lower @username @username @username @username @username @username @username  it's not a matter of proportion, it's a matter of who is protectless @username @username because smbdy would be stupid enough to shoot a stinger from inside a house? @username @username I wish I could I say I know the feeling but I don't. it's tough though to go as far as empathizing with scared soldiers @username @username fucking hell, how far are you in the south ? I thought they were discussing another ceasefire.. @username @username  it wouldn't set the room on fire?  god, i've watched to  many stalingrad documentaries @username @username @username @username @username @username @username  Hi Yoav, because I try to follow "both sides", i'm a scientist 1/2 @username @username @username @username @username @username @username  so I use bing, google translate and all I can to try to understand @username @username @username @username @username @username @username how come there is such a damn gap between those two sides @username @username @username @username @username @username @username spent hours reading stuff on the Israeli official archive, haaretz.. @username @username @username Israel isn't one side either then cf. gideon levy's side vs likoud. Religious vs secular, etc. but less and less @username @username at leas they can give people so air, no? time to gather victims.. @username @username @username @username @username @username @username so, are you saying that the current death toll is exagerated? #hope? @username @username @username or by the IDF, a lone soldier being bored or a smbd genuinely scared by some guys coming close the no man's land @username @username @username sorry, was off trying to make an over excited baby go to bed (and stay there). @username @username @username Although I found this creapy at best, here's one list found from a non neutral source too http://t.co/QLh1LkbFU7 @username @username @username yeah, feel so hopelessly useless right now. being obsessed by live report, reading Saddate in Jerusalem, hoping. @username @username I will. I hope he'll have some time to follow @username @username @username @username  it is. I don't know how to cope with anything else right now. Being obsessed by what is happening. #peace @username me too, fucking hell.. not that it matters in absolute, but it hard to explain to coworkers who don't give a shit btw @username is that confirmed that whole tradegy in the play yard today? a hamas misfire? @username well, wether people care or not, they must pay attention to alerts and stuffs? @username what's PIJ ? Islamic Djihad? @username as I said it already, totally fucked up. @username  I once said in a paper that social media was a revolution because everyone could become a valuable source of information. so true @username too bad it's about a fucking surviving game nightmare @username ? why are you lying about @username? she created her twitter in march 2012, not conveniently 2 weeks ago? What do you imply? @username good luck, with all my care. @username @username @username  if that can make you sleep better, go ahead. @username @username Don't embarrass yourself: 1.8m in 40kmx10km, that's  4500 per km2 so, 4.5 per m2. 1/2 @username @username add the no go zone increase by 44%, that's about 10 people per square meter now. @username @username well, if that makes you sleep better, keep thinking they're evil and the other are good. Pffff. Following @username and losing all hope whatsoever.. @username @username @username @username sure. As opposed to when they were pogrommed in Europe for centuries while given asilum by musl. @username @username @username @username If you knew anything, you'd be able to make the difference between al-quaida wanabee and people. @username what? she died??  omfg.. @username hope there's no harm in the neighborhood. You live in the south? @username any news from @username? haven't heard from her in a while, I hope she's ok too. @username :) no need to. I hope this nightmare will be over soon. (still hoping for an happy ending though) @username @username Great !! btw, you'll be in Dublin next month, right? @username @username  ok, I'm glad you're ok.  I hope you guys will manage to get some money but Dublin can be very expensive (+ Coling fees) @username @username we managed to find cheap housing at Trinity via http://t.co/gPVD0zRcoZ (and yes I know you probably don't care right now) @username @username  come on dude, this hoax was debunked years ago. You can troll better, try again.. @username @username @username  like half of Gaza people, she was 8 years old. Keep insulting a young girl, you'll feel better @username @username so you needed to insult a little girl scared to death instead of taking 2mn to get some facts straight? @username @username @username she deserves to live in a free country, not in an open air prison. She deserves to live her life. 