Babylon Zoo's 'Spaceman' on @username brings me right back to the nineties #vandejaren90 so romantic :) Physicist Boyfriend Proposes To Physicist Girlfriend With Academic Paper http://t.co/qFXc3NgyOe via @username BBC News - Alzheimer's blood test could give early diagnosis http://t.co/ruCi3OkRAy @username oh no I wasn't there! "Opening up Scientific Data", launch of the Research Data Alliance http://t.co/xdIfoa1wwq The evolution of our spines and speech - The Oatmeal http://t.co/GjPk37GaYW via @username @username I guess I got the same message :) some guy going on about alphabetic phonetic writing? @username creepy... What's Wrong With the Scientific Method? | Wired Science | http://t.co/7nFg8RtJPT http://t.co/mwgc6naAqq This is so cool! -- The Scale of the Universe http://t.co/LkZWXXmIuX Great Scientists Don't Need Math http://t.co/9bWxCAhqsW via @username Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/0KsI8yvM8m Queens of the Stone Age - My God Is The Sun I just reserved my name on Mammoth. Go to http://t.co/LbyVPYdzF6 and reserve yours! http://t.co/LbyVPYdzF6 Heal Them With Fire From Above. Now. http://t.co/zUtE5cbrEg #MyGodIsTheSun via @username Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/ArKFjXtacR Queens of the Stone Age - I Appear Missing Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/p315ViXGMy Queens of the Stone Age - Avon (Feat. Dave Grohl) Glastonbury 2002 ugly Belgian houses http://t.co/3Gqnk4FJKl Japanese Barista Makes 3D Latte Art http://t.co/k5htYyaCMz via @username Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/8c0hNhJO1k 19 I Appear Missing - Queens of the Stone Age (Live The Wiltern 2013) @username by using nohup you mean? Check out BBC dimensions! http://t.co/XDeGqBiU2c Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/XbYouqRxIp Arctic Monkeys - Do I Wanna Know? (Official Video) @username love the title! @username make sure you don't collapse, trust me, I've been in that place of PhD frenzy Somebody Built A Life-Size, Fully Functional Wall-E Robot | Geekologie http://t.co/R5iFgrAVOn via @username must read -- "Why I Hate Pandas and You Should Too" http://t.co/fPMOsQeErW via @username @username I would suggest we team up for a collaborative PhD dissertation on 'Writing a PhD dissertation' - interested? @username I sympathize - hang in there! PHD Comics: Search Results http://t.co/KhCFIYFtKO via @username hilarious! -- The one and only difference between OS X and Windows http://t.co/uFeZw0mrJX Tips for project managers http://t.co/ZDdH3a4V9D my #personality: leading, extrovert secure agreeable conscientious open to experience | discover yours http://t.co/9rwDrQ4q5D #personalitwit Hidden mothers in Victorian portraits http://t.co/mdXUuBnfVE via @username "The Vampyre Of Time And Memory" [Video im 1LIVE FERNSEHER] http://t.co/nhTdlbnVDJ Somebody please explain this one to me - The Oatmeal http://t.co/HlZw9Cs9Gp via @username The world reacts to the crisis in Syria - The Oatmeal [Comic] http://t.co/kueFRPqXYH via @username @username wondering where that inclination towards the negative comes from... Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/YFMTOOgjI8 Whomadewho - Space For Rent Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/tTOTqSf3EF Eat That Frog! by Brian Tracy a must read for all men and women about gender differences | http://t.co/OyfYkH7O5h via @username @username "radically different" as in "becoming a barista"? @username I'll check you out on Thursday to see if you've changed enough to become a gigolo -- LOL @username your humour is your best feature (take it as a compliment) attending a @username talk on ensemble methods for personality recognition by @username and @username @username Japan's favorite animated gifs http://t.co/wlKqiV6Qo0 Doctoral researcher in the field of bioinformatics / data mining - Universiteit Antwerpen https://t.co/X1qZ1VlY9l via @username TomTato: 'mutant' plant that grows tomatoes and potatoes unleashed via @username http://t.co/xO59I2YJIh Justin Timberlake Shows Us How Dumb We Sound When We Use Hashtags http://t.co/LWxASoqNrs PHD Comics: Government Shutdown http://t.co/bKa5pGXwdx via @username cannot stop loving this -- Soundgarden - Black Hole Sun: http://t.co/HgV7uC2uma via @username Vending Machine Dispenses Free Coffee For Yawns | Geekologie http://t.co/E5CmXuc60o via @username The Gmail Extension That Aims to Drown the NSA in Nonsense http://t.co/dQM3eqRYs5 via @username Look At You: Guy Solving The Lyrics To Daft Punk's 'Harder, Better, Faster, Stronger' On A Rubik's Cube http://t.co/hXSfN0ZMUv The history of "free" - http://t.co/XubTiMJLdz words from other languages to adopt immediately http://t.co/1P1P7P8jHn jIyIntaHvIS not qajegh (Klingon Rick Roll Parody): http://t.co/IUynKT6wqi via @username Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/jjYdQyncq4 "MEDIEVAL LAND FUN-TIME WORLD" EXTENDED TRAILER — A Bad Lip Reading of Game National flags made from each country's chow http://t.co/mv9qIr6vsg Digital taxidermy http://t.co/c8cE9NiC5A now there's an argument for wallpaper! -- Natural History Wallpaper http://t.co/sHd0YkvHI7 want! #forthekidsofcourse -- Sweet Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle Shell Backpacks http://t.co/btXdOEBjwo lovely Garfield comic about Pooky http://t.co/sI5N7uCWCg @username you have to start drinking coffee before you get the headache - for me that works Burnout syndrome art by Ole Ukena http://t.co/eiQL16jQ9I 30 Of The Most Powerful Images Ever | Bored Panda http://t.co/adQ5cGkVrp … via @username Well It's About Time: A Golden Girls LEGO Minifig Set | Geekologie http://t.co/fxcroWXh0D via @username Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/T5vDteM3rI Compact Disk Dummies - What You Want (Official Video) Apparently I have one of the rarer birth dates: 24 December http://t.co/ooEisZFnqd Not So Fun Anymore: Photos Of Abandoned Toy Factories | Geekologie http://t.co/tOjm83XkfU @username cool!!! Just do it later - The Oatmeal http://t.co/bnAztV8Ewb via @username My Dog: The Paradox - The Oatmeal http://t.co/iW9dKzSBVb via @username Why Nikola Tesla was the greatest geek who ever lived - The Oatmeal http://t.co/MGpFZDMMQx via @username viva Soulwax! http://t.co/PL2Cla65L4 These parents are amazing! http://t.co/mHYF9597AT scientific news from Belgium | Professors Find Traces Of Herpes Virus On Library Copies Of 'Fifty Shades Of Grey' http://t.co/V5jz5PVOD1 Ik vind een @username van @username leuk: http://t.co/HbX9741Jx9 CGI VFX Animated Short HD: "iDiots" - A tale by Big Lazy Robot Awesome | CGI VFX Animated Short HD: "iDiots" - A tale by Big Lazy Robot VFX: http://t.co/crYqb57IM5 Leonardo Da Vinci's 'Viola Organista' Built In Real Life, Looks Like Piano, Sounds Like A String Orchestra http://t.co/0TnBGLfC6u looks great :) | Lego set with no instructions for budding architects | http://t.co/C0zxmXCgSJ Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/Et6KLumVtS Arcade Fire - Here Comes the Night Time I'm learning about Nelson Mandela's extraordinary life on the Nelson Mandela Digital Archive Project #mandela http://t.co/lEzBJLqA5T Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/owtuYMNEqF Arcade Fire - We Exist live from Capitol Studios. October 29, 2013. BBC Nature - Zebra stripes mystery 'explained' http://t.co/wH1l65ZCcO So you think you can logistische regressie - http://t.co/mmnfn7xqZs Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/xy05VBzeIV Greetings from Chuck (The epic christmas split) 'Gritty' Illustrations Of Childhood Characters | Geekologie http://t.co/sNGa97nFPH via @username Register for the Antwerp EADH Spring Academy in Digital Humanities 2014 http://t.co/OzlR8g48Sh Scientists explain their processes with a little too much honesty http://t.co/syel9YoUMu @username 'Formidable' transformed into an ad on http://t.co/UOXTmRygGT PHD Comics :: Valentine's Gifts for your Professor http://t.co/crdOrhjHaI @username sorry I could not make it; congratulate Oydis for me! @username super!!!! proficiat dr. Hide A must-read! http://t.co/0dVf6oQl9p Single woman spends 14 years with mannequin family to make a point http://t.co/vPg1YBQuUo "Gendered Language: Feature or Bug in Software Documentation?" http://t.co/IDnWqJ6RLi Ik vind een @username leuk: http://t.co/r7lqrqffyk Pixies - Gouge Away (live 1990 RARE) PHD Comics: Magic Code http://t.co/Ky18xa5B4d via @username Is Speed Reading Possible? - Olga Khazan - The Atlantic http://t.co/gUPoQ4xiQi Check out 2048, a game where you join numbers to score high! #2048game http://t.co/aNFn1YCVPG via @username 