<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="user344">
	<document><![CDATA[@username check http://t.co/xZXHJcaF0n if your answer isn't there, add it to the comments.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username well, what did you mean?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username so we agreed. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I do have a soft spot for certain people. ;)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username lol cnxn is just as bad, but at least we have LP		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username well, if that soft spot passes love, it might turn blind. :D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username sorry mate, I don't play cross-atlantic.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username Somme fonttypes are Capital only. Change font and try again.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I would. Sue me.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username and then the buzzer rings to wake you up.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username cringingly cute. :S		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username read http://t.co/m4xgBigM5c		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I speak 4 languages. Why does that matter?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username with a touch of creative imagination I know exactly what you mean. :D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[.@username @username the truth is: there is no truth.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thank on that notion I'll probably have my next nightmare, so much thanks.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username worst salesman ever. *turns around, SHE asked for slim calf boots!?* *other people around start laughing*		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I admire the climatologists trying to pose a model on this behaviour. Climate models are still not reliable.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username nothing to worry about. The usual gifted wannabe trait of feeling self confidence. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username we used to say no, But we are about to change things.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username in relation to?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Roger who?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username not too shabby		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username i have no real judgement about you being gifted, i merely rephrased it from your profile.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username and about the perceived narcisism, naeh mate, no worries. Read the DSM or wikipedia and judge yourself.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username you having no balls is not newsworthy.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username in his case: eunoch.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username smh. AND you favorite your own tweet? Narcissistic tendency. :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I'll pull your tail. as usual. :D		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username as in all things in life: Balance with a Smile. :) Both too little and too much swearing can be uncomfortable.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Aristotle, the first humanist. Father of humanity and logical reasoning. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username so much cringe and good in this tweet. But I know it came from a good heart. <3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I have ways to haunt your dreams.... MWHUAHAHAHAAAAAAH!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username it should read: "The best player in a TEAM is..." With the answer @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username stfu yourself. Go back to sleep.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I prefer Raid S&D. Just saying.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username by what mechanism has an INFJ become a superhero sensing something outside their introvert realm?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username how many stereotype in one tweet? #LeSigh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username he IS a serial plagiarist http://t.co/JzwyVG26kc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username he is a serial plagiarist though http://t.co/JzwyVG26kc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username you do realize the one hand is water and not ice?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username when reality is a stereotype, one cannot improve on describing it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username dear senator, Denmark might not be the best example anymore http://t.co/cqS8sdXy6B		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username other perspective; you know one of your trusted followers has a thing for Yin Yang AND is meticulous about truth. So? :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username nope, you merely shared a beautiful picture and I like it. ;) How about that Yin Yang flip-flop convo? :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[To all gamers stressed out over games...  http://t.co/AmhnBSbztW		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username *raises hand*		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username these meals are a major cause of your acne outbreaks. #GoVeggie or #LessMeat		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username at least we can make an approach. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why judge someone? Each and every person has their own struggles in life.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Want to improve yourself? http://t.co/jDW8AFaqic		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I understand the feeling, I have the same weak spine in front of our BBQ. :S #OhWell :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username is this love of self?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username more like every other day?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I experience love of self as the most strongest. And I experience love for my kids stronger as love for my partner.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username everything? Ok.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username from a logical POV; Yes, I disagree. from your personal POV; as stated Ok. :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username kinda funny, there are actually multiple POVs here. 1. You doing things for the first time. Ok. 2. You cannot do all things.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username 3. logically every thing can be done for the first time. 4. logically "there is" is present tense, as in the first is already		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username here and executed and not considered a potential first time. Summary, dom Ne's are creative. :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thnx, I needed that.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hmm, I think I am on to something on how to fix ANY COD connection... any Fariko volunteers that wanna test with me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username yup, definitely developing European tendencies... speedos. smh.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I just told you we don't work that way. Now stop begging.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username so, now you want to change the way we operate? gtfo.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username it is EXACTLY what you are saying. Why even deny it? And you even continue to change it. /blocked		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username I wasn't referring to the men wearing speedos, but to the focus of naughty K. ;)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username love works in mysterious ways.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Change is the key to improvement. http://t.co/1AgxPtwHnt		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username spirituality is the operative word. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username with dropbox we have had that for years AND including windows and android. Apple seems to become more and more of a copycat.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username merely a balance with a smile between Jung's cognitive functions Te and Fe. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username what is the current literacy rate amongst muslims?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username planet USApe apparently?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username you do realize what "Boko Haram" means?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[.@username @username the point is: science should be about improving ALL of mankind. Not a matter of groups pounding their chests.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username it is not about dividing people by religions, race, sex or nation. But about joining as one to improve humanity.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username the url you gave merely stated SA, which is highly doubtfull. no USA rates and no European rates. You're a propagandist.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username the question is, is he still a writer for Salon and others where he published plagiarized content?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[.@username nothing much, merely kicking trickshotters/snipers ass in FFA.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I think @username should adopt you as well if you get 50 RTs. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username http://t.co/m4xgBigM5c then http://t.co/tEETWPZ3ZX to find a team		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username just joining the conga line. Yay!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username sure go http://t.co/m4xgBigM5c and then http://t.co/tEETWPZ3ZX to find gamers		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[300 Years of FOSSIL FUELS in 300 Seconds: http://t.co/5mclrY6AVJ via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username read how we work here http://t.co/m4xgBigM5c		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username only for games you need a separate GFX-card. the inboard GFX-chip will suffice for movies.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username go to your device manager and let it discover new devices, it might not have its device driver installed/activated?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username errr, do what?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username but it DOES help in creativity brainstorm sessions. :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username you in da mirror = double scare. don't EVER do that again. #StillShaking		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username the one moved has the power to create usefulness in any direction he moves.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username YOU are a kind person #INFJ #truth		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username arrogant pricks. No one can really understand someone else, leave alone themselves.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username never experienced trees in fall? feel sorry for you in a compassionate way.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username i couldn't resist such a nice yin yang setup :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Free iOS App of the day: Ichi by Stolen Couch Games, very cool puzzle game! https://t.co/6RbCvQyCUV http://t.co/PEpdWH0JW7		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username only FREE today!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username "Call of Duty pro is a woman" what do you mean with that?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username depends on what situation occurred and what you have been told during that...		]]></document>
</author>