<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="user77">
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  i think ive seen it only a couple of times. No idea why though		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  1° the raid (et de loin) 2° Taken  3° le dernier samaritain 4° Predator		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  you never tried playing tic-tac-toe on google doc? 
remember playing Tag with Reut or Yuval, CFP spmrl 2012 :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username I have to admit that I recently used the svn2git bridge to commit something on github... I'm too old for mercurial		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I could survive for 73 days in a Zombie apocalypse! http://t.co/iP2TTCOxgH Follow @username for more fun surveys!! #QZombie #SurveySays		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username you can find one of those postcards on sale here http://t.co/bAf5EwOMLR		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username not sure the reality is better: rumor has it that the DFKI will have most of the EU NLP money for the years to come		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username everyone has already moved to Germany. Haven't you heard about J.vonG. ?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username you were wondering why do people translate your post. That one and its intringuing search request is a good example of why :)))))		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  funny. The use of we is prefered in French academia. Even in a thesis (which is supposed to be an individual work).		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username As far as I can remember, almost all people I know (French) use we (or sometimes "one" like "one can see in Fig." instead of..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username .. Curve in Fig x shows that... my two cents: here it's considered vulgar to show off with "I proved", "I'll demonstrate" ...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username .. we prefer to include the reader in the rhetorical argument and make him part of the scientific journey		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username lol,  I've seen that a lot and I've done it many times (just checked and all my single auth. papers have it). Is it that wrong		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username check that out: it's called "nous de modestie" (modesty we) --> http://t.co/K5awUDiSpH  . it says that its use is favored ..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username .. because  1) it reminds that the author did not start from scratch (shoulders, giants)  and 2) it allows to put the ego away		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  there's even a paper on that very topic (in French) http://t.co/7ttrfyuZSf that guy did some stats apparently (small sample)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I don't want to be rude but I don't think it was van Baster (who was very white). that must be Gullit		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username what's the game?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username  Hey, I didn't  know hebrew2French MT was that accurate. Are you talking about some statues with chainsaws?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username  the penguins stuff would have been hilarious though :) like the next catchy title of every MTers out there		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Nice :) please tell hi to Laura and the guys :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I’ve wasted 58 days and 23 hours of my life watching TV shows. Calculate your time: http://t.co/A2EqQoUxQW		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username too bad this workshop isn't linked to the semeval semantic parsing shared task. Unofficial results are out and they're impressive		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username if they're confirmed, surface syntax parsing would be of no use anymore and that would have been something worth discussing		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#nlp #nlpproc who is up for helping bootsrap a dothraki treebank? would need a lexicon first and @username unsupervized stuff		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  I hope you'll invite the Task organizers to present the task results  because they're groundbreaking. (way above previous tasks)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username seriously, Excel is way better than OpenOffice Calc. And way faster too.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username don't tell me about it, the whole IR French Industry is still working with Unitex (a rule based system)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username mainly because it has a fancy interface to design rules, comes with tons and tons of different lexicon		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username and because they all can sell very expensive expertise to adapt them to new domain, etc.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username what could they sell with a standard ML package ? new data set ? too risky. it's like giving all away		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#YoManuscript is so bad, you added fake co-authors to share the shame and hide your name in the crowd		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#YoManuscript is so bad, it's like it has 666 pages, it's written in blood and will cause all reviewers to die before the next moon		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#YoManuscript is so bad Reviewer #3 sold it to Weird Al Yancovik for his upcoming  Benny Hill's theme song cover		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username what did he say about European academic and montague? (what a challenge for 140 char long messages :))		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username we do? well, you probably right. trying to remember last time I've said "la porte était fermée je te dis !!!"  if I meant "à clef"..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username  Only if they have a catchy title, otherwise they're screwed.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Oh, "cool" tweeter has become some kind of Facebookstein..  it's doomed.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username wtf?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username how about the misnomers like "French fries" ?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username well, frontier is blurry between named entities and some mwe. btw, isn't capital always needed?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username :) we're going to be doomed anyway when parsing stuffs like "I love Algerian music from Paris".		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username that would probably require a third field "originofconcept" or something like this		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[the infinite joy of discovering the paper you must review is 62 pages long, due in two weeks and you so don't want to do it. #justsayno		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[is that me or reviewing ate half of people's time this year? #toomanyconfs #justsayno #NLP #NLProc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  does it really produce this? I've seen a presentation from  S.Pulman and he showed some really baffling examples		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username also, do you know if there's  some formal links between the way embeddings are learned and analogy learning?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I am, I am... nice improvement btw. I'm just puzzled by this france-paris+italie= rome thinggy.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username pulman said something like "first I couldn't believe something could come out from this but it turned I was wrong" 1/2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username it was a talk on deep learning actually, RNR trained on word embeddings, very interesting (short talk) http://t.co/e56my63Ool		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username and by puzzled, I mean totally hallucinating		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username well, yes a bit, according to Pullman, it's Paris-France+Italy= Rome (9mn43 on the video)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I really need to read your paper, @username just told me to RTFP yours :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I'm  wondering if this would work with Movies vs Director..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username My sister says that mommy killed her. Mommy says that I don't have a sister.  (that one from reddit is my favorite)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  digging into old proceedings (< 90) I found this http://t.co/0t44QtZCsG  you might like it (free word order dep. parsing) :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username what the fucking fuck !!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[worse idea ever: follow some lame fucktards who has nothing better to do than posting photos of cannibalism victims #WTF		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username @username  I'm  a parisian and I didn't know it either. Is it fun for  a 3 years old ?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I still can't believe Jack Bauer is back! #palmer4president #jackbauerisback		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username in all total fairness Cyclops's optic ray is no laser, it's some kind of plasma, pretty much like Havoc's		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username at least, there doesn't seem to be 3 months kebbab leftover and a dead pigeon behind the first pile of stuffs..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username let me guess, you use its heat to keep your lunch warm.. nice light effect on the laptop btw, it looks like it's been instagrammed		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username worse are end of chapter footnotes, raaaaaah		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username what's wrong[1] with footnotes ? I like them very much    [1] As I can put little jokes inside a  paper		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username nan, that  would disrupt  the reading flow (as I can put little jokes) too much to be super funny (like (Benni Hill et al, 1983))		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username Hollywood, marshall plan and coca cola I'd say.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username care to share it ?  Some people do that..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  yes cool for the paper, but I meant the review itself :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Depeche Mood: a Lexicon for Emotion Analysis from Crowd Annotated News" best paper title ever. #NeedMoreCatchyTitle #NLPROC #ACL2104		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Actually I don't, only because the reviews I have are usually used to improve the paper which is them resubmitted.  1/2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username does it. He put online some reviews with some of his papers, turned into technical reports. I found it interesting. 2/3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Actually, you can also ask for the review to be unanomized and put them online if they really helped to improve the paper.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  I've always thought of a way to credit the reviewers when they helped to fix a very important flaw		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username that should be done in a opt-in basis.. like if I don't mind my rewiew been online, I sign it.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username I think i've seen a thread about this in hal daume's blog some years ago. About crediting the reviewers for published papers		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username I think it'll be cool...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username on mandatory signature: people may think they were reviewed by concurrent or just not fairly and retaliate		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username you know, I've heard cases of rejection just so the reviewers won't get their own work scooped and ..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username so signing would be a way to avoid this		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username well, there's always some flaw in a paper and some people can be really convincing at killing a paper		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username I couldn't agree more, I've tried rising this subject at emnlp2012's meeting, and I was unsuccessful		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username that year, there were more than 60 xACL workshops, LREC  and around 10 coling ones.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username you add all others (Formel Grammer, essli, LACL, etc.) it's more than 100, easily. On a given leap year		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username leap = eacl+coling+lrec+xACL		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username I'd suggest SPMRL but I like it very much  #joke #dontshootme		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username seriously, there should be merged of stuff but it's hard to do and how about small, and technical venues ?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username what do you mean last paper, last week works too...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username nice :) How long before people do that on all kind of spelling variation?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username even in slang? in French verlan (reverse spelling) we have arabe --> beur (short for be-ara) --> reu-beu  1/2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username but they are so few of them, you're better off with a lexicon or something like dynamic lexical acquisition		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  it's not that harder than English :)  both total randomness at play :)  btw, we're working on a new crapbank..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username I've seen so much horror in it, it's like the Replicant's speech  "I've seen things you cannot imagine"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username wasn't that proved for dogs and roosters some years ago?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[he's so the best at what he does  https://t.co/PNGlb7CrzO #ImaGeekSoSueMe		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username they're moving 300km away or is this like a second unit?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username wtf do you mean abandonned? it's been the location of a tv show for the last 20 years, broadcast in idk how many countries		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Woaw, and here I am always playing my sissy in my papers...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hi Reut, I know it's none of my business but what does this ht mean #?????????????????? it made google translate explode :) ...		]]></document>
</author>