<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="user577">
	<document><![CDATA[NO CHATEES MIENTRAS MANEJAS!!!!!! #PIENSA HAGAMOS CAMPAÑA PERMANENTE, RT TODOS LOS DIAS!!! AYUDEMOS TODOS!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[And you can call this place HOME http://t.co/aZ4DYpJ8RA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Regardless of which team wins the #FifaWorldCup the best performance overall has been from #GER & that is undeniable		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Rory Mcilroy		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My golf swing isn't what it used to be 5 years ago but Saturday mornings with the guys are getting better every year #golf #Friendship		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#DisneyCup2014 amazing for the kids! Prince! #proud #parenting #parents http://t.co/nb6UKwxjy8		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Today's @username easy going for a Saturday afternoon with Dragon & Shadow! #Missing Prince http://t.co/XZ6LmkTKrW		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Priceless! Shadow and cousin http://t.co/LzzP67xCt2		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Dont you hate it when she is right? I do! I hate it when my dragon is right! #Wives #women #boss		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Dont know how big my heart is but I guess is huge cause I love you so much! #Dragon #Prince #Shadow		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Everybody's Changing de Keane en #Spotify #diademúsica Amazing!!! http://t.co/yt1mnUANUj		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#itspsychobunny easy saturday watching @username at LA at the Guiness Cup http://t.co/Oj1r0sO7s6		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username help me out here. My website is http://t.co/5vHYuxc0L9		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username last friday a nice shopping experience at the store in Puebla Mx, gingham shirt, pants & blazer. Congrats!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Little Shadow and someone else! http://t.co/HRIzsQnKE1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#beutiful piano impossible not to remember... anything! ? River Flows In You - Original – Yiruma http://t.co/Fm1rJs2R7v #NowPlaying		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Ladies and Gentleman, my beautiful little Shadow. http://t.co/6wzSqlfxIp		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[What else do we have in this #life but #hugs & #Kisses , from the ones we love so very much? Not much		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[if you ever ask yourself who you are? the answer is that you are what you have become by those you love and that´s just wonderful...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Regardless of whether they are here or they are not, they were here once and got into you. They will always be here with you #always		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username That is so unfair Rory is great, amazing but @username really is an amazing golfer. Next time		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username red ginham		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The best shirt in the world #PINK #WSAY I'm all! @username @username http://t.co/jrniu2wdxm		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username too late! Sorry ????		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#mondaymorning blues is almost over! By next Wednesday will be surely over!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pure knowledge! #wine #winechat #WineWednesday #vino #VinoMexicano http://t.co/zHMXZS4Lcy		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#tee box hole 1 #saturday golf http://t.co/a0UAM0hcH5		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Good enough, not very fruty, clásico Toro. Vino from Telmo Rodriguez via @username: http://t.co/MYGVaCE2aL		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Shadow and a Dementor (@username ) doing funny stuff #sundayfunday #sunday http://t.co/mAgyVrsxNf		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just saw for the third time #GoodWillHunting what a great movie! #goodfilms #RobinWilliams #robinmemories		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Into to the battle! #mondaymotivation #monday #mondaymorning #cpa #auditor		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Pruebe este wine de Bienbebido. Lo escaneé con la aplicación @username: http://t.co/StgVuZMIzc the plus is that it is simple		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tuesday is over now, at least the #weekend is just ahead! #PIENSA #think  #TuesdayTreat #TuesdayTip		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username yes it does it shows his is inmature and in no control of the qb postion and the offensive line		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Inclusion inspires innovation. Apple. #phrases we are all players in the same game		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[If it is about thinking I am no 1 not because of the content or the depth but because of the amount of thoughts #busy http://t.co/eOP5EilPrn		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username AMAZING wine guys!  I had a glass today [a meal without wine is called breakfast]		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username everything we've been getting from Garret the last few years has been mistaken :(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#sundaynight and the #Mondaymorningblues is already here!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Tony Romo every single day of the week and twice om Sundays		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  @username nxt season will not be complicated not at all i'll be dramatically absurd #Cowboys #Cowboysforever		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Almost every successful person begins with 2 beliefs: the future can be better than the present and I have the power to make it so.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#sundayafternoon with my sun #priceless		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Everything you've ever wanted is on the other side of fear." -George Addair		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It is not about #MORE it is about #BETTER #Contador #contadores #Contaduría #CPA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Amazing the plot on @username of all 4 seasons. Genius writers #louislittfan		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username like he said, he is the new dominant golfer of this era. Someone was needed (?)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Sunday Morning
Maroon 5 • Songs About Jane en #Spotify to get in the proper mood! Jaja http://t.co/kYGqSRZtdL		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Looking Too Closely
Fink • Hard Believer en #Spotify sunday, about to rain http://t.co/NnX6Za1OSc		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The #office. Calm, nice place to work http://t.co/VhZelYfFxU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Right now looking for people willing to make a professional life in #Accounting  #Consulting & #Tax Career Plan ready!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It will take hard work, self-study, years of trainning & comes along with professional technical challenge in more than 1 lenguage ...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["If things start happening, don't worry, don't stew, just go right along and you'll start happening too." - Dr. Seuss		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Always give without remembering and always receive without forgetting." - Brian Tracy via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["You have enemies? Good. That means you've stood up for something, sometime in your life." - Winston Churchill		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#TeamEurope will win the @username! #RyderCup http://t.co/sM3J0ugoDn		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Person who chases two rabbits catches neither." - Confucius via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["The shoe that fits one person pinches another; there is no recipe for living that suits all cases." - Carl Jung		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[As fast as each opportunity presents itself, use it! No matter how tiny an opportunity it may be, use it! - Robert Collier		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["It's not what happens to you it's what you do about it that makes the difference." - Wilson Mitchell. via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username go Cowboys! Please! Please! Please!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Life is about giving other people inspiration to do whatever they want to do well." - Trisha Mason  via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["A people that values its privileges above its principles soon loses both." - Dwight D. Eisenhower  via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#shadow all the work by herself http://t.co/6QERYoGSFv		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[This one will be a though week. Better to get into it so it will end sooner (?) is that even possible? #MondayMorning		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I am not a product of my circumstances, I am a product of my #decisions . Covey  #DecisionsDesicions		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["People do not change, they are merely revealed." - Anne Enright via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username you guys dont have any idea of how important it is that you held a Evernote Conference in Mexico. Come here! You'll be thrilled		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I know not with what weapons World War III will be fought, but World War IV will be fought with sticks and stones." - Albert Einstein		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I learned that if you want to make it bad enough, no matter how bad it is, you can make it. - Gale Sayers  via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Hard work without talent is a shame, but talent without hard work is a tragedy." - Robert Half via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username exactly!!!! Meetings are efficiency killers		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["When you are content to be simply yourself and don't compare or compete, everybody will respect you." - Lao Tsu via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Its not a joke! Dont text & drive!!!! #drivesafe #responsability #kidsdrivig #youngpeople #oldpeople		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[A happy person is not a person in a certain set of circumstances, but rather a person with a certain set of attitudes. - Hugh Downs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username just got my sandalwood kit. Amazing shaving! Congrats!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Shoutout to my new followers: @username @username via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Found some new friends: @username @username @username @username @username via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Awesome day on twitter: 2 new followers, 5 new friends, 129 tweets, 5 Fvs via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[The only disability in life is a bad attitude. - Scott Hamilton  via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I have found the paradox, that if you love until it hurts, there can be no more hurt, only more love." - Mother Teresa		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Milenio hoy http://t.co/h3VOLKQ2aU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hi how can I present my evernote desktop like the one on this photo? the color notes right next notes? http://t.co/uSJasIPg2o		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying The Adventure
Angels & Airwaves • MTV Presents Laguna Beach - Summer Can La…todays recommendation http://t.co/AbGfFXWDM3		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username thanks!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Shoutout to my new followers: @username via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[No more #whatsapp PLEASE! Talk to people! Use your mouth!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Awesome day on twitter: 1 new followers, 24 tweets, 2 Fvs via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username our momentum is better, our defense is getting compact, it is our time. Going for 5		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["If you make a mistake and do not correct it, then only it is called a mistake." - Confucius via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Shoutout to my new followers: @username via http://t.co/1OZY3C77oL		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Awesome day on twitter: 2 new followers, 14 tweets via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Time is a created thing. To say 'I don't have time,' is like saying, 'I don't want to.' " - Lao Tzu via http://t.co/1OZY3C77oL		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Come To Me
The Goo Goo Dolls • Magnetic en #Spotify todays recommendation ! Real nice http://t.co/v9JDMmv4MU		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Say You Love Me
Jessie Ware • Say You Love Me en #Spotify bonus track for #wednesday afternoon http://t.co/RD6EtuQI1O		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[What We Learned Analyzing 595 Blogposts: A Complete Content Audit And Spreadsheet Template http://t.co/RuEK4PSjyO http://t.co/a1kYZmldcz		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["Hard work without talent is a shame, but talent without hard work is a tragedy." - Robert Half via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Dont miss the film The Hundred Foot Journey  amazing film, great story, great cast, amazing location. Trust me		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Shoutout to my new followers: @username via http://t.co/4KKSwparAh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Excelsior hoy vierned http://t.co/4tSAsMYaD0		]]></document>
</author>