<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="user549">
	<document><![CDATA[Looks great. Sad not to have been invited! RT @username: Atelier Edition numérique http://t.co/kwY7uvjq		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[is enjoying the passagiato #fb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Antoine Dodson : he's cool.   http://n.pr/cQVqMB		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Inexorable pale blue seepage of FB charted over time and space http://t.co/6bcdII5k : what happened to diversity?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[managed to register for  #tcp2012 ! hoorah! possibly the worst user interface I have ever seen, so let's hope the event is a lot better.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username no doubt but that doesn't prove anything!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hello England what.is this warm yellow fiery thing in the.sky?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username come to zatcamp paris on Sept !		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Spoke too soon .. its not available in oxford.  MT @username Hello England what is this warm yellow fiery thing in the.sky?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username 25/26 Sept ...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Shame! anyway here's the list http://t.co/WIANtpMY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I dont know what I'm doing here		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[back in dun loaghoaire waiting for the ferry home after a few days  promoting #tei  odds  to iso tc37 sc4		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[It's official!  http://bit.ly/9hoMcZ		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Tx Channel4 for screening "Attack the block" tonight as an alternative to tedious foopball. #fb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Should be hard at work prepping for #dhoxss but instead am off to Upton park (wherever that is) for a mauritian party #fb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username we'll be ok its in a church.hall . Must say your gig looks more fun tho		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I saw this wall in Dun Laoghaire last weekend and thought of you:  http://bit.ly/alrsyq		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username oh yes you can		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username he means "whole world" as in "world series" no doubt...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username You know you're a hardcore digital humanist  when you find yourself thinking, "Ah, now I'll do some TEI encoding to relax."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Back from bristol and having a days rest before heading to hamburg for #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[On the bus to the train to the plane to the train to #dh2012 and its not raining!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hoorah for Birmingham Airport and its free wifi! Edging my way closer to #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Made it to Hamburg in time for free drinks -- met dozens of people -- had dinner -- finished tomorrow's talk -- time for bed #dh2012 #fb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Panel on text analysis vs text encoding... a constructed opposition : the differences are purely social, surely? #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[a cynic might say that some people make a nice living out of constructing xml as too hard for humanists to understand #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[syd confesses he's in markup biz for fun ... but has noticed most people are not #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[All the problems with XNMLTEI posed so far have the same simple solution: RTFM . Why do people find that so hard? #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MT @username: #dh2012  Selection of Document Bits, from Bauman + SpMcQ http://t.co/R8xEWw4h -- an xform based stylesheet generator		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[dino's point about circularity of marking up what you expect to find cf concerns about annotn of lang corpora expressd by J Sinclair #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[we need a nicer way of visualising odd internal workings e.g. uml output from schemafrag  #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/X9LuDNEf transcribed Chinese sutras in tei #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Another exciting and exhausting day at #dh2012 closes... and here i am writing slides for tomorrow's #agora presentn, sigh #fb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[so far this a.m. at #dh2012 -- a cool project annotating & analysing 17c titlepages in TEI, 2 demos of bagofword apprch to txtclassifying		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MT @username: .@username I'm embarrassingly fat! ...! http://t.co/K7YpZpGg #dh2012 -- me too! and why do i  wave my hands so much?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Tx for reminder. I didnt have time to mention all software ! muruca is also relevant...		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username we were all taught to say what you're going to say, say it, and then say what you just said ! #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username sorry to be pedantic, but babel wasnt a library!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MT @username: @username: The great Xbox boom of 1901 isn't a reason to lampoon google books. Poor OCR is near ubiquitous. #dh2012 Quite!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MT @username: Good to know that The Gutenberg Elegies is still remembered...I remember when it was new. #Olddher #dh2012 -- oh! is it old now?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[80% readers of 19c newspapers come from public lib users -- pity our govt is closing them down #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[combination of gabbling and poor acoustics in this lecture room are making the topic mapping panel suboptimal for me  #dh2012 nice bell tho		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[is topic modelling is a stable methodology, well understood statistical model? one says yes, another says doesnt matter #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[is topic modelling substantially different from other  usesof statistical techniques in text analysis? seemingly only in its claims #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I was thinking of ancient programs like General Enquirer and statistical methods  which do automatic keyword extraction		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username well, http://t.co/Qt3ktFe6 for ex.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[for example as described in  http://t.co/Qt3ktFe6
RT @username: What other techniques do you have in mind?. #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username would this be the same first folio as the one which has been available from the OTA for the last 30 yrs #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Ah, OK. So we could link them with the existing xml transcript? #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MT @username: .@username "Interfaces have to change over time...Word Clouds now dead/dated designers say" #dh2012 good thing too!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MT @username: Sitting in on the ADHO AGM meeting to hear more about DH training programs. #dh2012 // AND to qualify for free lunch //+1		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Elisabeth Burr describes workshops in Leipzig: co-taught largely by computer sci staff? #d2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[langefors information theorist cited by thaller #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Thallers views imply primacy of "original" creator of a doc (authorial intention) ... a bit old fashioned surely? #dh2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[enjoying evening sunshine by the beach at blankenese. bring on the matjesfilets #fb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username Naturally, there are broken links on Ubu. We still write the damn thing by hand in BBEdit. If you find something let us know.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MT @username:   Email @username if you want to join this little TEI git repo//  yes please! (now i kno wot a gitrepo is tx @username)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username Olympic opening ceremony a Labour party broadcast? Yup, that's about right http://t.co/2j9RnTuQ via @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[went for nice bike ride : got drenched by rain and dried out by sun. twice. ah the delightful british summer. #fb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Off to west drayton for #drha2010 at brunel		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[As Bodley starts yet another shakespeare digitization project, this article from 2001 makes good reading http://t.co/wFZ5dTHn #fb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["In every punctuation mark thoughtfully avoided, writing pays homage to the sound it suppresses"  tx mr adorno !  http://t.co/oINb2tvY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[First full day of #drha2010 done... brill plenary, lots of cool sessions, and some wild performances. bring on tomorrow (but less rain plz)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I'm a techno-classicist myself #drha		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[coyne: for mcluhan, the defining technology was the printing press; for mumford the clock #drha2010		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[coyne: is there anything other than metaphor? #drha2010		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[coyne (quoting urry): we are hybrid assemblages of humans, objects, technologies and scripts , always tourists #drha2010		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[seen google today? http://bit.ly/137f1v  there's pretty!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I feer the walrus was definitely not russell brand		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[enjoying the octopus though #olympics		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[and whoever this twerp is he s no freddy mercury #olympics		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[brazil's anthem is a perky little number #olympic		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I wasn't expecting the spanish inquisition #closing ceremony		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Blimey its darcy bussell doing a downmarket version of the firebird. igor must be turning in his grave b#closingceremony		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[isnt this where they say "hopei die before i get old"?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username: (I can't take credit for this) ... "Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan" anagrams to "My ultimate Ayn Rand porn" #perfect		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username Novel text analysis uses PageRank to identify influential Victorian authors | Ars Technica http://t.co/QOOWPbsY		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MT @username  announces Visual Poetry section 100+ PDFs of historical & contemporary work: http://t.co/ADNvJQfR ll .. no John furnival tho		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Gotta love that "even" :  Exploiting digital information will be dominant in all future research even in arts and humanities" - G.  Crossick		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MT @username: "RailAir" from Heathrow to Reading is,a bus, ...// it goes from the RAIL station to the AIRport. Keep up at the back		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[sad to be missing #dhcshef but enjoying polyglot wrapup of Berne #TEI workshop		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Back in Paddington being made to run for train home by fgw . Such a nice change from sbb/sncf who got me here without fuss #welcometouk		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hooray for iPlayer but can I manage another drwho or should I be catching up on parades end ? #firstworldproblems		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username Chris P. has only ever DMd me twice on Twitter and both of them (I now suspect) were spam. Sigh		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username I have been with budgetmobile.fr for a year and never paid more than 10 euro a month, including one when i sat on phone for an hour		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username @username See for example http://t.co/gihn3yzu (I assume you don't want the Fr version)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Teaching #TEI and genetic editing in Bern, in French, German, and Italian. New blogentry at http://t.co/2RcAWAd9 #fb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username that's why the tei gave you join		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RT @username Extensibility of TEI is key to it being able to provide a systematic representational language to any project @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username we need to steal this and make it produce TEI markup!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Why is getting from cutteslowe to st Pancras on a Sunday such a nightmare? Trains late buses elusive and its raining miserably. #fb		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[At #ZatCompParee Serge and Alexei show us how TXM copes with the variable state of #TEI XML text in http://t.co/gERxe9KX #21stcenturyprobs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Oooh, my first publicn of 2012 en francais! Read/Write Book 2 - Du literary and linguistic ...OpenEdition Press http://t.co/P3fct7fO		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[MT @username: I suspect there is no .iscat method. #tcp2012 http://t.co/R2eOjzsO and plato hated cats anyway		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/ZPgN115Y RT @username: @username It's reference to "The Shining"! #tcp2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Comment tradiuire en francais "shelling peas while wearing boxing gloves"? #tcp2012 c'est ca programmer en python!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[there have been quite a few thatcamps in the usa too, but they don't seem to feature in frederique's history #tcp2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[even non-conferences have to start by thanking their organizers and funders #tcp2012		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[ALLC rebrands self as "European association for digital humanities". #ihavelivedtoolong		]]></document>
</author>