<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><author id="user130">
	<document><![CDATA[A month until my b-day !!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Doing my geography homework dont you guys  love high school		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I know tht im really broken when one direction doesnt even make me feel better		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Sorry i havent been on high school is tough		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I hate life why cant it always go up making you happy cause right now im going straight down		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey guys homework sucks thts all i got to say :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  omg  your pic is really cool how did you take it?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#mtvhottest one direction		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username hey guys retweet this cause it counts so vote for our husbands		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  make our boys win vote!! #mtvhottest one direction RT counts		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey good night everyone i g2g so BYEEE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[One direction is in the same city as me!!!!! IM SOOO HAPPY!!! too bad i wont get to see them :(		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#imagine you run into one direction while your on a shopping spree and they go buy stuff for you and carry your bags		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[directioners athem : http://t.co/7dpigvwLfA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My friend went to the one direction concert and she didn't take me!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Paulina #2 went to with her cousin and she had seats in the middle		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Every one talking about how awesome the one direction concert was then there's me" I'm just happy the weren't 5,000,000 miles away from me"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I LEARNED LEEROYS DANCE!!  its Per-fect!! :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#Awkward when your parents look through your one direction pics		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Me when my one direction poster falls ontop of me when im sleeping " LOUIS! YOUR BAAAD BOOY!!"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Some girls in the locker room today were saying louis not loui then i got mad and yelled " THE S IS SILENT GET IT RIGHT!!"		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[" cause you right here and i shouldve taken the chance but i got so scared and i lost the moment again" - One Direction		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[You know you love somebody when it been over a year an your still not over them #notoveryou		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I'm sensitive okay so you can offend i'd use a come back then id go away and cry my heart away.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[when asked to rate 1D write down numbers 1-5 but then put all there names on #1 :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey guys i g2g dont know if i'll go on later but if i dont #GoodNight		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Saw i was following 666 people fraked out and followed 10 more #Christan		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  whoops i freaked out not fraked out #typo		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  what happened did something pop up and dont worry louis your famous (sexy too) one day you'll meet him.		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Follow me		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Please please please 

Follow me  PLEASE :) :) :) You'd make me the happiest person in the world :) :) :):) :)		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[REMINDER: 17 days till my B-day who wants to get me 1D as my Present :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[#imagine one direction came to your house and spent a week with you		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[222 tweets thats like a perfect number well now its 223 :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[One direction always makes me feel better		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My hearts better as of today @username 3:19 :)  gotta change my bio now		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[VOTE FOR ONE DIRECTION!! Now for both #mtvhottest one direction  and for teen choice awards cmon directoners		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Leaving soon BYE GUYS!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Who's exited to see one direction @username the #TCA		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username sorry i havent sent the response i'll tell you why in the response		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Took the trash out w/h my cousin she takes empty trash can i tell her to put it back same moment bro turns on lawn mower she runsand screams		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Louis " i dont think theres anything sexy about the way i look" Me: hahahahhahaha thats a good one louis!! @username		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  hahahaha no you should do it more often :P You should tell Louis to do it  him with dat sexy bum :D PLEASE 

FOLLOW ME		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[g2g guys more tweets tommorow i promise :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey guys have tooooons of homework tonight this'll be my only tweet sorry BYE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey guys hows life?  mines well eh :P  JK IM HAAAAAAPPY !!!!!! Not really i more neutral but whateves		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Who loves 1D i love 1D who saw 1D win i saw 1D at the TCA's!! GOO DIRECTIONERS!! Next stop #mtvhottest one direction		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[C'mon you guys Justin is catching up we gotta win VOTE!! #mtvhottest one direction  1D is waaay hotter then Justin so VOTE!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["happiness often seeps through a door you didn't know was open."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Cmon you guys vote for one direction #mtvhottest one direction  and #voteonedirection		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey guys havent gone to the bathroom alllll day gonna go right now!! Sooooo yeah im kinda random :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Just went to the bathroom now making spaghetti #YUM		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[getting off now wont be able to get back on do #goodnight you guys more tweets tomorrow		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey guys today im at home but at school cause were doing a classes online day and i finished all my work early YEAH!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Head phones were invented for only us to here are music but theres still the mouth. My brother tells me to shut up then i go "TO THE BEST.."		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  follow me ?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username OMG! I got angie to watch BSE!! she said it was okay!!! were making progress soon shell be a directioner !!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hey guys i like food :p		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  hey lou wanted to be the first you saw on this tweet did i make it hope soo. Follow me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  hey lou hope you read this im what you call a dedicated directioner follow me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  Lou i really do hope you read this follow me ? Im what you call a dedicated directioner		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  Hope you get this i know how you dont think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hope you get this i know how you dont think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hope you get this i know how you dont think your sexy  "but your perfect to me" follow me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hope you get this i know how you don't think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username hope you get this i know how you dont think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hope you get this i know how you dont think you'r sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hope you get this i know  you dont think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username Hope you get this i know  you don't think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me?		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[just tweeted a bunch of times to louis in hopes he'll see it and follow me		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Said his name was louis tomlinson, and his daddy was a pro polo player		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username  hahaha see thats what #Directioners do we make directionaters watch there videos and then make them fans		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hey guys sorry i wasnt on yesterday but well this is life #shithappens		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[SOOO HAPPY TODAY MAKIN PROGRESS... with something that you guys dont know about		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My life has been filled with problems..most which have never occurred- Norman		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[OMG 1D's NEW SONG LEAKED!!! Everyone look up cant let her go !!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[OMG!! I ATE IT TODAY!! In spainsh girl takes my chair i had no clue try to sit down and ended up falling IT WAS SOO FUNNY #epicfail		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Yesterday had cross country try-outs today had cross country practice yup i guess that means im a fast runner you guys :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I hate it when people tell blonde jokes in front of me its like really		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Doing a video spree on 1D #dedicated fan		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[boreeed dont wanna watch little league game wait.. is it over eh idk i dont care just gonna finish this then sleep soooo tired		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[she so mean but i gotta love it and i just cant let her go  - One direction		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Uggg stupid cross country ran 3 miles once and that was bad now i on sat. i have to run 6.4 miles thanks coach lopez #notethesacrasm		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[hey guys finished my homework im tired sooo good night		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[My birthday is 3 days away!!  soo tommorow imma a wear a big sticker that says its my b-day id let you hug me but.. i dont like hugs		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username @username   haha lol and write there name on out hands with hearts for the dots on the i's or is that just me..		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[RUMOR CONFIRMED : Zayn and Perri are engaged		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Saw 705 following thought thats how many followers i had Me: oO then i realized thats how many people i was following me: -____-		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[does this make anyone else hungry  cause i want a cookie now http://t.co/lQBnZUy9aE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[@username  3 days till my birthday and all i want is a follow from you		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey guys wanna know what i want for my b-day http://t.co/Hsdmn6cJRE		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[boooored out of my mind what to do oh yeah listen to one direction :P		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[I dont know if you can tell but ima a dedicated directioner you should see my english notebook		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA["I see it in your eyes your disapointed cause im the foolish that you anointed with your heart i tore it aprat" - One Direction		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[gonna pull a #allnighter who wants to do it with me!!!		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Who needs sleep when you can watch tv and go on Facebook		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Growing up sucks miss middle school :( #teardrop		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[oh yeah tv rocks		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[Hey guys still up told ya doin all nighter		]]></document>
	<document><![CDATA[i think i just fell in love with someone on.. facebook :p		]]></document>
</author>