#31 313 13  3 -  -  - t  tu tur urn rns ns  s s  su sun uns ns. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - g  gi gir ira ras aso sol oli li  i #  #3 #31 314 14  4 -  -  - a  ag aga gai ain ins nst st  t h  ha han and nd. d.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  co con ont ntr tro rom oma man ano no  o #  #3 #31 316 16  6 -  -  - w  wi wit ith th  h i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôm ôm  m b  ba bac ack ck. k.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  co con ont nto tor orn rno no  o #  #3 #31 317 17  7 -  -  - d  di div ive ve  e a  at at  t t  th the he  e h  he hea ear art rt. t.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - t  tu tuf uff ffo fo  o a  al al  l c  cu cuo uor ore re  e #  #3 #32 320 20  0 -  -  - t  ti tin iny ny  y r  ro roa oas ast st. t.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - a  ar arr rro ros ost sti tic ici cin ino no  o #  #3 #32 321 21  1 -  -  - a  at at  t p  pa pai ain in. n.  . -  -  - a  ap app ppe pen ena na  a #  #3 #32 322 22  2 -  -  - p  pu put ut  t t  th the he  e h  ha han and nds ds  s a  ah ahe hea ead ad. d.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . p  pe ped ede der ers rse sen en) n)  ) -  -  - m  me met ett tte ter ere re  e l  le le  e m  ma man ani ni  i a  av ava van ant nti ti  i #  #3 #32 325 25  5 -  -  - w  wh wha hat at  t a  a  a t  ti tin iny ny  y t  ty typ ype pef efa fac ace ce! e!  ! (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  ch che he  e c  ca car ara rat att tte ter eri rin ino no! o!  ! #  #3 #32 326 26  6 -  -  - d  do don onk nke key eya yac act ct. t.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - m  mu mul ula lat att tto to  o #  #3 #32 328 28  8 -  -  - e  en ent nte ter ere red ed  d a  at at  t t  te ten ens ns  s l  le leg eg. g.  . -  -  - e  en ent ntr tra rat ato to  o a  a  a g  ga gam amb mba ba  a t  te tes esa sa  a #  #3 #32 329 29  9 -  -  - p  po pok oke ke  e t  to too oot oth th. h.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti  i f  fe fea eat at. t.  . m  m. m.  . e  en eng ngo gol oll lli li) i)  ) -  -  - s  st stu tuz uzz zzi zic ica cad ade den ent nte te  e #  #3 #33 330 30  0 -  -  - b  br bri rin ing ng  g h  ho hom ome me  e t  th the he  e r  re res esu sul ult lt. t.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f g  g. g.  . t  to toi oia ia) a)  ) -  -  - p  po por ort rta tar are re  e a  a  a c  ca cas asa sa  a i  il il  l r  ri ris isu sul ult lta tat ato to  o #  #3 #33 333 33  3 -  -  - a  at at  t f  fa fac ace ce  e g  ga gar arl rli lic ic. c.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f t  t. t.  . l  lo los osc sch chi hi) i)  ) -  -  - a  av avv vvi vis isa sag agl gli lia ia¬ a¬† ¬†  † #  #3 #33 334 34  4 -  -  - r  re re- e-a -as ass ss. s.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . s  s. s.  . p  pe ped ede der ers rse sen en) n)  ) -  -  - r  ri rin inc ncu cul ulo lo  o #  #3 #33 335 35  5 -  -  - a  a  a l  lu lum ump mp  p a  at at  t t  th the he  e t  th thr hro roa oat at. t.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - u  un un  n n  no nod odo do  o a  al all lla la  a g  go gol ola la  a #  #3 #33 336 36  6 -  -  - h  he he  e s  st sta tay ays ys  s o  on on  n h  hi his is. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  so som ome meo eon one ne  e i  i  i d  do don on‚ n‚Ä ‚Äô Äôt ôt  t r  re rem eme mem emb mbe ber er) r)  ) -  -  - s  st sta ta  a s  su sul ull lle le  e s  su sue ue  e i  i  i f  fa fav avo vor ori rit ite ted ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o l  le les es  s l  lu lut uth thi hie ier ers rs  s -  -  - p  pe per erd rdo don ona nal ala la  a (  (b (bo bol ol√ l√© √©r ©ro rol olo lo) o)  ) #  #3 #33 338 38  8 -  -  - w  wa wat ate ter er  r i  in in  n m  mo mou out uth th. h.  . -  -  - a  ac acq cqu qua ua  a i  in in  n b  bo boc occ cca ca  a #  #3 #33 339 39  9 -  -  - w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the he  e t  ti tim ime mes es  s t  th tha hat at  t r  ru run uns ns. s.  . -  -  - c  co coi oi  i t  te tem emp mpi pi  i c  ch che he  e c  co cor orr rro ron ono no  o #  #3 #34 341 41  1 -  -  - y  yo you ou  u l  li liv ive ve  e i  it it. t.  . (  (‚ (‚Ä ‚Äú Äúi úi  i k  kn kno now ow  w a  a  a c  ci cit ity ty‚ y‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù s  sp spe pec eci cia ial al  l e  ed edi dit iti tio ion on  n b  by by  y a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - t  te tel ela lav avi viv iv  v #  #3 #34 342 42  2 -  -  - t  th the he  e f  fo foo oot ot‚ t‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s t  tr tre ree ee. e.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . b  bu bub uba ban ani ni) i)  ) -  -  - l  la la  a p  pi pia ian ant nta ta  a d  de del el  l p  pi pie ied ede de  e #  #3 #34 343 43  3 -  -  - o  ou out ut  t r  re rea ead ads ds. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - f  fu fuo uor ori ri  i l  le leg egg gge ge  e #  #3 #34 345 45  5 -  -  - i  it it‚ t‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s a  at at  t a  a  a s  sh sho hot ot  t o  of of  f g  gu gun un. n.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f c  c. c.  . g  ga gat att tti ti  i f  fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -¬ -¬† ¬†√ †√® √®  ® a  a  a u  un un  n t  ti tir iro ro  o d  di di  i s  sc sch chi hio iop opp ppo po  o #  #3 #34 347 47  7 -  -  - i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôm ôm  m b  bo boa oat ati tin ing ng. g.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - m  mi mi  i s  st sto to  o i  im imb mba bar arc rca can and ndo do  o #  #3 #34 348 48  8 -  -  - c  ca car art rti tin ina na  a t  to tor orn rna nas aso sol ole le. e.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . a  am ame men end ndo dol ola lag agi gin ine ne) e)  ) -  -  - l  li lit itt ttl tle le  e p  pa pap ape per er  r c  co com ome meb eba bac ack cks ksu sun un  n #  #3 #34 348 48  8 -  -  - l  li lit itt ttl tle le  e p  pa pap ape per er  r c  co com ome meb eba bac ack cks ksu sun un. n.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . a  am ame men end ndo dol ola lag agi gin ine ne) e)  ) -  -¬ -¬† ¬†c †ca car art rti tin ina na  a t  to tor orn rna nas aso sol ole le  e #  #3 #35 350 50  0 -  -  - f  fi fis ish sh  h d  da day ay, y,  , t  ti tim ime me  e e  es esc sca cap ape pes es. s.  . (  (s (sp spe pec eci cia ial al  l e  ed edi dit iti tio ion on  n c  ce cel ele leb ebr bra rat ati tin ing ng  g t  th the he  e 3  35 350 50t 0th th  h p  po pos ost st) t)  ) -  -  - c  ca car arp rpe pe  e d  di die iem em  m t  te tem emp mpu pus us  s f  fu fug ugi git it  t #  #3 #35 351 51  1 -  -  - o  on oni nio ion on  n w  we wea ear ari rin ing ng. g.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f c  c. c.  . g  ga gat att tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - v  ve ves est sti tir irs rsi si  i a  a  a c  ci cip ipo pol oll lla la  a i  i  i l  li lik ike ked ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o m  mo mo? o?d ?d? d?e ?er er  r d  da dan ani nie iel els lss sso son on  n f  fr fre res esc sco co  o "  "a "af afr fri ric ica ca" a"  " #  #3 #35 355 55  5 -  -  - a  at at  t t  th the he  e b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l b  be bet ett tte ter er. r.  . -  -  - a  al all lla la  a b  be bel ell ll‚ l‚Ä ‚Äô Äôe ôe  e m  me meg egl gli lio io  o #  #3 #35 356 56  6 -  -  - s  st sta tay ay  y s  su sun unn nny ny. y.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f m  m. m.  . z  za zam amp mpo pol oll llo lo) o)  ) -  -  - s  st sta tai ai  i s  se ser ere ren eno no  o #  #3 #35 357 57  7 -  -  - i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôm ôm  m a  at at  t t  th the he  e t  ta tak ake ken en  n w  wi wit ith th‚ h‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ -  -  - s  so son ono no  o a  al all lle le  e p  pr pre res ese se  e c  co con on‚ n‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ #  #3 #35 358 58  8 -  -  - m  me me  e h  ha has as  s p  pu put ut  t t  th the he  e w  wa wal alk lki kin ing ng  g s  st sti tic ick cks ks  s b  be bet etw twe wee een en  n t  th the he  e w  wh whe hee eel els ls. s.  . -  -  - m  mi mi  i h  ha ha  a m  me mes ess sso so  o i  i  i b  ba bas ast sto ton oni ni  i f  fr fra ra  a l  le le  e r  ru ruo uot ote te  e #  #3 #36 360 60  0 -  -  - t  th the he  e b  br bra ran and nd  d o  of of  f b  bu bub ubb bbl ble le. e.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - l  la la  a m  ma mar arc rca ca  a d  da da  a b  bo bol oll llo lo  o #  #3 #36 361 61  1 -  -  - a  at at  t m  me mer erm rma mai aid ids ds  s e  ex exp xpl pla lai ain ine ned ed. d.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . m  m. m.  . z  za zam amp mpo pol oll llo lo) o)  ) -  -  - a  a  a s  si sir ire ren ene ne  e s  sp spi pie ieg ega gat ate te  e #  #3 #36 362 62  2 -  -  - a  at at  t h  ha han and ndc dcu cuf uff ffs fs. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f m  m. m.  . z  za zam amp mpo pol oll llo lo) o)  ) -  -  - a  a  a m  ma man ane net ett tta ta  a #  #3 #36 363 63  3 -  -  - d  da day ay  y o  of of  f t  th the he  e g  gr gra rac ace ce  e c  ch chi hin in  n a  ag aga gai ain in. n.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti  i f  fe fea eat at. t.  . m  m. m.  . z  za zam amp mpo pol oll llo lo) o)  ) -  -  - g  gi gio ior orn rno no  o d  de del el. l.. ... ..  . #  #3 #36 364 64  4 -  -  - h  ho hol old ld  d o  of of  f e  ey eye ye. e.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - t  ti tie ien eni ni  i d  d‚ d‚Ä ‚Äô Äôo ôoc occ cch chi hio io  o #  #3 #36 365 65  5 -  -  - s  st sto top op  p s  st sta tay ayi yin ing ng‚ g‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ -  -  - f  fe fer erm rmo mo  o r  re res est sta tan and ndo do‚ o‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ #  #3 #36 366 66  6 -  -  - t  th the her ere re‚ e‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s w  wa wat ate ter erf rfa fal all ll. l.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of. f.  . s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - c  c‚ c‚Ä ‚Äô Äô√ ô√® √®  ® c  ca cas asc sca cat ata ta  a #  #3 #36 367 67  7 -  -  - p  po pop ope pe‚ e‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s p  po pop ope pe‚ e‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - p  pa pap apa pal ale le  e p  pa pap apa pal ale le  e #  #3 #36 368 68  8 -  -  - e  ey eye ye  e d  do doe oes esn sn‚ n‚Ä ‚Äô Äôt ôt  t s  se see ee  e h  he hea ear art rt  t d  do doe oes esn sn‚ n‚Ä ‚Äô Äôt ôt  t h  hu hur urt rt. t.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f t  t. t.  . l  lo los osc sch chi hi) i)  ) -  -  - o  oc occ cch chi hi  i n  no non on  n v  ve ved ede de  e c  cu cuo uor ore re  e n  no non on  n d  du duo uol ole le  e #  #3 #36 369 69  9 -  -  - i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôm ôm  m a  at at  t t  th the he  e j  jo joi oin int nt  t o  of of  f g  ga gas as. s.  . -  -  - s  so son ono no  o a  al all lla la  a c  ca can ann nna na  a d  de del el  l g  ga gas as  s #  #3 #37 371 71  1 -  -  - w  wa wai ait it  t a  an and nd  d h  ho hop ope pe. e.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - a  as asp spe pet ett tta ta  a e  e  e s  sp spe per era ra  a i  i  i l  li lik ike ked ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o m  ma mar arc rc  c r  ri rib ibo bot ot' t's 's  s c  ce cer era ram ami mic ic  c d  do dog og  g -  -  - l  li lie ies es  s m  my my  y b  bo bod ody dy  y t  to tol old ld  d m  me me  e #  #3 #37 374 74  4 -  -  - a  am amo mou oun unt nts ts  s t  th thr hro row owi win ing ng. g.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - t  ti tir ira rar are re  e l  le le  e s  so som omm mme me  e #  #3 #37 375 75  5 -  -  - n  ne ner erv rve ves es  s a  at at  t f  fl flo low owe wer er  r o  of of  f s  sk ski kin in. n.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - n  ne ner erv rvi vi  i a  a  a f  fi fio ior or  r d  di di  i p  pe pel ell lle le  e i  i  i l  li lik ike ked ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o j  ja jaz azz zze zed ed  d o  ou out ut  t o  os osl slo lo  o -  -  - d  da day ays ys  s i  in int nto to  o n  no nor orw rwe weg egi gia ian an  n j  ja jaz azz zz  z #  #3 #37 376 76  6 -  -  - w  wh whe hen en  n i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôm ôm  m h  ho hom ome me  e i  i  i h  hi hit it  t y  yo you ou  u w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the he  e p  ph pho hon one ne. e.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f h  hi his is  s m  ma maj aje jes est sty ty  y r  r. r.  . d  de del el  l n  ne ner ero ro) o)  ) -  -  - q  qu qua uan and ndo do  o s  so son ono no  o a  a  a c  ca cas asa sa  a t  ti ti. i.. ... ..  . #  #3 #37 378 78  8 -  -  - d  do don on‚ n‚Ä ‚Äô Äôt ôt  t d  do do  o t  th the he  e f  fa fal all lli lin ing ngd gde dea ead ad. d.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . a  am ame men end ndo dol ola lag agi gin ine ne) e)  ) -  -  - n  no non on  n f  fa far are re  e i  il il  l c  ca cas asc sca cam amo mor ort rto to¬ o¬† ¬†  † #  #3 #37 379 79  9 -  -  - l  li lik ike ke  e i  if if  f n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g i  it it  t w  wo wou oul uld ld  d b  be be. e.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  co com ome me  e s  se se  e n  ni nie ien ent nte te  e f  fo fos oss sse se  e i  i  i l  li lik ike ked ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o h  hi him ima mal ala lay aya ya  a s  sp spe pee eed ed  d p  pa par art rt  t 2  2: 2:  : c  cl cli lim imb mbi bin ing ng  g c  ch cho hol ola lat ats tse se  e #  #3 #38 380 80  0 -  -  - b  bu buy uyp ypu put ut. t.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f c  c. c.  . g  ga gat att tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  co com omp mpr pro rom ome mes ess sso so  o #  #3 #38 381 81  1 -  -  - i  it it  t m  ma mak ake kes es  s m  me me  e f  fr fro rot oth thi hin ing ng. g.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - m  mi mi  i f  fa fa  a s  sc sch chi hiu ium uma mar are re  e #  #3 #38 382 82  2 -  -  - a  as ass ss  s a  an and nd  d s  sh shi hir irt rt. t.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  cu cul ulo lo  o e  e  e c  ca cam ami mic ici cia ia  a #  #3 #38 383 83  3 -  -  - e  ev eve ver ery ry  y h  ho hol ole le  e i  is is  s t  tu tun unn nne nel el. l.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f r  r. r.  . b  bi big igi gio iol oll lli li) i)  ) -  -  - o  og ogn gni ni  i b  bu buc uco co  o √  √® √®  ® g  ga gal all lle ler eri ria ia  a #  #3 #38 385 85  5 -  -  - w  we we  e a  ar are re  e c  ch cha har arg rge ged ed! d!  ! (  (d (d. d.  . g  ge ger eru rus uss ssi si  i f  fe fea eat at. t.  . w  w. w.  . a  an ang nge gel eli lin ini ni) i)  ) -  -  - s  si sia iam amo mo  o c  ca car ari ric ich chi hi! i!  ! #  #3 #38 386 86  6 -  -  - t  th the hey ey  y a  ar are re  e a  al all ll  l f  fe fen enn nne nel els ls  s w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the he  e o  ot oth the her ers rs‚ s‚Ä ‚Äô Äô  ô a  as ass sse ses es. s.  . -  -  - s  so son on  n t  tu tut utt tti ti  i f  fi fin ino noc occ cch chi hi  i c  co col ol  l c  cu cul ulo lo  o d  de deg egl gli li  i a  al alt ltr tri ri  i #  #3 #38 388 88  8 -  -  - a  at at  t b  bu bur urn rn  n f  fu fur ur. r.  . -  -  - a  a  a b  br bru ruc uci cia ia  a p  pe pel elo lo  o i  i  i l  li lik ike ked ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o m  mt mt  t e  ev eve ver ere res est st  t i  im ima max ax  x -  -  - t  th the he  e d  dr dre rea eam am  m i  is is  s a  al ali liv ive ve  e #  #3 #38 389 89  9 -  -  - f  fr fro rom om  m w  wh whe hen en  n t  to to  o h  he her ere re! e!? !?  ? -  -  - d  da da  a q  qu qua uan and ndo do  o i  in in  n q  qu qua ua! a!? !?  ? #  #3 #39 390 90  0 -  -  - a  a  a l  lo lot ot  t o  of of  f s  st stu tuf uff ff! f!  ! (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . a  am ame men end ndo dol ola lag agi gin ine ne) e)  ) -  -  - t  ta tan ant nta ta  a r  ro rob oba ba! a!  ! #  #3 #39 391 91  1 -  -  - f  fr fro rom om  m t  th the her ere re  e t  to to  o l  li lit itt ttl tle le. e.  . -  -  - d  di di  i l  l√ l√¨ √¨  ¨ a  a  a p  po poc oco co  o #  #3 #39 392 92  2 -  -  - s  sm smi mil ili lin ing ng  g t  ti tin iny ny  y c  ci cit ity ty. y.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - r  ri rid ide den ent nte te  e c  ci cit itt tta tad adi din ina na  a #  #3 #39 393 93  3 -  -  - f  fu fun une ner era ral al  l b  bl blo low owj wjo job obs bs. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . a  am ame men end ndo dol ola lag agi gin ine ne) e)  ) -  -  - p  po pom omp mpe pe  e f  fu fun une neb ebr bri ri  i #  #3 #39 394 94  4 -  -  - b  bi big ig  g w  wo wor ord rds ds  s a  ar are re  e f  fl fly lyi yin ing ng. g.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - v  vo vol ola lan ano no  o p  pa par aro rol ole le  e g  gr gro ros oss sse se  e #  #3 #39 395 95  5 -  -  - a  at at  t f  fr fre ree ee  e w  wh whe hee eel el. l.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - a  a  a r  ru ruo uot ota ta  a l  li lib ibe ber era ra  a #  #3 #39 396 96  6 -  -  - h  he he  e t  to too ook ok  k i  it it  t u  un und nde der er  r t  th the he  e l  le leg eg. g.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f f  f. f.  . p  pa pal all lla lav avi vid idi din ini ni) i)  ) -  -  - l  l‚ l‚Ä ‚Äô Äôh ôha ha  a p  pr pre res esa sa  a s  so sot ott tto to  o g  ga gam amb mba ba  a #  #3 #39 397 97  7 -  -  - t  to to  o o  ow owl wl. l.  . -  -  - g  gu guf ufa far are re  e #  #3 #39 398 98  8 -  -  - t  th the he  e d  dr dro rop op  p t  th tha hat at  t m  ma mak ake kes es  s b  be bet etw twe wee een enm nmo mou out uth th  h t  th the he  e v  va vas ase se. e.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - l  la la  a g  go goc occ cci cia ia  a c  ch che he  e f  fa fa  a t  tr tra rab abo boc occ cca car are re  e i  il il. l.. ... ..  . #  #4 #40 400 00  0 -  -  - w  wo wol olf lf  f i  in in  n t  ta tal ale le. e.  . (  (s (sp spe pec eci cia ial al  l e  ed edi dit iti tio ion on  n c  ce cel ele leb ebr bra rat ati tin ing ng  g t  th the he  e 4  40 400 00t 0th th  h p  po pos ost st) t)  ) -  -  - l  lu lup upu pus us  s i  in in  n f  fa fab abu bul ula la  a #  #4 #40 401 01  1 -  -  - a  at at  t a  al all ll  l r  ro rou oun und nd. d.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - a  a  a t  tu tut utt tto to  o t  to ton ond ndo do  o #  #4 #40 402 02  2 -  -  - t  to to  o i  in inw nwi wis ish sh. h.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - i  in ina nau aug ugu gur ura rar are re  e #  #4 #40 403 03  3 -  -  - o  on on  n e  ev eve ven eni nin ing ng‚ g‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s d  do doi oin ing ng. g.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - s  su sul ul  l f  fa far ar  r d  de del ell lla la  a s  se ser era ra  a #  #4 #40 404 04  4 -  -  - w  wh whi hit it  t t  th the he  e i  if if  f a  an and nd  d w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the he  e b  bu but ut  t y  yo you ou  u d  do don on‚ n‚Ä ‚Äô Äôt ôt  t m  ma mak ake ke  e h  hi his ist sto tor ory ry. y.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f w  w. w.  . a  an ang nge gel eli lin ini ni) i)  ) -  -  - c  co con on  n i  i  i s  se se  e e  e  e c  co con on  n i  i  i m  ma ma. a.. ... ..  . #  #4 #40 405 05  5 -  -  - i  is is  s n  no not ot  t b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l w  wh wha hat at  t i  is is  s b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l b  bu but ut  t i  is is  s b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l w  wh wha hat at  t i  it it‚ t‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s l  li lik ike ked ed. d.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - n  no non on  n √  √® √®  ® b  be bel ell llo lo  o c  ci ci√ i√≤ √≤  ≤ c  ch che he  e √  √® √®  ® b  be bel ell llo lo. o.. ... ..  . #  #4 #40 406 06  6 -  -  - a  an ant nth the hem emg mgo goa oac act cti tio ion on. n.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - i  in inn nno nov ova vaz azi zio ion one ne  e #  #4 #40 408 08  8 -  -  - t  th the her ere re  e w  wa was as  s t  th the he  e h  h. h.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  ce cer era ra  a l  la lac acc cca ca  a #  #4 #40 409 09  9 -  -  - t  ta tak ake ken en  n g  go goo ood od. d.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - p  pr pre res eso so  o b  be ben ene ne  e #  #4 #41 410 10  0 -  -  - t  to to  o p  pa par are ren ent nts ts. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - a  ap app ppa par are ren ent nti ti  i #  #4 #41 411 11  1 -  -  - a  ai air ir‚ r‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s r  ro roo oom om. m.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  ca cam ame mer era ra  a d  d‚ d‚Ä ‚Äô Äôa ôar ari ria ia  a #  #4 #41 412 12  2 -  -  - b  be beh ehi hin ind nd  d t  th the he  e f  fi fif ift fth ths hs. s.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - d  di die iet etr tro ro  o l  le le  e q  qu qui uin int nte te  e b  bo boo oot ots tst str tra rap ap  p p  ps psd sd: d:  : f  fr fre ree ee  e f  fo for or  r c  co com omm mme mer erc rci cia ial al  l a  an and nd  d p  pe per ers rso son ona nal al  l u  us use se! e!  ! b  by by  y #  #4 #41 416 16  6 -  -  - f  fo for or  r d  de dep epa par art rte ted ed  d t  ta tak ake ken en. n.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - p  pe per er  r p  pa par art rti tit ito to  o p  pr pre res eso so  o #  #4 #41 417 17  7 -  -  - i  is is  s l  li lik ike ke  e s  sh sho hoo oot oti tin ing ng  g o  on on  n t  th the he  e r  re red ed  d c  cr cro ros oss ss. s.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -¬ -¬† ¬†√ †√® √®  ® c  co com ome me  e s  sp spa par ara rar are re  e s  su sul ull lla la  a c  cr cro roc oce ce  e r  ro ros oss ssa sa  a #  #4 #41 418 18  8 -  -  - g  go go  o t  to to  o m  ma mak ake ke  e y  yo you our urs rse sel elf lf  f w  we wel ell lls lsa say ay. y.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - v  va va‚ a‚Ä ‚Äô Äô  ô a  a  a f  fa far art rti ti  i b  be ben ene ned edi dir ire re  e #  #4 #41 419 19  9 -  -  - t  th the he  e b  bi big ig  g w  wi wiz iza zar ard rd. d.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - i  il il  l m  ma mag ago gon one ne  e #  #4 #42 423 23  3 -  -  - h  hu hun und ndr dre red eds dst sth the her ere reb ebo bor orn rn. n.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  ce cen ent nte tel ell lli lin ina nat ata ta  a #  #4 #42 426 26  6 -  -  - s  se sen ent nt  t i  in in  n w  wa wav ave ve. e.  . -  -  - m  ma man and nda dat ato to  o i  in in  n o  on ond nda da  a #  #4 #42 427 27  7 -  -  - t  to to  o d  dr dri rin ink nk  k a  at at  t t  th the he  e d  dr dro rop op. p.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - b  be ber ere re  e a  al all lla la  a g  go goc occ cci cia ia  a #  #4 #42 428 28  8 -  -  - a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s a  an and nd  d a  an any nyw ywa way ay. y.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - s  se sem emp mpr pre re  e e  e  e c  co com omu mun unq nqu que ue  e #  #4 #42 429 29  9 -  -  - i  if if  f y  yo you ou  u p  pu put ut  t o  on on  n t  th thi his is  s f  fl flo loo oor or. r.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - s  se se  e l  la la  a m  me met ett tti ti  i s  su su  u q  qu que ues est sto to  o p  pi pia ian ano no  o h  ho ho  o a  ag agg ggi giu iun unt nto to  o u  un un  n v  vi vid ide deo eo  o a  a  a u  un una na  a p  pl pla lay ayl yli lis ist st  t d  di di  i :  :  : k  k2 k2  2 -  -  - t  th the he  e k  ki kil ill lle ler er  r s  su sum umm mmi mit it  t (  (b (bb bbc bc  c f  fo fou our ur  r -  -  - s  st sto tor ory ryv yvi vil ill lle le  e -  -  - 2  20 201 014 14) 4)  ) #  #4 #43 433 33  3 -  -  - g  gi giv ive ve  e t  ti tim ime me  e t  to to  o w  we wea eat ath the her er. r.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - d  da dai ai  i t  te tem emp mpo po  o a  al al  l t  te tem emp mpo po  o #  #4 #43 434 34  4 -  -  - d  do do  o n  no not ot  t t  th thr hro row ow  w t  th the he  e s  st sto ton one ne  e a  an and nd  d t  th the hen en  n h  hi hid ide de  e t  th the he  e h  ha han and nd. d.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - n  no non on  n l  la lan anc nci cia iar are re  e l  la la  a p  pi pie iet etr tra ra  a e  e  e p  po poi oi. i.. ... ..  . #  #4 #43 437 37  7 -  -  - a  a  a b  ba bar arl rli lig igh ght ht. t.  . -  -  - u  un un  n b  ba bar arl rlu lum ume me  e -  -  - u  un unc nch cha hai ain ine ned ed. d.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äúu úun unc nch cha hai ain ine ned ed‚ d‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - s  sc sca cat ate ten ena nat ato to  o #  #4 #44 441 41  1 -  -  - r  ro rot ott tte ten enf nfo foo oot ot. t.  . -  -  - m  ma mar arc rci cia iap api pie ied ede de  e #  #4 #44 442 42  2 -  -  - r  ra rat ath the her er  r t  ti tim ime me. e.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - a  an anz nzi zit ite tem emp mpo po  o #  #4 #44 443 43  3 -  -  - w  wi win ind nd  d i  in in  n b  bo boo oob ob. b.  . -  -  - v  ve ven ent nto to  o i  in in  n p  po pop opp ppa pa a 