afte fter ter  er w r wr  wri writ riti itin ting ing  ng v g vo  vol volu olum lume umes mes  es o s of  of  of " f "m  "my "my  my w y wa  wat watc atch tch" ch"  h" o " on  one one  ne w e wo  wou woul ould uld  ld t d th  thi thin hink ink  nk h k he  he  he n e ne  nev neve ever ver  er w r wa  wan want ants nts  ts t s to  to  to s o se  see see  ee g e ge  gej gej  ej e j ev  eve ever ver  er c r co  cos cos  os h s he  he' he's e's  's t s th  the the  he d e de  dev devi evil vil, il,  l, b , bu  but but  ut a t al  ala alas las. as.. s... ...  .. " . "i  "in "int inte nter tere eres rest est" st"  t" = " =   = p = po  pol poli olit liti itic tics ics! cs!  s! s ! si  sig sigh igh! gh!  h! : ! :   : b : bi  big big  ig h g hy  hyp hypo ypoc pocr ocri crit rite ite  te k e ku  kuw kuwa uwa. wa.r a.rt .rt  rt : t :   : o : ob  obj obj, bj,  j, s , su  suc such uch  ch a h a   a h a hy  hyp hypo ypoc pocr ocri crit rite ite! te!‚ e!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù su  suc such uch  ch a h an  an  an e n ev  evi evil vil  il a l an  and and  nd v d vi  vil vile ile  le m e ma  man man  an w n wh  who who  ho t o th  thi thin hink inks nks  ks h s he  he  he c e ca  can can  an l n li  liv live ive  ve f e fo  for fore orev reve ever ver! er!  r! s ! sm  smh smh  mh a h an  and and  nd s d se  sen sens ense nsel sele eles less ess! ss!  s! s ! sm  smh smh  mh : h :   : g : ge  gej gej  ej a j an  and and  nd h d hi  his his  is p s po  poi poin oint intl ntle tles less ess  ss c s ca  cam camp ampa mpai paig aign igns gns. ns.‚ s.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù in  ind inde ndee deed eed! ed!  d! : ! :   : j : ju  jus just ust  st a t a   a p a po  pol poli olit liti itic tici icia cian ian. an.  n. a . as  as  as a s an  any any  ny o y ot  oth othe ther her. er.‚ r.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù am  ame amee meen een  en a n am  ame amee meen een! en!  n! h ! ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay b y br  bro brot roth othe ther her! er!  r! a ! al  all alla llah lah' ah's h's  's k s kh  kha khai hair air  ir : r :   : i : i'  i'm i'm  'm o m of  off offi ffic fici icia cial iall ally lly  ly y y ye  yea year ears ars  rs o s ol  old old. ld.  d. a . al  all alla llah lah  ah y h ya  ya  ya r a ra  ray raya aya  ya n a ni  ni  ni d i da  da  da k a ko  kow kowa owa. wa.  a. i . i   i n i ne  nee need eed  ed f d fe  feb febr ebru brua ruar uary ary  ry t y to  to  to e o en  end end! nd!  d! : ! :   : u : u   u n u ne  nee need eed  ed n d ne  nex next ext  xt w t we  wee week eek  ek t k to  to  to e o en  end end. nd.  d. u . u   u s u sa  say say? ay?  y? : ? :   : a : am  am  am a m al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys c s ca  car care ares res  es w s wi  wit with ith  th g h gi  gir girl irls rls  ls b s be  bec beca ecau caus ause use  se o e of  of  of t f th  the the  he p e pa  pai pain ains ins  ns t s th  the they hey  ey s y su  suf suff uffe ffer fer  er f r fr  fro from rom  om ? m ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù m ù me  mee meen eena ena  na w a we  wel weld eldo ldon done one  ne ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : b : bu  but but  ut w t wh  why why? hy?  y? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  har hard ard  rd g d gu  guy guy  uy b y bu  but but  ut y t yo  you you  ou d u de  dey dey  ey p y pl  pla play lay  ay c y ca  can cand andy ndy  dy c y cr  cru crus rush ush. sh.‚ h.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù " ù "‚  "‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lm  lma lmao mao  ao : o :   : t : te  te. te.. e... ...r ..re .re. re.. e... ...b ..bl .ble ble  le r e rt  rt  rt : t :   : u : u   u s u sa  say say? ay?  y? : ? :   : a : am  am  am a m al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys c s ca  car care ares res  es w s wi  wit with ith  th g h gi  gir girl irls rls  ls b s be  bec beca ecau caus ause use  se o e of  of  of t f th  the the  he p e pa  pai pain ains ins  ns t s th  the they hey  ey s y su  suf suff uffe ffer fer  er f r fr  fro from rom  om ? m ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù‚ Äù‚Ä ù‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i m i mu  mus must ust  st a t as  asw aswe swea wear ear! ar!  r! m ! mo  mov move ovee veee eeee eeee eeee eeee eee  ee ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???: ??:  ?: h : ha  har hard ard  rd g d gu  guy guy  uy b y bu  buh buh  uh y h yo  you you  ou k u kn  kno know now  ow g w ge  get get  et b t be  bea bear eard ards rds  ds . s .   . d . do  don don' on't n't  't m t me  me  me : e :|  :|  :| s | so  som some ome  me o e of  of  of y f yo  you you  ou a u ar  are are  re s e su  sub subb ubbi bbin bing ing  ng y g yo  you your ours urse rsel selv elve lves ves  es s s sh  sha sha. ha.. a..  .. ? . ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": s : so  som some ome  me o e of  of  of y f yo  you you  ou a u ar  are are  re s e su  sub subb ubbi bbin bing ing  ng y g yo  you your ours urse rsel selv elve lves ves  es s s sh  sha sha. ha.. a.." .."‚ ."‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ! ù !!  !!! !!!  !! : ! :   : e : en  end end  nd o d of  of  of d f di  dis disc iscu scus cuss ussi ssio sion ion! on!! n!!  !! r ! rt  rt  rt : t :   : r : rt  rt  rt : t :   : e : ev  eve even ven  en t n th  the the  he h e ha  har hard arde rdes dest est  st o t of  of  of g f gu  guy guys uys  ys a s ar  are are  re s e so  sof soft oft  ft f t fo  for for  or s r so  som some omeo meon eone one. ne.‚ e.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lov love ove  ve y e yo  you you  ou m u mo  mor more ore  re d e da  dar darl arl  rl ? l ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : j : ju  jus just ust  st m t ma  mad made ade  de m e my  my  my d y da  day day. ay.  y. i . i   i l i lo  lov love ove  ve y e yo  you you  ou d u da  dar darl arli rlin ling ing  ng ? g ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù g ù go  god god! od!  d! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": b : bo  bos boss oss  ss c s ch  chi chic hick ick  ck b k bo  bos boss oss  ss c s ch  chi chic hick ick  ck b k bu  but but  ut u t u   u s u st  sti stil till ill  ll d l de  dey dey  ey g y ge  get get  et m t me  men mens enst nstr stru trua rual ual  al c l cr  cra cram ramp amps mps  ps : s :p  :p" :p"‚ p"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i a i ai  ain ain' in't n't  't n t no  no  no b o bo  bos boss oss  ss c s ch  chi chic hick ick  ck o k or  or  or b r bo  bos boss oss  ss l s la  lad lady ady, dy,  y, n , ne  nev neve ever ver  er b r be  bee been een  en a n ab  abe abeg beg! eg!  g! n ! no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng w g wr  wro wron rong ong  ng w g wi  wit with ith  th s h so  sof soft oft. ft.. t..  .. e . ev  eve even ven  en i n if  if  if n f na  na  na s a so  sof soft oft  ft g t gu  guy guy, uy,  y, n , no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng w g wr  wro wron rong ong  ng w g wi  wit with ith  th t h th  tha that hat  at ? t ??  ??? ???  ?? s ? sm  smh smh  mh : h :   : h : ha  har hard ard  rd g d gu  guy guy  uy b y bu  but but  ut y t yo  you you  ou n u no  no  no f o fi  fit fit  it p t pl  pla play lay  ay t y tw  two two  wo c o ch  chi chic hics ics‚ cs‚Ä s‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lol lol! ol!  l! s ! st  sti stil till ill  ll n l no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng w g wr  wro wron rong ong  ng w g wi  wit with ith  th t h th  the them hem  em : m :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? so  sof soft oft  ft g t gu  guy guys uys  ys a s ar  are are  re j e ju  jus just ust  st s t so  so  so . o ..  ... .... .... .... .... .... ...  .. s . so  sof soft oft  ft ‚ t ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù ah  ah! ah!  h! : ! :   : t : th  the they hey  ey s y sp  spe spea peak eak  ak l k li  lik like ike  ke g e gi  gir girl irls rls  ls o s on  on  on p n ph  pho phon hone one  ne ‚ e ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù so  som some ome  me g e gu  guy guy  uy j y ju  jus just ust  st s t su  sub sub' ub'd b'd  'd s d so  som some omeo meon eone one  ne w e wi  wit with ith  th o h on  one one  ne o e of  of  of t f th  the thes hese ese  se h e ha  har hard ard  rd g d gu  guy guy  uy t y tw  twe twee weet eet  et & t &   & d & de  del dele elet lete eted ted  ed i d it  it  it b t be  bef befo efor fore ore  re t e th  the the  he o e ot  oth othe ther her  er g r gu  guy guy  uy c y co  cou coul ould uld  ld s d se  see see. ee.. e..  .. h . ha  har hard ard  rd g d gu  guy guy  uy i y in  ind inde ndee deed eed! ed!  d! w ! we  we  we d e de  dey dey  ey o y ob  obs obse bser serv erve rve  ve ? e ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? o ? or  or  or n r ni  nig nige iger geri eria ria! ia!  a! : ! :   : w : wo  wor worl orld rld  ld l d le  lea lead eade ader ders ers  rs m s ma  mar marc arch rch  ch a h af  aft afte fter ter  er k r ki  kil kill illi llin ling ing  ng o g of  of  of a f a   a c a co  cou coup oupl uple ple  le o e of  of  of r f ra  rac raci acis cist ist  st c t ca  car cart arto rtoo toon ooni onis nist ists sts  ts i s in  in  in f n fr  fra fran ranc ance nce  ce b e bu  but but  ut n t no  not not  ot f t fo  for for  or k r ki  kil kill illi llin ling ing  ng o g of  of  of 1 f 10  100 1000 000s 00s  0s o s of  of  of i f i   i i i i   i t i ti  tir tire ire  re : e :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  har hard ard  rd b d ba  bab babe abe  be b e bu  but but  ut n t no  not not  ot a t a   a s a si  sin sing ingl ngle gle  le t e to  toa toas oast aste ster ter. er.  r. . . .   . . . .‚  .‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù n ù na  na  na b a br  bre brea read ead? ad?‚ d?‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù li  lik like ike  ke s e sm  smh smh  mh : h :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": g : go  god god! od!  d! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": b : bo  bos boss oss  ss c s ch  chi chic hick ick  ck b k bo  bos boss oss  ss c s ch  chi chic hick ick  ck b k bu  but but  ut u t u   u s u st  sti stil till ill  ll d l de  dey dey  ey g y ge  get get  et m t me  men mens enst nstr stru trua rual ual  al c l cr  cra cram ramp amps mps  ps : s :p  :p" :p"‚ p"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù" Äù"‚ ù"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù g ù gi  giv give ive  ve m e me  me  me l e lo  lov love ove  ve l e li  lik like ike  ke n e ne  nev neve ever ver  er b r be  bef befo efor fore ore, re,  e, c , co  cos cos  os l s la  lat late atel tely ely  ly i y i'  i'v i've 've  ve b e be  bee been een  en c n cr  cra crav ravi avin ving ing  ng f g fo  for for  or m r mo  mor more ore  re ? e ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? s ? so  som some ome  me m e me  men men  en a n ar  are are  re i e in  int inte nter tere eres rest esti stin ting ing  ng s g sh  sha sha  ha ? a ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? q ? qu  qui quic uick ick  ck q k qu  que ques uest esti stio tion ion: on:  n: w : wh  why why  hy c y ca  can can' an't n't  't s t so  som some ome  me m e me  men men  en m n ma  mar marr arry rry  ry w y wi  wiv wive ives ves  es t s th  the they hey  ey c y ca  can can  an d n do  do  do s o so  som some ome  me o e ou  out out  ut d t do  doo door oor  or a r ac  act acti ctiv tivi ivit viti itie ties ies  es t s to  tog toge oget geth ethe ther her  er b r bu  but but  ut y t yo  you you  ou c u ca  can can  an w n wi  wit with ith  th y h yo  you your our  ur g r gf  gf? gf?  f? t ? tf  tf  tf ? f ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? a ? am  am  am d m di  dis disg isgu sgus gust uste sted ted  ed r d re  rea real eall ally lly! ly!  y! n ! no  not not  ot a t a   a m a my  mys myst yste ster tery ery, ry,  y, j , ju  jus just ust  st n t nu  nun nuna una  na i a is  isa isa  sa n a ne  ne  ne k e ka  kaw kawa awai wai  ai f i fo  for for  or s r so  som some ome  me o e of  of  of t f th  the them hem  em : m :   : s : st  sti stil till ill  ll r l re  rem rema emai main ains ins  ns a s a   a m a my  mys myst yste ster tery ery‚ ry‚Ä y‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù m ù ma  mar marr arry rry  ry a y a   a w a wi  wif wife ife  fe y e yo  you you  ou c u ca  can can  an p n pr  pre pres rese esen sent ent  nt t t to  to  to e o ev  eve ever very eryb rybo ybod body ody! dy!  y! p ! pa  par pare aren rent ents nts, ts,  s, f , fa  fam fami amil mily ily, ly,  y, f , fr  fri frie rien iend ends nds, ds,  s, b , bu  bus busi usin sine ines ness ess  ss a s as  ass asso ssoc soci ocia ciat iate ates tes  es & s &   & c & ca  can can  an e n ev  eve even ven  en s n st  stu stun tun  un e n en  ene enem nemi emie mies ies! es!  s! y ! ye  yes yes  es o s o!  o!  o! : ! :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú  Äú m ú ma  mar marr arry rry  ry a y a   a w a wi  wif wife ife  fe y e yo  you you  ou c u ca  can can  an p n pr  pre pres rese esen sent ent  nt t t to  to  to e o ev  eve ever very eryb rybo ybod body ody! dy!  y! p ! pa  par pare aren rent ents nts, ts,  s, f , fa  fam fami amil mily ily, ly,  y, f , fr  fri frie rien iend ends nds, ds,  s, b , bu  bus busi usin sine ines ness ess  ss a s as  ass asso ssoc soci ocia ciat iate ates tes  es & s &   & c & ca  can can! an!‚ n!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lou loud oud  ud i d it  it! it!! t!!‚ !!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù so  sos sosa osai sai  ai k i ka  kam kam  am : m :   : m : mo  mos most ost  st o t of  of  of t f th  the them hem  em d m do  don don' on't n't  't u t un  und unde nder ders erst rsta stan tand and  nd t d th  the the  he v e va  val valu alue lue  ue o e of  of  of m f ma  mar marr arri rria riag iage age  ge t e th  tha that hats ats  ts t s th  the the  he m e ma  maj majo ajor jor  or p r pr  pro prob robl oble blem lem‚ em‚Ä m‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù a   a w a wi  wif wife ife  fe y e yo  you you  ou c u ca  can can  an p n pr  pre pres rese esen sent ent  nt t t to  to  to y o yo  you your our  ur f r fa  fam fami amil mily ily  ly i y is  is  is e s ex  exc exce xcel cell elle llen lent ent  nt o t oh  oh. oh.. h... ...  .. b . bu  but but  ut p t pl  ple plea leas ease ase  se g e go  go  go a o ah  ahe ahea head ead  ad a d an  and and  nd g d ge  get get  et a t a   a w a wi  wif wife ife  fe t e th  tha that hat  at c t ca  can can  an s n se  ser serv erve rve  ve a e al  all all  ll o l or  or  or m r mo  mos most ost  st o t of  of  of y f yo  you your our  ur p r pu  pur purp urpo rpos pose oses ses! es!  s! d ! do  don don' on't n't  't k t ke  kee keep eep  ep y p yo  you your our  ur w r wi  wif wife ife  fe a e at  at  at h t ho  hom home ome  me a e an  and and  nd g d go  go  go " o "b  "bo "bor borr orro rrow rowi owin wing ing" ng"  g" e " el  elo eloq loqu oque quen uent ent  nt o t or  or  or a r as  as  as t s th  the they hey  ey s y sa  say say  ay " y "p  "po "pol poli olis lish ishe shed hed" ed"  d" w " wo  wom woma oman man  an t n to  to  to p o pr  pre pres rese esen sent ent  nt t t to  to  to t o th  the the  he w e wo  wor worl orld rld! ld!  d! j ! ju  jus just ust  st s t st  sto stop top  op ? p ?   ? l ? lo  lol lol! ol!  l! u ! u   u h u ha  hav have ave  ve m e mi  mis miss isse ssed sed  ed t d th  the the  he p e po  poi poin oint int! nt!  t! i ! i   i m i me  mea mean ean  an a n a   a p a pr  pre pres rese esen sent enta ntab tabl able ble  le w e wi  wif wife ife  fe f e fo  for for  or a r al  all all  ll o l oc  occ occa ccas casi asio sion ions ons  ns & s &   & s & so  som some omet meti etim time imes mes  es m s mu  mul mult ulti ltip tipu ipur purp urpo rpos pose ose  se s e se  sef sef  ef : f :   : # : #w  #wi #wif wife ifen feno enot notm otmu tmul mult ulti ltip tipu ipur purp urpo rpos pose oset seto etoo too  oo i o i   i d i do  don don' on't n't  't g t ge  get get  et w t wh  why why  hy t y th  the they hey  ey s y st  sti stil till ill  ll t l th  thi thin hink ink  nk t k th  tha that hat  at w t wa  way way  ay w y wa  wal wall alla llah lahi ahi! hi!  i! i ! if  if  if t f th  the they hey  ey r y re  res resp espe spec pect ect  ct t t th  the them hems emse msel selv elve lves ves, es,  s, a , a   a w a wo  wom woma oman man  an w n wi  wil will ill  ll s l su  sur sure ure  re r e re  res resp espe spec pect ect  ct t t th  the them hem  em n m no  no  no m o ma  mat matt atte tter ter  er w r wh  wha what hat! at!  t! l ! lm  lma lmao mao  ao i o i   i k i kn  kno know now  ow n w na  na  na : a :p  :p  :p : p :   : l : lo  loo looo oool ool. ol.  l. i . i   i w i wa  was was  as m s me  mes mess essi ssin sing ing  ng w g wi  wit with ith  th y h ya  ya  ya ; a ;)  ;)  ;) ‚ ) ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù ag  agr agre gree ree  ee t e to  to  to d o di  dis disa isag sagr agre gree ree  ee r e re  res resp espe spec pect ectf ctfu tful full ully lly! ly!  y! o ! on  onl only nly  ly m y me  men men  en w n wi  wit with ith  th n h na  nap napo apol pole oleo leon eon  on c n co  com comp ompl mple plex lex  ex t x th  tha that hat  at w t wa  wan want ant  nt t t th  the thei heir eir  ir e r eg  ego ego  go w o wo  wor wors orsh rshi ship hipe iped ped  ed w d wi  wil will ill  ll t l te  tel tell ell  ll y l yo  you you  ou a u a   a w a wo  wom woma oman man  an i n is  is  is " s "t  "to "too too  oo p o po  pol poli olis lish ishe shed hed" ed"  d" # " #b  #be #beg bego egon gone one  ne j e ju  jus just ust  st h t ha  had had  ad t d to  to  to r o ra  ran rant ant  nt t t th  tha that hat  at o t ou  out out  ut ? t ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? a ? al  all all  ll i l i   i w i wa  wan want ant  nt i t is  is  is t s th  the the  he t e ta  tas tast aste ste  te t e th  tha that hat  at y t yo  you your our  ur l r li  lip lips ips  ps a s al  all allo llow low  ow ? w ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? l ? lm  lma lmao mao  ao t o th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you  ou k u ko  ko  ko ? o ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: j : ju  jus just ust  st h t ha  had had  ad t d to  to  to r o ra  ran rant ant  nt t t th  tha that hat  at o t ou  out out  ut ? t ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù * ù *h  *ha *han hand ands nds  ds h s he  her her  er a r a   a g a gl  gla glas lass ass  ss o s of  of  of c f ch  chi chil hill ille lled led  ed w d wa  wat wate ater ter* er*‚ r*‚Ä *‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : e : ed  ed  ed ? d ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: a : al  all all  ll i l i   i w i wa  wan want ant  nt i t is  is  is t s th  the the  he t e ta  tas tast aste ste  te t e th  tha that hat  at y t yo  you your our  ur l r li  lip lips ips  ps a s al  all allo llow low  ow ? w ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù‚ Äù‚Ä ù‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lol lol  ol : l :   : a : a'  a'a a'a  'a b a ba  ban bans ansa nsan san  an w n wa  was wasa asa  sa ? a ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? " ? ":  ":  ": a : al  all all  ll i l i   i w i wa  wan want ant  nt i t is  is  is t s th  the the  he t e ta  tas tast aste ste  te t e th  tha that hat  at y t yo  you your our  ur l r li  lip lips ips  ps a s al  all allo llow low  ow ? w ??  ??? ???? ???" ??"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  the ther here ere' re's e's  's a s al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys a s a   a t a tw  twe twee weet eet  et o t or  or  or a r a   a s a so  son song ong  ng t g th  tha that hat  at g t go  goe goes oes  es w s wi  wit with ith  th h h ho  how how  ow a w am  am  am f m fe  fee feel eeli elin ling ing  ng e g ev  eve ever very ery  ry t y ti  tim time ime. me.  e. g . go  got got  ot y t yo  you you  ou s u st  stu stuc tuck uck  ck o k on  on  on m n my  my  my b y bo  bod body ody, dy,  y, o , on  on  on m n my  my  my b y bo  bod body ody, dy,  y, l , li  lik like ike  ke a e a   a t a ta  tat tatt atto ttoo too  oo ? o ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? t ? tr  try try  ry t y to  to  to t o te  tel tell ell  ll y l yo  you you  ou " u "n  "no "no" no"  o" b " bu  but but  ut m t my  my  my b y bo  bod body ody  dy k y ke  kee keep eeps eps  ps o s on  on  on t n te  tel tell elli llin ling ing  ng y g yo  you you  ou " u "y  "ye "yes yes" es"  s" ? " ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? t ? tr  try try  ry t y to  to  to t o te  tel tell ell  ll y l yo  you you  ou " u "s  "st "sto stop top" op", p",  ", b , bu  but but  ut y t yo  you your our  ur l r li  lip lips ipst psti stic tick ick  ck g k go  got got  ot m t me  me  me s e so  so  so o o ou  out out  ut o t of  of  of b f br  bre brea reat eath ath  th ? h ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : a : am  amm amma mma  ma m a ma  mak make ake  ke y e yo  you you  ou b u be  beg beg  eg t g ti  til till ill  ll y l yo  you you  ou s u sc  scr scre crea ream eam  am n m na  nag nago agod gode ode  de ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù am  ame amen men  en : n :   : d : de  dea dear ear  ar g r go  god god, od,  d, d , de  del deli eliv live iver ver  er # r #n  #ni #nig nige iger geri eria ria  ia f a fr  fro from rom  om p m ps  psy psyc sych ycho chop hopa opat path aths ths, hs,  s, e , eg  ego egot goti otis tist ists sts  ts a s an  and and  nd s d sc  sch schi chiz hizo izop zoph ophr phre hren reni enic nics ics  cs ‚ s ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  the the  he m e mo  mom mome omen ment ent  nt | t |   | k | ke  ken kenn enny nny  ny g y g   g ? g ??  ??  ?? t ? th  tha that hat  at s t so  som some omeb mebo ebod body ody  dy w y wa  was was  as y s yo  you you  ou ? u ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? c ? co  col colo olor lorl orle rles less ess  ss : s :   : w : wh  wha what hat  at c t co  col colo olor lor  or i r is  is  is l s lo  lov love ove? ve?‚ e?‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i a i am  am  am ? m ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : y : yo  you you  ou m u mu  mus must ust  st b t be  be  be a e a   a r a ro  rom roma oman mant anti ntic tic  ic ? c ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : p : po  pou pout out  ut n t na  na  na f a fi  fig figh ight ght? ht?? t??? ???? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lr  lrt lrt  rt w t wh  why why  hy a y ar  are are  re h e he  her her  er e r ey  eye eyes yes  es o s op  ope open pene ened ned  ed t d th  tho tho  ho ? o ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? sh  she she  he s e st  sta stay tays ays  ys s s sh  sha shar harp arp  rp : p :   : m : me  mei mei  ei q i qi  qir qiri iri  ri q i qi  qir qiri iri  ri k i ke  ken kena enan nan  an ? n ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??": ?":  ": l : lr  lrt lrt  rt w t wh  why why  hy a y ar  are are  re h e he  her her  er e r ey  eye eyes yes  es o s op  ope open pene ened ned  ed t d th  tho tho  ho ? o ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???" ??"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù si  sil sile ilen lenc ence nce  ce t e tr  tra tran rans ansl nsla slat late ated ted. ed.. d... ...  .. h . ha  has has  as t s to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a s a sq  squ squa quar uare are  re r e ro  roo root oot  ot o t of  of  of n f ne  neg nega egat gati ativ tive ive  ve z e ze  zer zero ero  ro ? o ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? i ? if  if  if w f we  we  we o e on  onl only nly  ly h y he  hea hear ear  ar t r th  the the  he t e th  thi thin hing ings ngs  gs w s we  we  we w e wa  wan want ant  nt t t to  to  to h o he  hea hear ear, ar,  r, w , we  we  we w e wi  wil will ill  ll n l ne  nev neve ever ver  er k r kn  kno know now  ow t w th  the the  he t e tr  tru trut ruth uth. th.  h. t . ta  tab tab! ab!  b! l ! la  lal lala alai lai  ai ? i ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  has has  as t s to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a s a sq  squ squa quar uare are  re r e ro  roo root oot  ot o t of  of  of n f ne  neg nega egat gati ativ tive ive  ve z e ze  zer zero ero  ro ? o ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù n ù ne  ner nerd erd  rd ? d ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù d ù de  des desi esir sire ires res  es a s an  and and  nd s d se  sec secr ecre cret rets ets, ts,  s, a , ar  are aren ren' en't n't  't e t ea  eas easi asil sily ily  ly s y sh  sha shar hare ared red. ed.  d. i . it  it' it's t's  's a s a   a s a sp  spe spec peci ecia cial ial  al f l fe  fee feel eeli elin ling ing  ng w g wh  whe when hen  en y n yo  you you  ou f u fi  fin find ind  nd s d so  som some omeo meon eone one  ne w e wh  who who  ho d o de  des dese eser serv erve rves ves  es t s th  the them hem. em.  m. t . th  the the  he s e se  sec secr ecre cret ret  et i t in  in  in y n yo  you your our  ur s r sm  smi smil mile ile, le,  e, l , lo  lou loud oud, ud,  d, y , ye  yet yet  et s t so  so  so s o si  sil sile ilen lent ent. nt.. t... ...  .. v . ve  ver very ery  ry w y wr  wro wron rong ong  ng o g o   o ? o ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ? : ??  ??? ???? ???, ??,  ?, w , wr  wro wron rong ong  ng a g as  ass assu ssum sump umpt mpti ptio tion ion‚ on‚Ä n‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  the the  he s e sl  sli slig ligh ight ghte htes test est  st o t of  of  of w f wh  whi whis hisp ispe sper pers ers  rs c s ca  can can  an f n fl  flo flou lour ouri uris rish ish  sh n h ne  neg nega egat gati ativ tivi ivit vity ity, ty,  y, b , be  be  be m e mi  min mind indf ndfu dful ful  ul o l of  of  of w f wh  wha what hat  at y t yo  you you  ou l u li  lis list iste sten ten  en t n to  to. to.  o. b . bu  but but  ut e t eh  ehn ehn  hn ? n ??  ??? ???? ???. ??.. ?... ...  .. : . :   : e : ei  eit eith ithe ther her  er a r a   a n a ne  ner nerd erd  rd o d or  or  or a r an  an  an i n in  int inte ntel tell elle llec lect ectu ctua tual ual, al,  l, u , u   u g u go  got gott otta tta  ta c a ch  cho choo hoos oose ose  se o e on  one one  ne ? e ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù so  som some omet meti etim time imes mes  es i s i   i g i gi  giv give ive  ve m e my  mys myse ysel self elf  lf t f th  the the  he s e si  sil sile ilen lent ent  nt t t tr  tre trea reat eatm atme tmen ment ent  nt j t ju  jus just ust  st b t be  bec beca ecau caus ause use  se w e we  we  we c e ca  can can  an b n be  be  be o e ou  our our  ur o r ow  own own  wn e n en  ene enem nemy emy  my s y so  som some omet meti etim time imes mes. es.  s. t . th  the the  he n e ni  nig nigh ight ght  ht i t is  is  is n s no  not not  ot c t cl  cle clea lear ear, ar,  r, t , th  the the  he s e st  sta star tars ars  rs s s se  see seem eem  em s m so  so  so f o fa  far far  ar a r aw  awa away way. ay.  y. a . ab  abi abi  bi : i :   : # : #d  #de #dee deep eep  ep " p ":  ":  ": t : th  the the  he s e se  sec secr ecre cret ret  et i t in  in  in y n yo  you your our  ur s r sm  smi smil mile ile, le,  e, l , lo  lou loud oud, ud,  d, y , ye  yet yet  et s t so  so  so s o si  sil sile ilen lent ent. nt.. t... ..." .."‚ ."‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : # : #g  #gb #gba gbam bam  am " m ":  ":  ": i : if  if  if w f we  we  we o e on  onl only nly  ly h y he  hea hear ear  ar t r th  the the  he t e th  thi thin hing ings ngs  gs w s we  we  we w e wa  wan want ant  nt t t to  to  to h o he  hea hear ear, ar,  r, w , we  we  we w e wi  wil will ill  ll n l ne  nev neve ever ver  er k r kn  kno know now  ow t w th  the the  he t e tr  tru trut ruth uth. th." h."‚ ."‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù o ù on  on  on c n cl  cle clea lear ear  ar n r ni  nig nigh ight ghts hts, ts,  s, t , th  the they hey  ey s y se  see seem eem  em s m so  so  so c o cl  clo clos lose ose  se t e to  to  to u o us  us. us.. s..  .. w . we  we  we s e sh  sho shou houl ould uld  ld d d de  def defi efin fine ine  ne o e ou  our our  ur f r fl  fla flaw laws aws  ws i s in  ins inst nste stea tead ead  ad o d of  of  of h f hi  hid hidi idin ding ing  ng t g th  the them hem, em,  m, i , it  it  it i t is  is  is m s mo  mor more ore  re l e li  lib libe iber bera erat rati atin ting ing. ng.  g. n . no  not not  ot a t a   a p a pr  pri prin rinc ince nces cess ess  ss o s or  or  or a r al  all all  ll t l th  tha that hat  at b t bu  but but  ut w t wo  wor wort orth rthy thy  hy o y of  of  of a f a   a k a ki  kin king ings ngs  gs l s lo  lov love ove  ve ? e ??  ??  ?? z ? ze  zer zero ero  ro e o ex  exp expe xpec pect ecta ctat tati atio tion ions ons  ns h s he  hel help elp! lp!  p! : ! :   : i : ir  iro iron roni onic nic  ic h c ho  how how  ow i w i   i k i ke  kee keep eep  ep t p ta  tal talk alki lkin king ing  ng a g ab  abo abou bout out  ut p t pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le l e le  let lett etti ttin ting ing  ng m g me  me  me d e do  dow down own, wn,  n, a , an  and and  nd i d i   i k i ke  kee keep eep  ep l p le  let lett etti ttin ting ing  ng t g th  the them hem  em l m le  let let  et m t me  me  me d e do  dow down own. wn.  n. t . th  tha that hat' at's t's  's h s ho  how how  ow " w "i  "i  "i l i li  liv live ive" ve"  e" : " :   : t : th  tha that hat' at's t's  's h s ho  how how  ow i w i   i a i al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys c s co  con cons onso nsol sole ole  le m e my  mys myse ysel self elf‚ lf‚Ä f‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù w ù we  we  we a e ar  are are  re o e on  onl only nly  ly h y hu  hum huma uman man, an,  n, w , we  we  we c e ca  can can' an't n't  't h t he  hel help elp  lp i p it  it  it s t so  som some omet meti etim time imes mes  es ? s ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : m : me  me  me t e to  too too! oo!  o! d ! du  dun dunn unno nno  no w o wh  why why  hy i y i   i l i le  let let  et i t it  it  it b t bo  bot both othe ther her  er m r me  me  me ? e ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lol lol, ol,  l, n , no  not not  ot l t li  lit lite iter tera eral rall ally lly  ly : y :   : * : *c  *ch *cha chan hang ange nges ges  es n s na  nam name ame  me t e to  to  to s o sa  san sanu anus nusi usi  si j i jn  jnr jnr, nr,y r,yo ,you you  ou c u ca  cal call alle lled led? ed?  d? r ? rt  rt  rt n t no  not not  ot a t a   a p a pr  pri prin rinc ince nces cess ess  ss o s or  or  or a r al  all all  ll t l th  tha that hat  at b t bu  but but  ut w t wo  wor wort orth rthy thy  hy o y of  of  of a f a   a k a ki  kin king ings ngs  gs l s lo  lov love ove  ve ? e ??  ??‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù am  ame amen men! en!  n! t ! th  tha than hank anks nks  ks : s :   : r : rt  rt  rt i t i   i w i wi  wis wish ish  sh y h yo  you you  ou t u th  tha that hat  at : t :   : n : no  not not  ot a t a   a p a pr  pri prin rinc ince nces cess ess  ss o s or  or  or a r al  all all  ll t l th  tha that hat  at b t bu  but but  ut w t wo  wor wort orth rthy thy  hy o y of  of  of a f a   a k a ki  kin king ings ngs  gs l s lo  lov love ove  ve ? e ??  ??‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù a ù a   a m a ma  man man  an d n do  doe does oesn esn' sn't n't  't n t ne  nee need eed  ed a d a   a t a th  thr thro hron rone one  ne t e to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a k a ki  kin king ing, ng,  g, e , ev  eve ever very ery  ry g y go  goo good ood  od m d ma  man man  an i n is  is  is a s a   a k a ki  kin king ing! ng!  g! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? t ? ti  tim time ime  me i e in  inv inve nves vest este sted ted  ed i d in  in  in t n th  the the  he r e ri  rig righ ight ght  ht p t pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le i e is  is  is f s fa  far far  ar m r mo  mor more ore  re p e pr  pro prof rofi ofit fita itab tabl able ble  le t e th  tha than han  an m n ma  mat mate ater teri eria rial ial  al i l in  inv inve nves vest estm stme tmen ment ent. nt.  t. y . ye  yes yes  es f s fa  fa! fa!  a! : ! :   : a : ab  abi abi? bi?  i? : ? :   : a : a   a m a ma  man man  an d n do  doe does oesn esn' sn't n't  't n t ne  nee need eed  ed a d a   a t a th  thr thro hron rone one  ne t e to  to  to b o be  be  be a e a   a k a ki  kin king ing, ng,  g, e , ev  eve ever very ery  ry g y go  goo good ood  od m d ma  man man  an i n is  is  is a s a   a k a ki  kin king ing! ng!  g! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù‚ Äù‚Ä ù‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??  ?? : ? :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: t : ti  tim time ime  me i e in  inv inve nves vest este sted ted  ed i d in  in  in t n th  the the  he r e ri  rig righ ight ght  ht p t pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le i e is  is  is f s fa  far far  ar m r mo  mor more ore  re p e pr  pro prof rofi ofit fita itab tabl able ble  le t e th  tha than han  an m n ma  mat mate ater teri eria rial ial  al i l in  inv inve nves vest estm stme tmen ment ent. nt.‚ t.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i l i le  lea lear earn arn  rn t n th  thi this his  is e s ev  eve ever very eryd ryda yday day  ay n y ne  nev neve ever ver  er s r st  sto stop top  op g p gi  giv givi ivin ving ing  ng y g yo  you your our  ur b r br  bri brig righ ight ght  ht s t sm  smi smil mile ile. le.  e. e . ev  eve even ven  en i n if  if  if y f ya  ya  ya t a te  tee teet eeth eth  th i h is  is  is b s br  bro brow rown own  wn ? n ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? p ? pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le w e wh  who who  ho s o st  sti stic tick ick  ck w k wi  wit with ith  th y h yo  you you  ou r u re  reg rega egar gard ardl rdle dles less ess  ss o s of  of  of h f ho  how how  ow d w di  dif diff iffi ffic ficu icul cult ult  lt y t yo  you you  ou a u ar  are are  re w e wo  wor wort orth rth  th k h ke  kee keep eepi epin ping ing. ng.  g. n . no  not not  ot a t at  at  at a t al  all all  ll : l :   : s : sh  sha sha  ha n a no  not not  ot a t a   a r a re  rea reas easo ason son  on t n to  to  to b o be  be  be d e di  dif diff iffi ffic ficu icul cult ult  lt ‚ t ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú  Äú p ú pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le w e wh  who who  ho s o st  sti stic tick ick  ck w k wi  wit with ith  th y h yo  you you  ou r u re  reg rega egar gard ardl rdle dles less ess  ss o s of  of  of h f ho  how how  ow d w di  dif diff iffi ffic ficu icul cult ult  lt y t yo  you you  ou a u ar  are are  re w e wo  wor wort orth rth  th s h so  som some omet meti etim time imes mes  es e s ex  exp expl xpla plan lana anat nati atio tion ions ons  ns a s ar  are are  re w e wo  wor wort orth rthl thle hles less ess, ss,  s, w , we  we  we h e he  hea hear ear  ar w r wh  wha what hat  at w t we  we  we w e wa  wan want ant  nt t t to  to  to h o he  hea hear ear. ar.  r. p . pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le w e wh  who who  ho m o ma  mak make ake  ke u e us  us  us s s sm  smi smil mile ile  le w e wi  wit with itho thou hout out  ut s t sa  say sayi ayin ying ing  ng a g a   a w a wo  wor word ord. rd.  d. i . i   i m i ma  man mana anag nage age  ge t e to  to  to s o st  sta stay tay  ay g y ge  gen gene ener nera eral rall ally lly  ly h y ha  hap happ appy ppy  py e y ev  eve even ven  en w n wh  whe when hen  en l n li  lif life ife  fe g e ge  get gets ets  ts s s sh  shi shit hitt itty tty. ty.. y... ...  .. i . it  it' it's t's  's k s ki  kin kind inda nda  da a a aw  awe awes weso esom some ome  me a e at  at  at t t th  the the  he m e mo  mom mome omen ment ent. nt.. t... ...  .. u . ur  urb urba rban ban  an w n wa  wat wate ater ter  er f r fr  fro fron ront onts nts  ts a s as  as  as t s ti  tic tick icki ckin king ing  ng t g ti  tim time ime  me b e bo  bom bomb ombs mbs  bs l s li  lis list iste sten teni enin ning ing  ng t g to  to  to m o mu  mus musi usic sic  ic w c wi  wit with ith  th l h ly  lyr lyri yric rics ics  cs w s we  we  we a e ar  are are  re a e af  afr afra frai raid aid  id t d to  to  to s o sa  say say. ay.. y... ...  .. m . mi  min mind ind  nd f d fu  ful full ull  ll o l of  of  of w f wo  won wond onde nder der. er.. r..  .. t . th  the the  he e e el  ela elas last asti stic tici icit city ity  ty o y of  of  of m f my  my  my s y so  sou soul oul. ul.. l..  .. l . lo  lol lol! ol!  l! : ! :   : s : su  suc such uch  ch p h pr  pro prof rofo ofou foun ound und  nd w d wi  wis wisd isdo sdom dom  om " m ":  ":  ": o : on  onc once nce  ce a e a   a h a ha  hau haus ausa usa  sa a a al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys a s an  an  an i n il  ill illi llit lite iter tera erat rate ate" te"‚ e"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lo  lol lol  ol : l :   : " : ":  ":  ": t : th  the the  he e e el  ela elas last asti stic tici icit city ity  ty o y of  of  of m f my  my  my s y so  sou soul oul. ul.. l.." .."  ." h " hm  hmm hmmm mmmm mmm‚ mm‚Ä m‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù b ù ba  bar bari ari  ri k i ka  kaw kawa awai wai  ai ? i ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : ‚ : ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: " : "m  "my "my  my p y pe  pep pepp eppo ppo  po m o my  my  my p y pe  pep pepp eppo ppo" po"  o" ? " ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? i ? in  in  in h n hi  his his  is z s zo  zon zone one  ne t e to  tod toda oday day‚ ay‚Ä y‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù so  so  so g o gm  gmb gmb' mb's b's  's g s gr  gre grea reat eat  at g t gr  gra gran rand and  nd m d mo  mot moth othe ther her  er w r wa  was was  as f s fr  fro from rom  om i m im  imo imo  mo s o st  sta stat tate ate  te ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? sa  san sann annu nnu  nu r u ro  roc roch ocha chas has  as ? s ?   ? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? : ? :   : r : ro  rot rotl otlm tlma lmao mao  ao " o ":  ":  ": s : so  so  so g o gm  gmb gmb' mb's b's  's g s gr  gre grea reat eat  at g t gr  gra gran rand and  nd m d mo  mot moth othe ther her  er w r wa  was was  as f s fr  fro from rom  om i m im  imo imo  mo s o st  sta stat tate ate  te ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? sa  san sann annu nnu  nu r u ro  roc roch ocha chas has  as ? s ?"  ?"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù k ù ka  kaw kawa awai wai  ai b i ba  ba  ba ? a ??  ??? ???? ???l ??lm ?lma lmao mao  ao : o :   : l : lo  lol lol! ol!  l! m ! mu  muh muha uham hamm amma mmad madu adu  du o u ok  oke okec kech echu chuk hukw ukwu kwu  wu b u bu  buh buha uhar hari ari  ri . i .   . " . "   " s " so  so  so g o gm  gmb gmb' mb's b's  's g s gr  gre grea reat eat  at g t gr  gra gran rand and  nd m d mo  mot moth othe ther her  er w r wa  was was  as f s fr  fro from rom  om i m im  imo imo  mo s o st  sta stat tate ate  te ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? sa  san sann annu nnu  nu r u ro  roc roch ocha chas has  as ? s ?"  ?"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù l ù lm  lma lmao mao  ao : o :   : l : lo  lol lol! ol!  l! m ! mu  muh muha uham hamm amma mmad madu adu  du o u ok  oke okec kech echu chuk hukw ukwu kwu  wu b u bu  buh buha uhar hari ari  ri . i .   . " . ":  ":  ": s : so  so  so g o gm  gmb gmb' mb's b's  's g s gr  gre grea reat eat  at g t gr  gra gran rand and  nd m d mo  mot moth othe ther her  er w r wa  was was  as f s fr  fro from rom  om i m im  imo imo  mo s o st  sta stat tate ate  te ? e ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? s ? sa  san sann annu nnu  nu r u ro  roc roch ocha chas has  as ? s ?"  ?"‚ ?"‚Ä "‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù c ù ca  cal calc alcu lcul cula ulat lati atin ting ing  ng t g th  the the  he t e tr  tru true rue  ue c e co  cos cost ost  st o t of  of  of e f en  ene ener nerg ergy rgy  gy s y st  sto stor tora orag rage age  ge b e by  by  by t y ti  tim tim  im h m he  hen henn enne nnes ness esse ssey sey. ey.  y. s . su  sus sust usta stai tain aina inab nabl able ble  le c e ci  cit citi itie ties ies: es:  s: i : in  inf infr nfra fras rast astr stru truc ruct uctu ctur ture ure  re c e co  cos cost osts sts  ts + s +   + u + ur  urb urba rban ban  an g n gr  gro grow rowt owth wth  th m h ma  man mana anag nage agem geme emen ment ent  nt l t lo  lol lol! ol!  l! w ! we  we  we a e al  all all  ll s l se  see see  ee e e el  ele eleg lega egan ganc ance nce  ce d e di  dif diff iffe ffer fere eren rent entl ntly tly  ly i y i   i g i gu  gue gues uess ess. ss.. s... ...  .. l . lu  lup lupi upit pita ita  ta l a lo  loo look ooks oks  ks f s fu  fun funn unny nny! ny!  y! c ! co  cos cos  os u s u   u f u fo  for fore orev reve ever ver  er m r my  my  my l y la  lad lady ady, dy,  y, f , fo  for fore orev reve ever ver  er m r my  my  my b y ba  bab baby aby  by ? y ??  ??? ???? ??? ?? ? 