@username What my love life will hold instore for me in the future. I'd never ask when I'm gonna die...???????? @username @username @username Who is this psychic you're gonna talk to? Theresa Caputo? #longislandmedium @username #AskAVJ Where does you love for all dark and horror things come from? @username Those boys in those days... http://t.co/Dgf0R6fF26 “@username: @username Oh oh oh, die rechterfoto... zo'n cutie! :-)” 1985....Theatre Of Pain @username More boys from those days... http://t.co/7g6bnxPCs6 @username https://t.co/U9XWAzvBQS The Ramones @username He looked so garrish... @username I rocked so much to their music! @username Haha, look at Ozzy's face! @username Aerosmith Rocks!!! @username Slade!!! Cool memories of my grammar school days!! @username Paul's cool answer to the Beatles' breakup @username Mott The Hoople was less known here in the 70's but I had two of their albums @username I love that show, saw it on live stream!! Cant wait to see you in April!!! #sixxam @username 33 great years of our lives! @username RIP Mick Ronson!! @username Bowie was extraordinary in his performance and still kills it!! @username @username They were exceptional for years and I'm glad they are still playing!!! @username The Stones!! I have all their music, just like I have all the @username albums!!! @username He deserves to be mentioned twice! @username 51 The Netherlands @username Badass Bass... @username @username @username #photoedit by @username ???? http://t.co/OXF1ZGaP1S “@username: @username really like your photo edits????” THANK YOU! ???? “@username: Black Sabbath, 1970 http://t.co/WBtHlPFXO3” @username “@username: There comes a point where you just love someone, not because they're good or bad. You just love them the way they are.” “@username: Karma has no menu. You get served what you deserve.” On @username http://t.co/JPKzm1bJ3I ???? @username @username New Coke, 1985 @username @username AC/DC ARE AMONG THE BEST ROCK BANDS OF THE WORLD, DEF TOP 10!!! @username We'll MISS your live shows BIGTIME!!! ?????????????? Autumn Leaves & Starry Eyes #photoedit of @username @username by @username ???????? http://t.co/MuQiU0LIbK @username Thanks! Now I could retweet your nice photo of @username ! ???? @username It's ok. If anyone bothers, they will let you know and ask for an unblock ;) @username  twitter bug? “@username: @username I like your profile photo.  Very nice!!! You look very pretty.  :)” THANK YOU! Took this photo in August this year. This is one of the nicest hotels I ever stayed in! #superb @username https://t.co/Gzcl3mvQBB @username I hope you had a great show in Calgary....Good night ???? @username #photoedit by @username http://t.co/QivN8ISOQj “@username: @username @username BEAUTIFUL OF COURSE!!!” THANK YOU! ???????? @username You're welcome! ???? @username @username @username I admit that this #photoedit turned out a bit #weird ....#lol ???? http://t.co/nvGmOyPHdd @username Your last name is from my old region in The Netherlands, where there's a village called Susteren (it's old Dutch for "sisters") ???????????? 2500 likes of http://t.co/0enHKm5ipB !!! Thank you ALL OF YOU MEGATIME!!! #verygrateful ?????????? @username @username @username @username @username I fully agree 100% ???????? A #photoedit for @username 's four legged pal, #LeicaSixx, by @username ?????????? http://t.co/RFWRgQ0LGF @username Rock Royalty Golden Retriever: #LeicaSixx #photoedit by @username ?????????? http://t.co/Uppz3OCSkN Fire In The Hole!!! A firy #photoedit of @username by @username #RIPMotleyCrue ???? http://t.co/VU43MnI8GJ @username @username @username Awww! Thank you! ???????? @username Thank you, Nikki, for your article. It triggers an interesting discussion! I'd say: @username over @username ! ???????? The BLUES BROTHERS all night and in the morning!!! #ReplayTheMovie ???? @username Cartoon Art #photoedit by @username ???????? http://t.co/TBT6MPDIK2 A shoutout to the one, the only @username ???????? That's my shouting for this week, babes! No #FF 's. Shouting is loud enuff, don't you think? Shout you out next Friday! ???????? I forgot one important person! #ShoutOut @username !!! ?? @username Got the prize in the mail today!! Thank you very much!!! #awesome ??????????????@username http://t.co/xcvYJ7k5s2 @username Done! Aren't you following @username on #instagram ? #ShoutOut to @username “@username: @username Check out @username Live! http://t.co/cnf1Reyuwl :D #SupportNewMusic” ???????? “@username: @username thanks love have a great weekend xoxo” YOU TOO!! @username @username Cool pic! Thanx! ???????? On my instagram now: http://t.co/uxOYg4ZDRF Who will be at the @username show in Vancouver tonight? #thefinaltour #2ndtolastshow @username You too! A Kingdom of Conscience is A Kingdom of Heaven... ~Kingdom of Heaven Holiness is in right actions and courage on behalf of those who cannot defend themselves... ~Kingdom Of Heaven #ShoutOut @username I sent you a message thru my Sixx page messenger ???? @username @username @username true! Be aware of this, music artists... “@username: @username @username @username @username thank you so much Rose !!! You rock !!! ??” yw ???????? @username #photoedit by @username with #crossdesign provided by @username ???? http://t.co/k4NBm2SiQq Thanx to @username @username @username @username @username @username & many others for RT-ing my tweets! ?????????? @username @username @username The #bestbandever #thebadboys #ilovemotleycrue “@username: @username @username @username awesome!??” thank you :3 @username #photoedit by @username #frame by @username ???? http://t.co/Xb9CbgCNsv @username #photoedit by @username ???? http://t.co/pTQeoNISyD @username #photoedit by @username I'm on an editing spree today ;) ???? http://t.co/f2TEDUgzI6 @username @username @username @username @username @username @username @username Thanks, hon! ???????? @username Good night...1 show left to go this year...???????? @username Good early morning to you with some #rrroarrr #pow and #oh!noo! #lol http://t.co/BVDOExtuxt To a #cool #CrüeFan @username !! #photoedit by @username @username @username #RIPMotleyCrue #rockon http://t.co/dCA0RuZ4JT “@username: @username @username @username that's awesome! Thank you!!” You're welcome ???????????? Thanx for the follow @username  Check them out!! Solid rock from Sweden!! ????????#rockon @username rocks da house when @username kills it onstage!!! @username #rockon #gottagetitright m/ ???????? http://t.co/WOX6iSevWR “@username: @username @username @username OMG!  I love it so much!  Thank you oodles big time! :D” YW! ???? Crüehead @username lives it up!!! #RIPMotleyCrue #rockon @username @username ???? http://t.co/2L2o3pez6x “@username: @username @username @username Thank you! Love it!” You're welcome! ???????? @username Totally Trüe! Good luck on your last show of this year tonight! ?????? @username The Monsieur roams the #HollywoodNights #rockon @username @username #RIPMotleyCrue ??????????? http://t.co/oJJ30mQ61w Rocking a Crüed Night is the Wolfing...@username @username @username #RIPMotleyCrue #rockon http://t.co/QWEVAt50Mc “@username: @username @username @username this is awesome, thanks :3” You're welcome! ???? @username @username @username @username @username It was the BEST tour I've ever followed online and been to myself!!! ???????? @username @username @username @username @username Hahaha, that app rocks!!! See ya next year in Europe, boys!!! @username No doubt it was a killer last show of a killer last tour in the US! Thank you for everything this year and ... Good night ???? @username @username @username @username @username @username They still are ;) I'm your REAL love. I'd go to the end of the world with you. The only thing I need is your love...?????? Hey @username I found you a dolly... #SixxDoll ???????? http://t.co/PJwVp0DqkW @username So COOL!! I like you two together and I love your smile, Nikki! ??????????4ever!!! @username @username @username @username @username I'm flying all the way from The Netherlands to LA to see @username ???????? @username @username We have a saying here: if the Prophet won't come to the Mountain, the Mountain will have to come to the Prophet! Had a wish just now and it got fulfilled! YAY!!! ?????????????????? @username @username Stick Together! 