Dev leaves minor bug in App -> User gives 1-star rating -> Dev fixes bug -> User never changes rating -.- Do not touch http://t.co/uewIGjoim4 Coding early in the morning and wondering why Eclipse for Java marks "for i in range(10)" -.- #python After feedly the online reader and chrome extension @username pro replaces Google Reader for me now. Well, thx for this elaborate review -.- http://t.co/vDPDE2brvm 60fps->impressive:interactive smoke&fluid,fish w/ AI,dynamic maps,subsurface shader,volumetric lighting,self shadow,highres texture #xboxone Ok,bye, I'm off for a 0 minutes walk. (You shouldn't first check boundaries and then do the float to int conversion) http://t.co/YZyk4BJtWD @username hübsches doodle; und Happy Birthday! :) @username pretty bad, because it's not a name but the title for the wife of the Dothraki chieftain. Daenerys would be better ;) @username pretty sure I will like that. I did swipe right to change column so many times :D @username @username iOS App in progress is nice but for me I'd rather see an Android App in the pipeline. Who thought this television order would be a good idea? http://t.co/JaGHFNMvhL TIL taking unimpressive operations out of a for loop may result in an impressive performance gain Finally had the time to converted my old POP email account to IMAP #holidays @username I read the "good news everyone!" in the voice of prof farnsworth :D #futurama I guess productive sunday is already gone by returing at #5am Latest Futurama Episode (S7E19) is nice, but not as total-ninja-super-awesome as in the last couple of weeks. The spring in the 3.5mm input jack is not sufficient and always overrides Bluetooth. Fixed it like a mechanic. http://t.co/b08dmxmWcG I read and checked my paper so many times I know it by heart. Suddenly a paragraph without a source reference appears. Were did I get the idea for that again? o.O PHD Comics: Coffee Security http://t.co/x1xX9p1pZj via @username @username add Flatland by Abbott to your next order, if you haven't read it yet. @username aside from the fact that google reader and google sync were discontinued ;) Just got my red @username One. It's awesome! @username haha! The calendar sync for outlook only keeps working for existing users, luckily I'm one of them. @username yes, they went from MS ActiveSync to CalDAV but MS is a little slow in adding support for that protocol. I updated my Android App Big Bang Script with a new UI and optimized it for various screen sizes. http://t.co/4QvQjsTuGn Any feedback? @username thank you, I'm going to adjust the layout later. Lily uses a strange UI skin on her iPhone #himym http://t.co/t3mHQ6M3O9 Got a USB flash drive and the famous blue T-shirt as presents from mcs unibnf. Thanks @username @username @username "I can practice my English skills" - "But I want to improve my German verbal abilities" -> every conversation I had with foreign students Just testing out some different evolutionary steps http://t.co/fhHvhr7LMZ The plot showing what points converge to which of the three zeroes turned out more impressive than expected http://t.co/9bMyahjsZ6 @username that was like 3 days ago...or on the internet this was a lifetime ago :D nice slider. Can't really say how old I am http://t.co/5O2Ru0maP2 I'm probably the only one who didn't know there's some kind of holiday today in fribourg. View through 4 empty rooms http://t.co/0RoDdBOaaJ Nope, I'm not. A woman just entered the room excusing for being late and then asking me where everyone remains :D #lasttweet @username what? :D I always choose the best team members. http://t.co/S2yLpqgem2 What a commit. Default files. Files without filetype. Randomly deleted colons in CSS. Username&Password for DB. Deleted half of my work. :@username @username @username ha emu e bon becho, bi aso anschiinend gnue dert :) Stupid team project! They commit broken code, they write incorrect stuff in the paper and they don't even help building presentation slides. Ha! In one of the projects my teammate quit the course (3 weeks ago; he told me Now!). I can do everything myself. That's honestly better ;) @username maybe the ambiguity is on purpose..? The value of the bounty I got this week for doing good work was higher than the money I actually earned while doing said work :) Thx for the review but I really don't have a Master of Arts. http://t.co/g73WOkcD6D The reflection on Kepler from the blue planet in today's Google Doodle is nicely done. http://t.co/CQ84tqxjiF The blue planet isn't the earth as the orbit is too elliptical. And for a comet like Halley it's too circular. It might be a colored Eris :) Programming languages used this year: Java, JavaScript, Matlab, PHP, Python #code2013 http://t.co/RzC3TJkU2v Yesterday, everybody smoked his last cigar, took his last drink, swore his last oath, sat last on his couch & ate his last unhealthy meal? Solving the TSP with 411 cities for the project of the Probabilistic Algorithms lecture. http://t.co/qMw6vs5cCP @username you have to use matlab in convex and (a lot of) java in rendering. Pervasive is partly HCI stuff. Maybe this helps deciding @username didn't ask for another choice and course description lists it (again) http://t.co/Norqyv2zi8 but tasks are easy and short :) @username hehe, but they were weekly. And not just matlab, sometimes just theoretical problems to solve on paper. @username sounds like the description of one of my classifiers.. I have to buy a new smartphone for this fancy cover “@username  Detailed shots of HTC's Dot View http://t.co/96QRY8hzPh http://t.co/36DYLrE2lG” Nice, how long has Google been doing this results comparisons? http://t.co/8SXOQWJdCm "It said something about 'merge conflict', so I send you the code in a mail." Every Team-member. Every Week. :( Obviously there is no such thing as @username at other universities where you have to use git. Most useful exercises ever (in retrospect). @username no problem, mistakes can happen. Good thing we always use tests, right? RIGHT? :) All new episodes and I have to prepare for a presentation :/ http://t.co/CXf1HMnCkl New external HDD vs external HDD that fell on the floor while writing data (same model) http://t.co/YFwqZ8nQqA Watching #IIHFCZE on ?eská televize because official stream doesn't work. What it's like to own a Tesla Model S - A cartoonist's review of his magical space car - The Oatmeal http://t.co/GGePKW3PHu via @username $226 since October 2010 sounds about right. http://t.co/ykYOfkVgCj 808 Cube beat http://t.co/wZ58GD6266 @username yes, this was 3 years ago. I don't remember more. If there was anything to remark I've probably written it in the lecture survey :) This is my 2^9 th tweet. Interesting talks on the first day of #3rdMUMIATrainingSchool. Looking forward to the next lectures. http://t.co/KvEe0i5kmk @username @username created in less than 10s...it's only the color (0/128/128). https://t.co/xAP8D2Hv6D redundancy in @username :) http://t.co/bXCEfvMkHM Woah, I tracked 3.5 million steps with my @username I'm in the top 0.6%. http://t.co/UvDxL7p019 Interesting talks on the first day of #CLEF2014. Looking forward to #replab2014 and #pan2014. http://t.co/6DKZLOkRBb @username Correlation does not imply causation. Maybe you tweet because you lose followers :) Simpsons-Futurama episode: TSP is class P,  Fermat's little theorem, Riemann hypothesis, prime number theorem, etc. http://t.co/rDanhvkPtH @username nice, congrats! @username I can't download prey on my Android Tablet Acer Iconia Tab A500 (WiFi-only). It's not compatible with my device. What now?? <3 @username support! My student plan was activated within less than an hour! @username the official update may arrive next week ^^ http://goo.gl/NFQ3Y A reasonable step back to android's openness RT @username We're reviewing our bootloader policy. http://on.fb.me/jog8Wa What the hell are you doing @username?!?!  http://yfrog.com/h76jltej @username @username @username na, I was at work. We gonna solve them in the lecture (again) ^^ lol @username as if they read our talk on #fb RT @username New option for the "following" page: view Tweets from the accounts a user follows. What do you do for a living, Microsoft? Making money on phones...by patent trolling. http://goo.gl/70QXd Sue 'em if you can't beat 'em ^^ @username What's the deal with the correction of ps9? It's still a 'nef' but no reason given why nor any advice on how to improve it further Cool, your brain is a 5 million core 9 Hertz computer http://goo.gl/eHXU1 @username ps09 is fixed. Take heed of the comments I added with the task tag 'MIKO'. Thx @username build highly cohesive* classes and have loose coupling** between those; eh? // *readability & reuse **extensible & flexible OMG HAXX0RZ APPLE IZ COPYING JUST LIEK MY SCIENCE TESTS IN THIRD GRAED!!!11 #stupidComment Honestly, I'm pleased Apple's making these changes, because it will force Google to reach for more. And this is what we ALL want. @username The platform is open enough for me to switch to a customROM with the latest kernel and android version ;D @username @username ...and therefore uses far less memory :) I don't care (anymore) about HTC Sense @username @username LOL! :D But I finally set up the VPN-Unibe. That was the only thing iOS did from day one and Android had problems. If it's too good to be true, it probably is. http://yfrog.com/h2ojarp There is always exactly one screw left if you disassemble a notebook and put it together an hour later. What is the point with those private Twitter profiles and protected Tweets? Gotta send a follow request?! Seriously?! Cool post. I'm going to "Fwd: like RT +1" that! *social media douchebag* That wifi keyboard works perfectly with my iconia tab. No tedious setup, no missing drivers or anything alike Woah! Even copy/paste and the special keys (music & volume control, search, homescreen, lock, calendar, ...)  are operative! I was on a shopping trip with my sister. Fancy new thing are cool, but I am almost out of money three days after pay day :$ 