You are eager to get started with something new. But jumping i... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 Endless night.. You may be feeling giddy with anticipation as things begin to ... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 Love is in the air with romantic Venus now visiting your sign ... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 I need spring, sun, daisies, hot days and holidays... @username Happy B-Day Yann! I love you :* good morning :)) Circumstances don't leave you much room for fun today as a co-... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 RT @username Seth's Blog: You rock http://bit.ly/9oMNL8 It feels like one minute you have the patience of a saint and ... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 waiting for gossip girl new episode to download then taking a break from study. I'm so sick of economics right now. You have pulled the bowstring back as far as you can. Now, as ... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 snow fight with my cousin this afternoon :)) I'm tired..going to bed! tomorrow I've to get up early, time to study seriously now :P a celebration of winter [stop-motion video] http://flic.kr/p/7JTia5 March Snow. http://flic.kr/p/7JMfvM It's not easy for you to express your needs now, especially if... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 You are not eager to work by yourself today, even if that is y... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 confused. http://flic.kr/p/7KaCfX I feel tired of this city. I want to run away from here. Your friends might not meet your expectations today, but that ... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 finally the sun is shining and I've to stay at home to study..really funny :(( Loneliness is and always has been the central and inevitable experience of every man. http://flic.kr/p/7KrA9o It's no simple matter to say exactly what you mean today, espe... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 You are caught in a strange spot in the fabric of time today a... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 Yet another wave of energy surges through your life today as t... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/twittascope/?sign=1 @username Italy is a good choice I think :)) going to the library to study all day :) You may be more realistic about what's ahead than you have bee... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 I love how my website look like, pretty soon It will be online! new upload on flickr! http://flic.kr/p/7LQ2J3 You are ready to shine your light and expect others to support... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 exam in few days and I feel I'm not ready at all.. reading "The Economist" last issue, then going to bed.. There is a delicate balance between what you intend to accompl... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 @username  me too I'm missing your wonderful photos, hope you will be back soon :)) oh, I really hate to study this stuff.... @username love your new twitter background :) Today can be an important day because there's more going on th... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 train tickets Arles-Cherbourg booked! You may feel as if you lost an opportunity now that the Moon h... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 exam tomorrow, wish me luck :P Your friends may be concerned about you today because you aren... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 It's best to think before you act today because the Moon fires... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 going to the hairdresser today! Lomoaholic !! http://flic.kr/p/7NocPC going to Oslo on Friday! #Beirut concert at Olympia next week! Your energy level can be so high that you could exhaust yourse... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 stasera the notwist all'estragon :)) i love spring, it makes me feel better and positive for almost everything :)) Next Thursday I will be in France for three weeks, whoaaa!! I will take tons of photos :)) Prepare yourself for Earth Hour 2010 with the "Lights Off" Twitter-application. http://lightsoff-earthhour.com #earthhour #nowwatching grey's anatomy :)) and tonight's gonna be a good night.. @username You're are more than welcome! I love your work as well..keep going on and good luck! great concert, now is time to go to bed, it's 2 a.m. :)) It may be the weekend, but you have plenty on your plate and h... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 Good morning! Today I'm going to Bologna :)) the postman just bring me #Internazionale and the #economist this morning, have to read a lot now!! #nowplaying automatic stop - the strokes @username I love it ;) errata corrige: I've almost reached 100,000 views on flickr :) @username sorry for my bad english :) new twitter background by the way.. @username did you study it at school? wow that's cool, studying italian is not very common I guess :) @username The Notwist all'Estragon! Earth Hour 2010 just started! Turn off the lights! http://bit.ly/dsChN7 #earthhour You may feel as if you cannot tell your friends what you reall... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 today I'm older than yesterday..happy b-day to me :) @username @username thank you!! @username anyway I'm 24 now :D, and what about you? @username @username thank you :) ..and yes you're right every day I will be older than the day before :P Revisiting 9/11: Unpublished Photos by James Nachtwey - LightBox http://t.co/0WXYsFj via @username happy birthday to me !! http://flic.kr/p/7P3wKD You want to do the right thing in a relationship, with today's... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 today I'm tired but happy :D @username I love it :) post-processing some photos from the photoshoot of yesterday :D Someone's indecisive behavior may increasingly bother you toda... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 in the woods. http://flic.kr/p/7PB5wR Everything becomes a bit more complex today because you cannot... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 Time to leave, I will be away until April 17th and I don't know If I will have time to upload something..we'll see :) http://bit.ly/bqoHyy Although nothing seems easy today, you are able to draw energy... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 in Arles..tired after 15 hours of train You may be a bit uncertain as to what to do next, for although... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 féria pascale :) I'm going to take so many photos!! #nowwatching Grey's Anatomy 6x19 :)) going to Nîmes tomorrow! It is finally clear that you know what you want, but alluring ... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 postcards from Arles (South of France) .. http://bit.ly/dfKg1f You may be drawn into an emotional drama now, even if you atte... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 View from the Rhône in Arles http://bit.ly/9m2Mpw Your life has taken a serious turn, and a sensible approach to... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 Last day in Arles..and tomorrow will be Normandy! You can say what's on your mind today but you'll need to pick ... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 in Normandy!! my website is almost ready! http://bit.ly/awfOhh You may have enough cool logic to make a plan, but your heated... More for Aries http://twittascope.com/?sign=1 tomorrow in Brittany with my boyfriend ;) 