What are the most popular computer programming jokes? http://t.co/q4Na1a1R Answer by Frank Heile to What are the most popular computer programming jokes? http://t.co/gS3tRMIQ I wrote: Hard to be an OR-er http://t.co/NHKd2GiQ I wrote: Just listened to &quot;Iron Butterfly&quot; http://t.co/tUbRBvLs OMG! :) RT @username: Love this @username post - how to cut a pizza into 11 equal slices... So good! http://t.co/8968gk3P I wrote: TCP/IP, as in TCP/IP (II) http://t.co/1an9MQ7D I'm at Greenwich School Of Management (Greenwich, Greater London) http://t.co/R9TuN7k0 I'm at Costa Coffee (London) http://t.co/qWsh2wgh How To Manage Projects: Double Down, Delegate, or Destroy | LinkedIn http://t.co/bsXUA7dK Coffee time! (@username Greenwich Picturehouse Bar) http://t.co/pO6XWm20 I wrote: Caipirinha's Algorithm http://t.co/MT11ddwA I'm at Cass Business School (London, Greater London) http://t.co/rg2tLFmj I wrote: Two Years and so on! http://t.co/zzQfiXj5 OMG! On the TV now: 'a high-tech form of internet marketing' Come On! It's just SEO!!!! I wrote: Does the other way round apply? http://t.co/PS08FneM I wrote: Innocentive &amp; OR-ers http://t.co/sN0PkGfU I've just entered a double points promotion on the Costa Coffee Club Facebook app! #costa #costacoffeeclub https://t.co/cH6AW3DE @username I recommend the tool I designed -> http://t.co/gSjhIvcy I wrote: Not another gentle post on Numb3rs... maybe. http://t.co/uSbVxxOd Time ago I wrote: LinkedIn http://t.co/DamUBieB I gave @username +K  on @username http://t.co/0VuwEPmL I gave @username +K  on @username http://t.co/s01XHaEa I gave @username +K about Social Media on @username http://t.co/Gl5xBNo8 .@username, your Klout Score is 55 (I'm a 56). Check out your @username profile today! http://t.co/zEl4EfFA Networking (@username Abacus) http://t.co/NEk583LP Check out my new list on @username, featuring @username, @username, and @username! http://t.co/jdTppe91 Time ago I wrote: Dark Music for the Dark Side http://t.co/FxzoS8eq RT @username: No one wants a toxic mentor... of course RT @username: The daily Dilbert http://t.co/UfvxGhNN #comic I'm at The Long Acre (London, Greater London) http://t.co/uLkVsvDN I'm at London Bridge Railway Station (LBG) (London, Greater London) w/ 6 others http://t.co/BOUDLPGV Time ago I wrote: 101% = [(100 + 1) / 100] x 100 http://t.co/Ueei3ARW Cortado & brownie... Paid with bonus points!!! (@username Costa Coffee) http://t.co/LgymbshC RT @username: Murder-low London ‘is one of the safest cities on the planet’ http://t.co/4Mkq0qcc Oh, great. @username always launches the special offers the day after I sent my order :'( It's a matter of timing! I'm at Greenwich Picturehouse Bar (Greenwich, Greater London) http://t.co/M07iQcjD I just became the mayor of Greenwich Picturehouse Bar on @username! http://t.co/Fw2lqLhn Time ago I wrote: Poor 'mean'..., just because is 'average' http://t.co/dEvQcUYE RT @username: Reading the riots on Twitter http://t.co/fSSKZ2k5 #research 2.6M tweets sent during the UK riots #video Time ago I wrote: TCO/TCP http://t.co/eWww4QCv Yes, my World domination plan includes make you believe #SocialMediaROI is useful! Hang on... isn't it? Thanks for the feedback! http://t.co/bPaMqeFB #ActiveListening Celebrity homes – the power of social media http://t.co/FsEG6V8D Time ago I wrote: Wow, I can't believe it! http://t.co/fZTG0vuM Time ago I wrote: My name is Francisco, does it matter? http://t.co/WmLqw5Vr RT @username: Thanks for the feedback [in the strategic process] http://t.co/bPaMqeFB #ActiveListening #SocialMedia The Internet Perspective http://t.co/8romwH76 Time ago I wrote: Mean Manufacturing http://t.co/gF0atv4w RT @username: 1.35 billion tourists traveled internationally in 2012 #Tourism2012 RT @username: 6 business apps that actually boost productivity: http://t.co/yExIcOB8 A curated list from HootSuite CEO @username @username this page needs to be ammended http://t.co/2UUsNJdz (i.e. the Twitter account) @username I loved your 'Ask a question' feature in the blog. Is that an internal development or a plugin? Just one day worth of twits and news got from the internet tell us this about @username It is a raw tag cloud, though. http://t.co/by4DXZaU @username :) on twitterland you can find me as @username, too. Time ago I wrote: 2010, not 2012 [insert scary face here] http://t.co/kpw3tJrD I'm at Greenwich School Of Management (Greenwich, Greater London) http://t.co/Hr05YCf2 These weeks I've been meeting very interesting people that have been doing great kick-offs in their digital businesses. D.McWilliams » As we forge deeper ties in Europe we're forgetting our closest ally http://t.co/oxaeRJ50 | If UK left EU, Ireland'd have too? How to Detect a Lying Client [INFOGRAPHIC] http://t.co/MF3DsDkh via @username How to manage a euro exit http://t.co/DsvD0BXQ via @username Time ago I wrote: Wastin' my time. http://t.co/nuNc3JoY Time ago I wrote: Warehouse Management System &amp; 1984 http://t.co/OdefnRaJ Time ago I wrote: MBA vs MSc http://t.co/Vf50flrI @username That's a cute idea, though! :D @username Harry, I've got a Westie; she barks in English but sometimes I've got problems 2understand her. Let's see: Woof! Welcome 2 Tw cc @username @username @username @username we were in a cocktail party and now have became a pack :D Who's alpha? (not meee!!!) Time ago I wrote: Ethinomics/Ethonomics http://t.co/WH0m9m1U @username woofmorning! ;) I'm at Star of India (Leytonstone, Greater London) http://t.co/lXh1SLo3 RT @username: Could social media be the key to building your future talent pipeline? http://t.co/h7HrrMFe Time ago I wrote: Think Twice http://t.co/R0WEJ7sG Time ago I wrote: Ever Growing Cloud (II) http://t.co/cCKpZ7iP The Psychology of Music  http://t.co/zeCZz09H via @username #infography Time ago I wrote: Bullwhip Effect in Education http://t.co/jOOPY6OA @username welcome to Twitter! ;) Biz mentoring meeting. (@username University College London) http://t.co/4hkJ0mB9 Weird and cold day ¬¬ Time ago I wrote: LinkIt &amp; Syxt http://t.co/qxlVHpZ1 I see everyone checking it this Mon RT @username: Your boss's signature says a lot about their personality: study http://t.co/cKwiINoa Too much alienation in society. People, get your human being hats back please :) Time ago I wrote: IDEAS for Economics, OO for OR... http://t.co/hBVwhGuL Economic impact of GIS http://t.co/1LF153Jx First there was chaos... in #SocialMedia. http://t.co/QcKRW3WF Then came #Cosmos! Even to #UK Time ago I wrote: Back from Holidays : ( http://t.co/ScTcPf3c I'm at Greenwich School Of Management (Greenwich, Greater London) http://t.co/EjYhauet 5 Tricks for Remembering Names | LinkedIn http://t.co/E2hHeJTx February 2013 Newsletter--Social media as a management tool http://t.co/h2dT6QKP Time ago I wrote: Lost in the Trade Fair!!! http://t.co/JaLk91KX First lessons this semester and already proud of it. I'm at Greenwich School Of Management (Greenwich, Greater London) http://t.co/XKSOHOTQ I'm at Greenwich Picturehouse Bar (Greenwich, Greater London) http://t.co/Hb8NSYHa Time ago I wrote: Misunderstood http://t.co/FSXrvEtU Today, in class, we have been talking about corruption and Spain... but it wasn't in the same conversation. I know, it's weird, isn't it? Time ago I wrote: Who let the JERKS out?? http://t.co/MId5D2Wq Analytics for your mobile apps with @username RT @username: Worldwide cost of living survey 2013 http://t.co/72Rfw43a via @username Wow! I'm in the Top 99% of most seen profiles in LinkedIn http://t.co/DdlLVuyL Time ago I wrote: The Name of the Profession http://t.co/BjMuNOrE I'm at London Euston Railway Station (EUS) (London, Greater London) w/ 12 others http://t.co/Y8UidXBl I'm happy everything is falling into place. Besides, that place is more likely UK rather than Spain. Wine Pairing Chart http://t.co/qiuqkoyq via @username 