I just remembered the dream I had last night about a fucking spider in my house the size of a puppy jesus fuck it was disgusting girls with muscles. FINALLY FOUND THE WORD OF IT I HAVE ''trypophobia'' now im confused headache started listening to marilyn manson for the first time ever a few hours ago and i havent heard 1 song I dislike oh and don't worry i've slapped myself over 39 times already for only just now listening to it @username fucking love Holy Wood dude every track on that is fucking sick this song gives me chillls https://t.co/kb6i78vQif fuckoff was in this dungeon for like an hour in skyrim died and started all the way where i started  nope fuckoff @username nobody wants to rape meg thisss https://t.co/kF5kWsjPBN Holy Wood is definitely Mansons best album my cousins gonna make dank fifa vids go sub if your penis size is above average https://t.co/RbkUZFaFOu Orange juice after toothbrushing isnt even bad at all thefuck moms listenen to Marilyn Manson holy shit this is amazing http://t.co/qDNUto0Swv @username already watched a bit of that. my opinion: https://t.co/oLuFbUDYLt @username @username I just absolutely cannot stand him. could only last like 3 minutes why http://t.co/dOjjNM3emc CHAPTER 14 IS OUT ALREADY OGMGGGGG HOLY FUCK IVE NEVER BEEN THIS SUPRISED IN MY LIFE IM SAHKIGN good chapter goosebumps WOOP Cheetos are the essence of life My eyes are so damn tired I can barely see halp fucked hyped for GoT season 5 doe Goodnight. I'll be going to my dreamworld now where McDonalds DELIVERS. @username faggot you read the manga first dont you dare start season 2 @username STOP IGNORING ME CHAI READ THE MANGA DMDMDMD check not-peasants chat @username saleh you too but I can't find your @username wtf had u blocked lmao CHECK CHAT NOW @username @username still the tunest tune in the history of tuny tunes https://t.co/R2akJs7sbi Nomadic guitar solo appreciation tweet if you die when theres no one watchinggg~~ irl mate is almost up to date with the tokyo ghoul manga like the non-peasant he is. i can finally take out my fanboy urges on someone 24/7 fuck me you're all peasants IQ removed Piet Paulisma from the header. I no longer have contact with any of them. they are forgotten. I can't forgive, I won't forget. Courage the cowardly dog was some next level weird shit We've only reached the third day of our seven-day binge~~ @username omfg the end had me pissing thisss https://t.co/u0HysUFZVk just watched Fury with m8s beast movie I'm fucking home fuck me my school is worthless Nancy Grace deserves infinite punches in her cuntface get this 3 more https://t.co/21Kgd8DAYT I take back what I may have said about beartooth in the past. theyre pretty beast I have given up on humanity and decides to join the animal kingdom. I am now a fucking lion. http://t.co/GswxeEIqIG Decided*. And why the fuck is the picture turned around lmao new tokyo ghoul ep was good but jesus fuck the manga just shits on this former pancakes IQ thinks I'm a cosplayer because I have a  fucking onesie. I can't fucking believe this @username you are...one very...very very confusing person.. taking back what i said about episode 4 earlier. its complete shit read the fucking manga peasants jesus fuck I love this song https://t.co/oZuQd1SyvJ IQ make fun of saleh because they know hes a fucking god in comparison to them for he has read the manga unlinke the peasants Unlike* sorry sometimes a fucking god among peasants makes his mistakes out of frustration caused by being surrounded by peasants @username beatin in lips is definetly my #2. i have a problem being my #1 ofcourse one day I will fucking tweet all the big tokyo ghoul spoilers to get rid of my peasant followers. start reading now or suffer the consequences @username I don't even think there is a sao manga thats how disgusting it is @username i just tried one. Didnt fall asleep but i fucking loved it. Thanks alot for introducing me to this. Man its good @username do you have any favorite videos/channels who do this? Goodnight @username so are you not gonna read the manga anymore or after this garbage season/ *everybody hurts plays in the background* This guy is gonna shoot up my school soon I just fucking know it http://t.co/UCeDc7cCvb @username the last two pics definitely look like he saw me... I won't be spared... help @username the fucking ''69'' tho nope nope nope nope fucking end his misery @username jesus fucking christ In train init Was sitting in train alone and peacefully then like millions of people decided to sit next to me and talk and shout n shit ffs Can u not. Out of all the places you can sit. Chaos is something I've been missing~~ BUT WHAT DID HE WANNA SAY THOUGH http://t.co/qYev6ElNOW how do I still have money @username this is nothing to be proud of @username sure do. you definitely attracted such beings with this @username @username oh i wouldnt mind that. we used to love ourselves~ we used to love one another~~~ https://t.co/n12JSPXNRo he deserved it http://t.co/WNYkFGR3Rh he's at volume 12. bow down to him peasants really should of taken a nap earlier @username @username Pevil and Deril? @username @username you say the only difference is 2 letters... when its obviously 4. kenny are you high? @username @username yea but youre talking about 2 fucking words here kenny @username @username a god? yea i am a god. for you are a peasant ryan is a fucking god peasants @username yes. youre a fucking peasant in comparison to him too. but your in peril so your kinda a peasant in comparison to everyone when people make fun of saleh when they're actually fucking peasants http://t.co/HvRfZUs4cQ Good mornin http://t.co/O69mQ5lIRk @username holy fuck thats amazing CHAPTER 15 SPOILERS ARE OUT fact: scarlett johansson is NOT attractive how has the new red album still not leaked yet the last 7 hours just fucking flew past me I swear weekends are in 2x speed 