"We had it all, and watched it slip away... Where are we now? Not where we want to be." "I am always missing her." @username is reading my tweets... http://t.co/9T3q6sThmP @username here I go again... You are not. What @username is doing now... http://t.co/XvdO5P4WKJ But I know we'll meet again some sunny day! Maybe you won't feel the same, but you have to know... @username :( Then who am I? Even a strange is someone. @username Look, I'm not upset, just confused. Don't you worry child! ;) "Is my story over?" Y AHORA 30 SECONDS TO MARS. Are you fucking kidding me? @username "Acoustic #3" de Goo Goo Dolls. "And if it's over It hurts but I'm giving you my word I hope that you're always Happy like we were Happy like we were" "And I don't know how you found me..." "One girl and one boy." I'm sooo gonna regret this. "And we'll keep on fighting... 'til the end." “@username: I'll always be there when you need me.” And when you don't I will be there too ??@username Flashbacks, flashbacks everywhere! "I've fallen for your eyes, but they don't know me yet." Freddy Mercury en su video de "We are the champions" es bien sensual. ?????????? "Tell me something to pass by." Please don't take my sunshine away... Will I make it? Oh, baby, at least let me hope so! I almost fainted, good Lord... "He is as crazy as the moon." "Would you hold my hand... If I saw you in Heaven?" “I told you to wait!” "But baby, there you go again, there you go again, making me love you!" YA ACABÉ EL TRABAJO DE ANATOMÍA ???? "But I don't want to be your friend, I want to kiss your neck." @username “Ed Wood” @username makes my days brighter and sweeter!! ???????????????????? Mis tweets son súper aburridos ahora :< "Oh, I know the ache you have held in your heart... But darling, I have felt it too." Oh, no... Shuffle... NO. "I'll hold you in my heart until I can hold you in my arms." @username U are not. <3 @username You're welcome. Remember that sometimes when we think we're alone is because we're used to company as we imagine it. Stay strong! @username TUITAZO. You are proof that distance has nothing to do with love, @username "There's no way escaping your love!" Lights guided me home. And you fixed me. Shut the FUCK up! @username Team Marsupiales “You know it's gonna be... Alright!” Me hicieron un collage hermoso ???? "And now I tell you openly, you have my heart so don’t hurt me, you’re what I couldn’t find." @username Don't worry, everything will be okay... On time. "I'm devoted, and you know it! And you know it!" @username I miss you @username A lot better, right after a panic attack. I have to stop over reacting... @username I hope that too, and I also hope you REALLY feel better, remember I'm here to talk. @username Yep, take care, dude. Goodnight, @username Dear delegate, this comission misses your company quite terribly! With good food, Souls may rest. @username That means a lot :) Somehow I feel at home again... I don't love you like I loved you yesterday... (????) (?) @username First one @username  s0 pr377y @username  don't hate me :( It's all in my mind, it's all in my mind!! @username Ash ???? @username  what Heaven looks like. Lucky smile, dude. @username know that feel http://t.co/D8HDyMmvjt Yo Sophie y él Howl... ???? @username  makes the world better tbh Canciones hermosas y ésta. (Tangerine Dream - Norwegian Wood). http://t.co/CZom1Zxaf9 @username Usted no es fea ;) @username De 30 Seconds To Mars http://t.co/bBsSpi39Pz @username is fangirling... ???????? http://t.co/Ira04UfMv5 @username Three Black Feathers de Jim Moray @username thank you for everything! ?????? 'Cause now I have to pretend that I don't really care... @username see you on Thursday! ???????????? http://t.co/MdCKaHwtcK @username Rolling Stones Rock and Roll Circus ???? @username Mmm, entonces Ed Wood :) Like the bloodstains on the pillow case that I wash everyday... He fades away. @username should sleep...???? http://t.co/A3yDkooBwO “I had to fall, to lose it all... But in the end... It doesn't even matter!” @username while Autumn you can hug a tree, which shows beauty in keeping... And letting go. Stay strong, friend "And well she loves you, the way she says that she loves you  While she's fucking behind your back!" @username you are beautiful... And amazing. ?? @username And you are beautiful too!! @username Time flies... @username ok, look for your DM “@username: Elephant painting an elephant ???? http://t.co/eNLKE0ZqR9” @username ???????? “I'm alive! And oh... I can fly, I can fly, I can fly! @username güinter is not sou far agüey @username #greñasmakeworldgoround @username Good luck, baby ???? “@username: newborn baby squirrel ? ' http://t.co/hArKjBZ5YI” @username ???? @username it stopped at a sexy/weird... What? http://t.co/i7GxT3aDI6 Errr... Happy Birtday to @username, I admire you, thanks for all these years of dreams. ?????????????? http://t.co/jgOXRvMJNz @username fuck the others, I love you @username though good and bad you have me here @username Because most people are shit. @username Wish I did “Wherever you are, you shall be my star. ” 