@username JAJAJAJJAJAJJAAJJJAJAJAJAJAJ ME MUERO TU PADRE ES UN GENIO JAJAJAJAJ "I keep staring at that empty seat again And I know this night I'll probably just end up high out of my mind" http://t.co/9ctBZTWByH @username JAJAJAJAJJ y lo twittea serás idiotooooo XD Las tildes son sexys. @username I JUST WANNA FLYYY LIKE EVERYONE ELSE "Maybe together we can get somewhere" I see the riot grow see the riot grow I see the skyline glow see the skyline glow http://t.co/9ctBZUNoWT It was so beautiful it hurt "Silence speaks when words can't". THEY ALL SING FOR YOUUUUUUU ITS ALWAYS BEEN ABOUT YOUUUUUUUUUUUUU IS IT THE WHOLE I LIKE MEN THING??????????????' "Love is hard. If it was easy it woudln't mean nothing" Semos wapos http://t.co/wppIuNVjwF Nothing's gonna bring him back. http://t.co/DexPLcsJgo Everything is your choice. Wake up. "'Cause I know I'm a mess he don't wanna clean up" Very well fandango "Love, don't cry. Soon comes rain. Dry your eyes." http://t.co/FXDkGYSzsB "Shouting out of my windows Roll down Cause I don't care anymore Said I don't care" http://t.co/ud8JaxVv2W I couldnt wait that long. @username Y LO TWITTEA JAJAJAJAJAJAJAJ IN YOUR HEAD IN YOUR HEAD THEY ARE FIGHTINGGGGGGGGGGGGGGGG If this is all there is, Don't wake me for the fight. http://t.co/usRgNbOvpR You can choose to run off or roll down the hill my trains of thoughts loose me I’m on some real shit here http://t.co/h3GpaNSzbV Its hard. Believe me, I try. Check out my @username Speedtest result! What's your speed? http://t.co/VJoq4j3PX9 #speedtest you can't just ask someone why they're 3D Don't seek those who don't do anything to find you. The hardest thing to learn is to lose something you've earned Saw your name in the sand. http://t.co/IVQrXwp9wb Barbie really squirts http://t.co/wpe9vSgjxm Me encanta recibir muchos favs a twitts QUE NO ESCRIBO YO GRACIAS TOMMY Y ANDRÉS "Nobody is too busy, it's just a matter of priorities". I BET MY LIFEEEEEEEEEEEEEE ON YOUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUU Well I'm just a slave unto the night http://t.co/81RIYVdSRN What if u never found it I'm back before the snow. http://t.co/O4xRZoGOTa "I've got a blank space babe, and i'll write your name" You light me up inside. Tears don't fall, they carry light. Where there is desire There is gonna be a flame Where there is a flame Someone's bound to get burned @username know that feel bro CONSUMPTION I was young, so I forgot. It's so cold in a place you call home "We're all just looking for love to change the world." carry on It feels so wrong. The fire in your eyes made this turn bliss @username i will always love you mi beloved reichy "Ever wonder 'bout what he's doing" Why do we fall in love so easy? "Loving you was the most exquisite form of self destruction". Ignore how you feel, and act the way you want to be. What's that that you're hiding? http://t.co/99gQ9a2HIo you go hard on tequilas at a party and end up sucking 1 maybe 9 dicks and people start putting labels on you Don't become who hurt you. "2am is for the poets who can't sleep because their minds are alive with words for someone who's not… http://t.co/SOfKbdzMWJ I WOKE UP LIKE THISSSSSSS Men know what men like "We are here to laugh at the odds and live our lives so well that Death will tremble to take us". Don't fear the bear. http://t.co/v7Q9lDI2r7 Hey, let's get it now! "You know its raining outside when you go outside and you get wet" Salad please I'm trying to eat!!!!!!!! "Salad pls I'm trying to eat!" JAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJA ES QUE NO PUEDO http://t.co/fpjikZPDRV "Love that you just can't help feeling" A road where you can find your limits, where you can find yourself. The future is not that far away. Baby, you are always on my mind. Spend my days locked in a haze, Tryin' to forget you babe, I fall back down http://t.co/E5nnCCknfK And I know that I can survive I walked through fire to save my life http://t.co/uAtwyG1KxW I'll walk through fire to save my life. http://t.co/5uNMdFOHm7 "I was born sick, but I love it" "You pick me up when all my hope is gone" http://t.co/gq8KIlRNcY "The only heaven I'll be sent to is when I'm alone with you" It's hard to lose a chosen one SEXY COMILLASSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS You're gone and I gotta stay high all the time to keep you off my mind WOULD YOU NOT EAT MY PAAAAAAAAAANTS¿¿¿ Trying to forget you babe, I fall back down - Vayne buy IE + Internet Explorer? Someday I'll find myself at the end of the way. "When all my hope is gone". "If I murdered someone you're the person I'd call to help me drag the corpse across the living room floor". "Parents should accept more what their kids are and care less about what society thinks they need to be." YOU LIFT ME UPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPP "they are not always with who we spend our lives" @username TE AMO TANTO QUE TE RAJARÍA LA GARGANTA POR GILIPOLLAS PERO OYE QUIERES UN CAFÉ? Let the moon do what she does. She doesn't know she shines for us. Who can you trust http://t.co/7WaieDZkuG "Don't base your self-worth on the response of others". http://t.co/wIHtZG4HrY http://t.co/3QMDnEqMN3 Get rejected. And another one bites the dust. @username christian ????? I am waiting to break when I keep saying that I'm looking for a way to escape http://t.co/4nnkeeSAsK @username bonitas horas "The scariest part about letting someone in is that they could take one look inside of you and never come back". Not six times. Just once. 