Aight leggo Sittin' Sidewayz, instant classic. "It's hard for the great to tell somebody how to be great" Who's There - Hopsin ft. Jarren Benton & Dizzy Wright, Hop en Jarren baggen die track So, if I’ve really changed and I’m turning my back on my home, who did I actually turn my back on? Instrumental van The Morning, dayumn. @username Nowadays people are satisfied with stuff that is half decent. Lot of bullshit driving through our mindstream in today's world. "You belong to the loneliness of filling every need, you belong to the world, you belong to the temporary moments of a dream.." @username Btw, ever listened to The Weeknd? I just hear him echoing your style in R&B, to be honest.. A collabo would be killer. Another 4 down, 3 to go. If I ruled the world.. Imagine that. Kill it with fire, just do it! @username @username @username Aaaaaaight, de clash of the WDGAF! @username Goddamn I want that shit, drop by Agga aight? RT @username: Did you hear about the Michael J Fox diet?  A shake for breakfast, a shake for lunch, then a sensible dinner. "But baby it's okay.. I swear it's okay." I'll show you the ropes so you can hang yourself. To all the killers and the hundred dolla billers And suddenly I'm awake again. I guess I must've done something good for God to bless me with a lady like you. @username Thanks Vince! ???? @username Je weetzelf pushin roti's all day nigga @username @username Ja kno' fade aweh bless bombaclot ok. @username @username Peace on you too son of a beach I'm going back to Italia @username @username or stay foolin @username @username I couldn't give a fuck less about your follow. Het is gewoon leuk om mensen die shit serieus nemen te trollen. @username @username You talkin to the mirror again? ???????? @username It's all love nohomo @username That's funneeeeeeeh #ok "I'm fallin and I can't turn back" Finally awake. It's always about me. Die mashup van Jhené's Runaway, Weeknd's Rolling Stone en Frank Ocean's Acura Integurl is heaven to ears. Waiting for an official collabo! @username +1 for sexism! @username Ahaha with a great age comes great responsibility bedoel je? Ik zie die shit ook al aankomen helaas.. @username Aiii shots fired naar Jason In 7 minutes, Vinai Ramjiawan will reach his 18th year of life. Hail the king! @username Thanks bro! GO VINAI, IT'S YO BIRTHDAY!! @username Thanks Pat!! I'd like to thank my mom and dad for putting me on this Earth at the time when I needed to wait just 5 days before starting to drink again. @username Of course I'm thanking 'em for that! Like.. duh! "Clap along if you feel like a groom without a roofie!" Get live muthafuckas! Who Blew Ya - Notorious B.I.T.C.H. Just a friendly reminder to you that I'm doing great. Now go love your life, take another look and start the hate. I'll always find a path. G'night! @username JA DAAR BEN JE WEL MOOI 1 UUR TE LAAT MEE CEES HET IS OVER TUSSEN ONS "I'm out for presidents to represent me" Fuck this. Creabeatrixenophobia Wen Uuu - Shlohmo, relaxing music is what I need right now. "I don't really cry ask why, because inside no one ever really dies, your presence is still alive" RT @username: If you lend someone $20 and you never see them again, it was worth the $20. Time to go home! RT @username: I'll be thinking about you. // aii esso naar @username @username JA GODVERDOMME JA @username @username Aight shots fired naar @username Klap een long if you feel like breathing is difficult - Pharrell Williams @username You ain't got this you way too late nigga Talk cursive to me. Some chickens just need to meet a fine butcher. Whatchu know 'bout niggarabbitz? http://t.co/GRL8QwvxbV Fuckin' in the bushes - Oasis, één van m'n favoriete rocknummers because.. It is what it is. @username That's the spirit! Stay strong :) @username yeah really! See that soap? - Justin Bieber ft. José, Jaevon, Tyrell & Luis Follow a boy on Instagram: http://t.co/gChZt6K5cL Light's out, TKO Promovideo done, thanks @username #HardBattles #MostWanted BRING IT ON NIGGGAAAA http://t.co/5fqwfgWwnp "Know we were going through some shit, name a couple that isn't" Simple but true. @username This is what we need. A great app with great service, always updating their status. Thank you Movie Box! :) RT @username: FLAPPY BIRD CHEAT http://t.co/a1yamga7DL @username Yo, ff Followback voor DM? Sensual Woman - The Herbaliser Liar liar pants on FAYA #sorrymrsdeboer RT @username: Tough immigration policies: turning welfare into farewell. Mornings ain't my cup of tea http://t.co/C2bYyM58yR Jah No Partial (Skream Remix) - Major Lazer @username @username @username #teamagga on that shit My baby brother got #skills! #cute http://t.co/ptCAg8mDcP Windspeaks - Nujabes ft. Uyama Hiroto, beste studymusic die er is. RT @username: #ThisCouldBeUsButYouPlayin http://t.co/h0lGgNtCls http://t.co/MLo8GJEzsu I guess every superhero need his theme music Cerebral Palsy phase.. Gimme that shit @username Noh Cake, cake cake cake cake cake, 500 million I got a pound cake.. Ait ok man Mustard on da beat http://t.co/KoRD5QB1nq Aight I want a posse cut wif Joey Bada$$, Gambino, Chance TR, Drake, Asher Roth. MAKE IT HAPPEN @username @username @username @username Hmm bollocks, ff followback voor DM? Runaway - Jhené Aiko, The Weeknd & Frank Ocean.. Bless the one who made this blend Acid Rap, Innanetape, Run The Jewels en Czarface are mine! #RipThoseAlbums Keep tellin' you: I guess I'm the president because my lady's #1 With my mind on a murder and a murder on my mind Get yo point across like Jesus' hands You ain't gotta like it cuz the hood gon' love it http://t.co/OtzuxGsM08 @username Yeah, definitely know that feel @username Good luck, hope you find it! :p Wait, slow it down, let me rewrite that. 