? The Chauffeur - 2009 Remastered Version – Duran Duran http://t.co/20SAddtM80 #NowPlaying #pezzoni ? Knights in White Satin – Giorgio Moroder http://t.co/31rxLayqky #NowPlaying #approfondirecapolavori ? 24 – Red House Painters http://t.co/qPImEuDUFT #NowPlaying How Gravity Explains Why Time Never Runs Backward | WIRED http://t.co/sbBC4WbyVC ? Grace Under Pressure – John Scofield http://t.co/YsCEyewY8J #NowPlaying #approfondirecapolavori ? The Black Saint And The Sinner Lady – Charles Mingus http://t.co/Ny8s5vu3iF #NowPlaying IRL: The OnePlus One is everything my iPhone wasn't http://t.co/WZtFjeBRH1 via @username Player Focus: Has Bojan Finally Found a Home from Home at Stoke? - article by @username via @username - http://t.co/5NNK3Pj5sC David Bowie- 05 Always Crashing in the Same Car: http://t.co/gOMVGpOmZh via @username ? Peace – Ornette Coleman http://t.co/bD1ILhgfBM #NowPlaying Moby --- New Dawn Fades --- Heat Soundtrack: http://t.co/z4JbCRh5MP via @username League Focus: Set-Pieces Still Key to Success in Serie A - article by @username via @username - http://t.co/bftd5NgEsn ? The Essential – Scott Joplin http://t.co/Z2u3hqoxr7 #NowPlaying It’s wrong to sack a scientist for her opinions | Andrew Brown http://t.co/KT1m4LSw2z The Smashing Pumpkins - Siva: http://t.co/QAXMl4mJIl via @username different - sybil. - in a small town: http://t.co/5Phx5ZdoNv via @username Pizza Hut asked a bunch of old Italian people to judge its pizza: http://t.co/x31XwhDVM8 via @username The Pills - Face Off: http://t.co/KbrJUohKY8 via @username ? The Essential Bill Withers – Bill Withers http://t.co/XvQGtNsL4e #NowPlaying Gordon Brown: without winning an election, he has left a legacy greater than Tony Blair’s - http://t.co/WQhNE7fLRn via @username Jurgen Klopp: If you only want success, support Bayern Munich http://t.co/e9rP3sMYSQ Bill Conti - Gonna Fly Now (Theme From Rocky): http://t.co/OwtfxJFK8L via @username Pesaro non delude *mai*. ? Hard Times for Dreamers – Brothers in Law http://t.co/vYYqQzeiy5 #NowPlaying ? When The Heart Emerges Glistening – Ambrose Akinmusire http://t.co/4A1bqxahbH #NowPlaying The evidence is in: there is no language instinct http://t.co/l1YT2EhSQY via @username Blonde Redhead - Dripping http://t.co/0pFgAmNL7G via @username This obsession with inheritance shows how much we’ve lost confidence in the future http://t.co/FD5XgrjS3p ? With Love – Ambrose Akinmusire http://t.co/ZGuKPe86x7 #NowPlaying Alexander Robotnick - Problèmes D'Amour / 12" Original (STEREO): http://t.co/fMi7E0SXvy via @username Moving for Love: Modern Relationship Milestone -- The Cut - http://t.co/XJCktbgiSF RT @username: A neat way to visualise your Last.fm listening data by @username: http://t.co/kUkVIMuVJT check this @username ? Ah Um – Charles Mingus http://t.co/E5IJRLBZuS #NowPlaying ? The Quintet: Jazz At Massey Hall [Original Jazz Classics Remasters] – Various Artists http://t.co/hu8nEFLxvi #NowPlaying I'm in the top 5% of readers on @username! See the best of what I've read in 2014 http://t.co/s4TYkhAw9x #MyYearInPocket President Obama's Cuba Speech (Full HD): http://t.co/6I4bJndEGK via @username Watch "Thelonious Monk - Epistrophy" on YouTube - Thelonious Monk - Epistrophy: http://t.co/djozgrPO5T Pat Mastelotto / Tobias Ralph: ToPaRaMa - http://t.co/VBdfj7Bd7r Netflix, Spotify: Streaming is ruining the easy Christmas gift. - http://t.co/1EZ2ob5Xd1 Free chocolate at poster 39? #cns2011 12 guidelines for surviving science - http://t.co/vGNryNsSrY I'm enjoying 'Jack Sheldon - Palermo Walk' on the Bebop channel at @username http://t.co/KUvRSbvijB I'm enjoying 'Cannonball Adderley - Grand Central (with John Coltrane)' on the Bebop channel at @username http://t.co/KUvRSbvijB SF MoMA for free today. 151 3rd street. 15 mins walking from hyatt. Nice way to spend free time left. #cns2011 #pezzoni ? Thème de Yoyo – Art Ensemble Of Chicago http://t.co/857X4eU0m3 #NowPlaying #acquistiobbligatori The Beach Boys - Pet Sounds [pic] http://ff.im/-ADjOr can't wait to read Friston's review and the first papers on the new Brain Connectivity journal http://bit.ly/asxblU #neuroscience #beforeDSOTM Pink Floyd - Fat Old Sun (Pt 1) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OjcK2Yosbu8 http://ff.im/-CuHQM #beforeDSOTM Pink Floyd - Fat Old Sun (Pt 2) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w79sOmN6yyc&feature=related http://ff.im/-CuJ2N The Eagles - Theme From Station Six Sahara #scopertadelgiorno http://ff.im/-CEiNO Mark Shuttleworth @username Ubuntu UDS http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rjyNTCHVyxs&feature=youtu.be #30daysSongChallenge - Day 01 - Your Favorite Song - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BGys4WhZNYg http://ff.im/-F2Kpo #30daysSongChallenge - Day 02 - Your least Favorite Song - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rY0WxgSXdEE http://ff.im/-F8YGU #30DaySongChallenge - day 03 - a song that makes you happy - The Housemartins - Happy Hour... http://ff.im/-Ffdfn 