#wp8 shame. Does not hv file manager. I cant find my downloaded files(pdf,mp4). Shame shame. Brad Hodge should be mom today #pepsiipl. Very effective innings by ex skipper D Sammy. Might be the difference of 2 team. #ct13 I just joined LinkedIn and created my professional profile. Join my network. http://t.co/NPCv8nc1JZ #in "Mirror is my best friend, because when I cry it never laughs" -- C. Chaplin Its great to hear that a new comer doing well in world stage. #pvsindhu keep it up. We are proud of you. May Prior should not play the next game. Poor performance. New should get the chance. #ashes S Broad magnificent. But I Bell should get the man of the match. #ashes @username l wd hv ensure common minimal education 4 free of cost, and enriched communication system with full security. #Pradhanmantri shared a link http://t.co/o07ftoHzIw #nokia #lumia 520 very bad service. I did not get #Amber update yet. They are saying to wait and wait. How long I have to wait no one knows. @username no #amber update yet in India. cc is saying to wait and wait. How long I will wait. will I get the update for my lumia 520? @username how much to wait for amber update. 2 legends face 2 face probably for d last time. Heart is divided by S and R. #clt20 #cricket @username No response. Its clear 2 every 1 dt #Nokia hz stopped d #amberupdate in India atleast.Chears #lumians u r totally **** all d way At the age 25 @username (Virat Kohli) owns 20 international centuries(16 odi + 4 test). He should not be treated as a young player any more. What a fate!! Sikhar Dhawan is the last boy in the. His mark shit contains just 95 in just 86 balls against Australia. Whn d cricket got "Sachin"@username word.I was Sachin(=6)yrs of old.2dy aftr ruling 4Sachin yrs(=24)my gf ready 2 marry me.#ThankYouSachin I just got a personalized digital autograph from Sachin Tendulkar & @username. http://t.co/bGXjcj3kEO To get yours Tweet @username #ThankYouSachin. Maratha kingdom has been handed over by Sachin @username to ROhit. #thankyousachin No useful update still now. Feet suckers are busy everywhere everyday and trying to make anybody Sachin Tendulkar by words. shared a link http://t.co/09OqWhyW0w My blood group is O+ FIRE 2013 in on. Fire 2013 successfully finished. @username shared a link http://t.co/G9O1sy9po7 merry christmas to everyone. may it bring all of you a lot of good cheer. history will remember jacques kallis as one of the greatest to have played the game. the game is richer for him having played it.#kallis i am stunned. a few days ago kallis bowled like a full 3rd seamer and batted sumptuously in the 2nd innings. too early to retire? @username How to download tweets by tweet-id for research purpose? Please let me know ASAP RT: bitter sweet for ashwin. bcci indian cricketer of the year on the day he is left out of the side? (via @username) England lost #ashes 0-5. #KP best english batsman scored 3 & 6 in last match. #Stoke is new find for England. Alash #Bengal will not get Manoj Twari and Md. Sami in #Rangi quarter final. The moral of Bengal team should be high after beating T'nadu. Finally after 6 matches a non-loose non-drawn result. Its a dramatic tie #IndVaNZL in ODI cricket.  http://t.co/q7sbbUHqqg RT: Well done son of the soil @username PADAM SHRI yuvraj singhjii.well done.proud of you rocky (via @username) @username #7RCR stop corruption in education. Have a great app idea? Share and win 1 Million. T & C Apply http://t.co/pqawOLxjQs I just scored 700 points. Beat my score & win a trip to Goa /Srinagar or #HIL Merchandise! Play:http://t.co/Etvx83c9Nl I just scored 4200 points. Beat my score & win a trip to Goa /Srinagar or #HIL Merchandise! Play:http://t.co/Etvx83c9Nl I just scored 18400 points. Beat my score & win a trip to Goa /Srinagar or #HIL Merchandise! Play:http://t.co/Etvx83tcPl I just scored 18400 points. Beat my score & win a trip to Goa /Srinagar or #HIL Merchandise! Play:http://t.co/Etvx83c9Nl #IndVsPak #asiacup Dinesh Karthik should v d Man of d series. He empowered Sangakara in d prev match & 2day Hafeez, Maqshood 2 kill India. shared a link http://t.co/NF160Oont5 Pak: No No we will go to ICC to ban WI. It was not a April fool. We were not even ready for that. #PakvWI Nokia lumia 520 and Nokia X is much better than Samsung under 10000 INR. I love Nokia. #nokia #Lumia #Samsung. MSD won my heart by not scoring any run. His bro the run machine was just awesome. #ViratKohli #dhoni #INDvsSA Dont blame @username. Last 11 ball in Indian innings @username and @username scored only 8 runs. y ? coz It happens in cricket and life. no more Kings XI (eleven) Punjab Vs Kolkata IX (nine) Riders (dont count @username and Youshuf Pathan). #IPL7 #kkr Just garbage #kkr #KKRvsRR. Remove all support staffs. There is no talent hunter for KKR. Lets see how long #KKR can survive. #pepsiIPL Flipkart rolls out the red carpet for their customers. Make sure to sign up for their priority service http://t.co/iD6lu0aL7T #FlipkartFirst I hv doubt about the success rate of captaincy of @username in his whole career. Can anyone help me by the giving his stat. #PepsiIPL #DDvsRCB Delhi- walo are in big trouble. Attack from two end Bengalore and Gujarat. #IPL2014 #RCBvsDD #DD #MPvote @username When will we get wp8.1 OTA update here in India? There are a lots of features we are missing. Who ever wins no Bengali people will be sad. Bengal win today. #KKRvsKXIP #Saha #IPLFINAL2014 Preity Zinta is looking most beautiful with her joyful smile seeing #Saha 's batting. I am in love with her innocent smile. @username Is there any tentative time line for wp8.1 OTA update here in India? @username Dear Sir, We are serving "Cross Lingual Information Access" DIT funded project. We are out of salary for 15 months. Please help @username CLIA DIT funded project out fund so out of salary for 15 fifteennnnnnnnnn months. We research students are about die. plz help If you are anti Hindu you are secular #WhyMediaSoAntiHindu. Feeling very sad Manish Chulbul Pandey (fearless) #IPLFinal2014 #KKRvsKXIP This night belongs to Knights. #IPLFinal2014 #KKRvsKXIP @username worst furrrrrrrr so far in the #FIFA world cup. To get prize Oscar need to write good script for Hulk. @username #BraVsGer. Do not dream 2 be opener they can score only 33,9. Dream about 2 bat 4 d final wicket they will score 111,176+. #IndvsEng @username #ArmsWideOpen Argentina will win by 2-1 How 2 get job n #Brazil difference? Its probably d most tension free job n d world.U can conceive 3+ goals per match. No1 is goin 2 blame u. There r lots of thing 2 learn 4m #wp81 1. dont set any set any release date 2. just spread rumor. 3. postpone date 4. repeat prev steps yes its a 100 4 @username but its 1 of d most valuable innings for any Indian played at lords. Thanks a lot @username. 4 the next test @username and @username should play in place of @username and Stuart Binney Missing @username and @username at slip. #IndvsEng. Indian bowlers allowed to come back in form two English batsman. @username is nothing but a garbage in the team now. Scores nothing, cant kill time and misses catches in the slip #IndvsEng Does @username get out? OOh no. He yet to face a ball. #IndvsEng @username Complete the sentence: ‘My Life without my smartphone would be Daanang with out @username . @username Q6. My Life without my smartphone would be a ship without a radder. @username Q6. Complete the sentence: ‘My Life without my smartphone would be sweet without sugar. @username Complete the sentence: ‘My Life without my smartphone would be Kitkat without crunch. @username yes it seems so if the http://t.co/reg99GFjM7 is not telling lies. Approaches are awesome. @username #HIVEInisde Yes, it seems so if http://t.co/reg99GFjM7 is not telling lies.Shown features in the site are awesome,just mind blowing. #IndvsEng  Its better by fighting 2 loose by 5-0 than 2 loose like this way continuously.histroy will say India lose by 3-1 bt wont tell d Harassed in passport office Kolkata. What to do when when everything goes against me? How to stay clam? @username Why we cant access ad-hoc wifi? How to access it? @username How to access printers? #CLT20 how many run conceded till now by #kkr? how many chance they waste ed? #narine 's punishment is nothing but #csk 's conspiracy @username I use linux (Ubuntu 14.04) in my laptop. I saw there is no way to connect ubuntu and wp8.1. Can u halp me on this issue #CLT20Final #CSKvsKKR @username should hv send Y Pathan at 3. coz 1st wicket gone after 10 overs. I think 3 overs has been wested. #CLT20Final #CSKvsKKR Yes, I wz r8. #kkr wz sort of 3 overs. they had d game out of dr grip whenever a wicket was fallen.Excellent @username #CSKvsKKR #CLT20Final @username was more flexible as captain. @username did not let any ball waste after a wicket fall. @username wasted 3 overs. #CLT20Final #CSKvsKKR @username is probably the only player who holds a ton in every format and  in big stage. @username Hats off. It seems 2 me that u r a bulldozer like @username, finisher like @username. Your clean stepouts r like @username. WOW #flipkart #flipkart totally flop, #flipkart #flipkart out of stock. #flipkart #flipkart could have rock, #flipkart #flipkart made a mock. @username I use linux (Ubuntu 14.04) in my laptop. I saw there is no way to connect ubuntu and wp8.1. Can u halp me on this issue @username Yes, I want 2 transfer files both ways lumia-Ubuntu14.04. I hv tried mtp file system 2 do so as described/prescribed by experts. #ATK 's getting worse day by day. Once Yudhisthir promises Krishna to delivery a flute by #BlueDart . After that no1 heard Krishna's flute tune and Yudhisthir left the world. Only 1 god could have made a win 4 India today #INDvsAUS, i.e @username.Tears in my eyes.At 1 stage India only required 65 for 5 wickets For the mentality Dhawan and Rahul should be punished. Two other batsmen should get chance. #INDvsAUS #OwnTheJersey @username Q2) 2 centuries Rahul Dravid scored 