I really want a job but no one will take on someone part time and I cant leave school. I never realized how annoying 9/10 year olds are until I met my boyfriends niece I think tomorrow will be one of those "take 2 million phitos and only be happy with 5 and edit the crap out of them" days That last retweet actually worries me now. I did a thing and started a blog I love having a Tidy room I just don't like putting things away or folding clothes Another storm this morning 60% of the time I spend at my boyfriends house I feel like he thinks I am an idiot and that his family hate me. I'm always the bad guy. So now I am sat alone in his bedroom while they all have lunch downstairs Back to square one @username your hair grows 1cm a month more or less, so cutting it every month doesn't really help for leaving it long. @username in that case my advice would be cut off all the damage, and then start trimming 1 cm off every 3 months. Back to school tomorrow And I have't done my hairstyles project for class Found the perfect bikini for this summer :) If this headache doesn't stop I am going to start crying I really don't want to move but I need to get stuff ready for school tomorrow and then i would have to get up anyway for bed. I have finally understood that yeah maybe I should weigh less to be healthy but ya know what? I am not hugely fat and disgusting I am actually the average size. It's not like I am as wide as I am tall Can you be allergic to like all food? I go through stages of loving my makeup and wanting to use it all, all of the time, and then hating the idea of spending 20 mins on it I pulled out of my scalp what I thought was one thick hair with a split end. Turns out it was like 5 hairs together, perfectly healthy Get #FeaturePoints on iOS or Android to earn points you can exchange for great prizes for trying free apps Use this code EXXHWT for 50 point Hi guys another girl on here was nice enough to post about this app and I thought I would share it.… http://t.co/gpEzQT9Bf6 A list of people I actually like being around http://t.co/4ImkcSCgOl All this about subway halal meat stuff- why not make it a choice instead of a must? I don't live in my own country and I (continued) Don't expect them to change to british ways here in Spain just because i want them to. If a bar doesn't serve tea I wont tell them not to(c) Serve coffee and instead serve tea. At most I would ask for it as an option. @username  the needle should be in a sealed package, taken out, used and then thrown away in front of you. 1 needle for 1 tattoo :) Why is saying "you're in this country you should at least speak it's language" rude/racist/whatever? I live in Spain, and have done for the last 10 years. I had to learn Spanish, I even got bullied at school for being English. I don't think it's racist or rude or whatever you want to call it to have to be able to speak the language of the country you are in I want to make a youtube channel but then I think "you have no camera, you don't like talking to people and no one would probably watch you Want to check out my blog? The link is in my bio :) If you check out my blog please tell me what you think! The good and the bad please! I just posted a new post on body confidence! Check it out? I'm sorry but if you're a dickhead don't go out. Too many of them about making me sick @username It's torture here with the boyfriends family and they keep fighting in front of me Good morning twitter! Had no internet yesterday and it made me realize just how much I need it in my life Writing a new post New post up if you'd like to check it out :) link in bio Giving myself a well deserved mani pedi today :) Got a new teacher today and I think she is going to be the one who shows us the most. Only 3 weeks… http://t.co/Lqsiru4IYt Out again with @username :) listening to #bvb http://t.co/BbOpRxcYmp I #love living in #spain http://t.co/ssAl30ECvy Sat in the car with friends waiting for class to start :) new post up soon on the blog http://t.co/KAl4itZbi4 A little #nailart from yesterday. http://t.co/n87fRz9eor Just posted a photo http://t.co/DmHVav2cEm I feel like I am going to pass out Day off school bc I can barely move. My back is causing me so much pain right now New #nailart for the weekend. Still not decided if I am going to keep it like this though. #manicure http://t.co/VbW8BPdzB9 I think I will be keeping this #nailart for the weekend http://t.co/r2fdDs8bjV Sooo... doctor says I have a contracture. I have never heard of that in my life and I suppose it's just a really badly pulled muscle. They gave me an injection in the bottom of my back and it f***ing hurt. I even cried ! And I don't like needles.. Not sure if I would wear this myself but this is an #updo #hairstyle I did at school on Tuesday http://t.co/WpNOZxsU0U Another #updo from yesterday! From the back it looks like and octopus. Btw, new #blog #post is up! The… http://t.co/CAKeaVPyzS New post up on my blog! Link in bio! #bblogger #fbloggers #lbloggers #blogger #monthyfaves Just one more week of official school, then exams I have a feeling that today might not be as nice as yesterday I keep forgetting I have a tattoo and when I catch a glimpse of it I'm like "WTF IS THAT!? Oh, okay" If you like #nailart , go check out my latest post and give me your opinion! Link in bio! #bblogger… http://t.co/YiUnNg7m1l If you like the idea of there being a #nailart series on my blog, fave this tweet so I know! #bbloggers #fbloggers #manicure Definitely going to be an interesting blog post up tomorrow! A #shopmissa haul will be up and just… http://t.co/rPme7fgswh My #shopmissa #haul is up on my blog! Reviews for specific items will be coming soon! #bblogger… http://t.co/ghuFVLdO6H First #beach day of the year! Water's a little cold still, but still nice. http://t.co/Ce1k5a7gUV What would you like to see on my blog? Give me some sugestions! #bbloggers #fblogger #ideas #help I have a mini #diy #planer post up on my blog! See how I made mine, it's easy! Link in bio! http://t.co/17Y448i1wu Watching Ghost in the Shell tonight Waking up at 6:30 in the morning on a Sunday is always great. I am actually comfortable enough at my boyfriends house to go to the bathroom on my own at 6:52 in the morning. SUCCESS Pets | What You Should Take Into Consideration Before Getting One https://t.co/Yo6bYfMpSv on @username If you´re thinking of getting a pet, I have a post http://t.co/8ENQflko7c with tips on how to decide if to get one or not. #lblogger It seems like you need money to make  money v.v New post up! What you should take into account when deciding to get a #pet or not. Links in my bio!… http://t.co/Jw9iohBXbs #SHOUTOUT to the first 5 people on #twitter and #instagram ! Click here: https://t.co/4HCc2b6xu5 http://t.co/PVatxn7wEg @username  posted: What to think about before getting a pet http://t.co/8ENQflko7c #lbloggers #bbloggers Check out my last picture tweet if you want a #SHOUTOUT  on #instagram  and #Twitter I really want to go upstairs and be on the laptop instead of the app but family is over and I'm just stuck here I don't want to waste another summer online but I probably will Taking photos for my upcoming reviews! Giving myself a treat and doing gel nails on myself #shopmissa #review up later! Link in bio! #bblogger #fblogger #lblogger http://t.co/iS773bko72 Did you see my #shopmissa #haul from last week? Check it out before I put my #shopmissa #review up! http://t.co/DBiZXyfJt8 My #shopmissa product review is up on my blog! Link in bio! shopmissa #bblogger #fblogger #lblogger http://t.co/UQfNwr6wcz I made it into an octopuss! Have you checked out my #summer #beauty tips post? There are tips for you… http://t.co/auOvWudOGI @username I do! But I probably shouldn't . Did you see my post with #summer #beauty tips for #hair and #skin ? check it out here : http://t.co/8ENQflko7c @username  #bblogger I want to start a #young #teen #series on the 1st of July, but I need your #questions ! #qanda… http://t.co/JSd9ruJRql a series for #young #teens will be starting on the 1st of June, but I need your questions! #questiontime #Question http://t.co/xfIRTmpEqU I need #questions for my new blog series! Get more info here : http://t.co/5c4hL3R58R @username  #qanda #bblogger #teens #lbloggers Wow! More than 500 page views! http://t.co/MRie0fsf0v I am thinking of cutting my hair short! Maybe shoulder length for starters? I am going to have to up my "girly game" if I cut my hair. Last time I had it short people literally spoke about me as "him" or "he". Only today, tomorrow and next week until schools out! This is going to be one of the best summers of my life! Any #questions you want an honest #awnser to from another #teen #girl? Ask me anything for my new Young Teen Series starting on July 1st! I think I´ll be going to the #beach later. It´s too hot to be anywhere else! 