@username Brisbane is right here! It is you who are far away. Also, there will be planes. JOBS: 10 Mid-career research fellowships, QUT.  Feel free to contact me if interested in the Digital Media area. http://t.co/SjILyLt1bI Happy birthday Franz Kafka, prophet of alienation and foreseer of life in the contemporary university http://t.co/Bk9SXB5wCJ @username @username although the CCI Winter School Mentors' table was SO much better behaved this year… ;) @username good morning Me too! And @username and @username!  MT @username: About to speak at the #ATOM13 Social Media Masterclass. Slides up later today. Oh and @username also! #ATOM13 @username I reckon there's a fair chance of that @username at least I didn't mention Jesus Thanks @username: Three social media dynamics - content&connection - creativity&consumption -intimacy&publicness @username #ATOM13 @username @username @username @username is this it? Has the world ended? wow, #anzca2013 is not very tweeted @username I hope you have your phone set up to capture reaction videos @username Every John Hartley keynote ever: the #redwedding episode, only for Media Studies. You can tell him I said that. @username @username @username not yet, not really @username thanks Rohan! List of proposed etymologies of OK http://t.co/yY4JeRnOlN @username I never know how to feel about that one @username definitely a compliment. I just wonder about the gender politics of these things sometimes! @username @username everything but the first one. @username @username congrats! C'mon you guys, where'd you hide the *real* #CCIWS13 feedback forms? http://t.co/3y2Vr9Gpib @username they were very well behaved this year. In comparison. @username @username yes because we wouldn't want...oh wait @username @username there was still pool and karaoke! Hijinks galore! @username gosh I wish I'd known you were going to be in Australia :( @username definitely! @username @username almost identical conversations & debates in digital humanities & internet studies How Brazilian protesters are using Twitter (Guardian Data Blog) - congrats @username et al http://t.co/fli4djon09 - ping @username How Australian Politicians Gained Their Twitter Followers - Mapping Online Publics http://t.co/gG99KTtUWY I get a lot more too much email in my new role at work, but when the emails are glowing PhD examiner's reports, that's A-OK with me. @username you're making it worse nic. Go get a beer and instagram a pony or something. OH NOES MT @username Tonight's guest tweeter is Assistant Prof of Journalism & Communications, Glen Fuller @username. #Lateline 1035PM @username @username you're both blocked @username just how many #cciws alumni are at #oiisdp anyway? @username you win at feelings AND thoughts @username I didn't know I had such a dictum @username  you may have been hacked luv Buffer Festival: "a multi-day theatrical event that showcases the best creative work from video creators on YouTube." http://t.co/FP9A7C0Ha0 @username *confused face* @username only mid-career ones this year sorry :( @username yeah close in Aug for 2014 YES @username: "considering an ignite talk with just pictures of the PM. obvious title "No Selfie Control", will take other suggestions” I hereby challenge you all. RT @username: JOB: Director of Cat-Meme Creation http://t.co/JJCPzclGxi (via @username) You can ignore it on Twitter, you can ignore it on telly, but you better wear noise cancelling cans if you want to ignore it IRL. #origin Did you know there is such a thing as Fax Spam? Well there is and here's some. http://t.co/ip97q4TmZ0 @username CCI does. It's actually necessary for some things believe it or not @username @username that's a great idea, applicable to e.g. scientists, politicians, bands/artists…. My NECTAR has spawned an instance thx @username In my experience so far: the more eminent and experienced the PhD examiner, the more generous and fair the report. #phdchat @username people earlier in their careers may compare people with themselves, not realising their standard is higher than the norm. @username or they may be highly invested in a particular sub-specialism. Of course this isn't always the case @username just time in the job as a supervisor, not even an examiner. maybe we should ask for X completions before examiners get quals @username yeah that all sounds unfortunate. END ROYAL BABY WAIT  CONV TO ROYAL BABYNAME WAIT @username yes but these are actual headlines at bottom of TV screen. Interrupted only by the news ticker - earthquakes, civil unrest, etc There is seriously NOTHING ELSE HAPPENING What happens if the Royals have an intersex baby? @username would the Royals disclose that though? @username  I know you hate people on twitter loudly performing not liking things that other people like but this is about more than a baby. @username ok I must have a different stream. I haven't seen that. @username @username I couldn't care less what the Brits do with their monarchy, I'd just like it to not have anything to do with me. New article by @username, me @username & @username  Patterns of Talk on Twitter During the #qldfloods http://t.co/jdUFL3Z5sn @username "glorified op-ed" 4 Reasons that Rudd's PNG policy violates the rights of refugees  http://t.co/aAmw03i5Sq Compromised data? New paradigms in social media theory and methods - Oct 28-29, Ryerson, Toronto. CFP deadline 1 Aug http://t.co/yeg3XjBJ12 @username for a second there I thought it said. "Digital Natives". Congrats! grainy floppy hat selfie with newly doctored Dr @username ! @username QPAC Concert Hall http://t.co/QoBN4isUOE @username it's a perfectly nice photo @username @username @username @username @username Mac version slated for "the future" I believe. @username oh how fab. @username congrats! Not the easiest gig @username @username there's a reason it's mostly "writers" & PhD students who are post-word. Ppl who work alone @username @username I was determined I was doing my whole PhD in Mellel at one point. But then: supervisors, co-authors happened @username *waves* Our special issue of JOBEM on Emerging Methods for Digital Media Research is now fully open access - thanks to @username http://t.co/uG1FA7Xz8y @username hard straight edge case @username actually brilliant dreams - a Baym compendium. @username genius is painful Nancy Sigh MT @username: Interviews for Aus legal clerkships selected "by eliminating all the public school applicants" http://t.co/oReUEYrx11 @username "the reasoning was that private school kids would likely have connections that could benefit the firm". Fair enough. @username @username I could hook you up with some pretty sweet regional QLD connections mate @username @username I nearly did law after Country Qld SHS but luckily changed to classical music which weirdly is way more merit based. lots of goodies in there congrats @username et al. via @username: Platform Politics: special issue of Culture Machine http://t.co/uBJwuQvitT @username @username and only in the MOOC version @username @username wait which one of you is the funny one? @username actually I really can't complain about my resource base. But I do empathise! If you are trying not to eat icecream DO NOT CLICK HERE http://t.co/Zrepiffuiw oh @username what have you done. @username @username @username lovely pic! Was trying to think of a way to jointly troll Dr Who fans and #auspol junkies but they all seem to be doing such a good job on their own. Via @username: @username on the changing media landscape during an election campaign. http://t.co/k4oaDyTVP2 "You play a faceless, cloaked figure who glides through a vast desert towards a mountain on the horizon" http://t.co/J4SqCFqPno @username my shopping trolley murdered; my groceries just gone. @username I remember hearing the song on @username, not sure where I saw the video. Rage? Another @username  PhD all done and doctored. Congrats Elija!! All theses are available at http://t.co/k4rbJddzyn http://t.co/WqE8rzIxdW Agree with the Harvard Uni Library's statement against embargoing dissertations - nothing but career-limiting IMO https://t.co/344ZON2Tgg Yay @username & @username - Understanding Social Media looks smart and useful. http://t.co/ivGj1UFeSm @username @username it's different in different countries. In Australia PhD research is supported with public money, publishing is required. @username @username Students do however retain copyright and can embargo if they want. Usually for commercial or ethical reasons though AFAIK Seems wise, recommended etc RT @username: http://t.co/jKA8GndXFP every time someone retweets dawkins into my feed i read this to calm down 