Zoom H1, firmware 2.0 enables it to be used as USB audio interface http://t.co/3ngaa3w3 I just unlocked the "Shutterbug" badge on @username for adding photos to my check-ins. Say cheese! http://t.co/Kiw9kYWJ @username you're welcome Un capolavoro: "How To Kill a Mustache" http://t.co/ErOpICrm A free and open world depends on a free and open web. And a free and open web depends on me. http://t.co/WmaNDT9J #freeandopen A proposito: Ave #SMS, WhatsApp te salutat. FXFactory 4.0.1 = love @username Excellent work! as always. Greetings from Italy, go on guy. One rule always true: K.I.S.S., "Keep It Simple, Stupid" The Real Story Of Apple’s ‘Think Different’ Campaign http://t.co/wRJne5No #RedBull's College Marketing Whiz Strikes Out on His Own http://t.co/fTVJxhozgw Your FREE license of Ondesoft Audio Recorder for Mac is just a tweet away! Thanks to @username http://t.co/yqXotZNs6X The worst feedback is indifference: no feedback at all. That means we've created nothing but banality. Want to see a really action sport film? #BANFF Film Festival » http://t.co/aswemBHJcT (@username Cinema Orfeo w/ 2 others) http://t.co/pCxWHxE4fM A tiny diamond of some time ago http://t.co/uAFaWx61tv 'Shopped Stills From Action Movies with Guns Replaced with Thumbs-Ups http://t.co/DyuTMLi8TG Social media explained | via Ninja Marketing http://t.co/o5HsYaWrFq I just liked "Foursquare check-ins show the pulse of New York City and Tokyo" on Vimeo: http://t.co/54HD7MvExw IL CARTONE http://t.co/F0gvPzLSXL Droga5 hits again » Adweek "Ad of the Day": Spotify http://t.co/KR2K3I2Jqp Success is not the result of how long you do something. Success is the result of how well you do something. Noooooooooooooooooooo! Just say yes to Leo Burnett's IndieLisboa film festival spot http://t.co/PNn4ncuH5L Time passes, in every sense http://t.co/lvRP4N9MgZ "You have not lived today until you have done something for someone who can never repay you", John Bunyan INFOGRAPHIC «The World as 100 people» http://t.co/XgIWD0nGQz #proudtobeafanof you, if you do what you have to do Foursquare Meetup: Milano, LO, Italy | Apr 16 http://t.co/1b5XCZ5FmK Behind The Scenes Shots From Popular Movies ~ ThePhotomag http://t.co/zbzii5JR53 Dan Ariely: What makes us feel good about our work? | Video on http://t.co/nFeSJUf1I7 http://t.co/Hk5olYJ1kC Teamwork http://t.co/HgravM1eDs YouTube adds 'tape mode' to celebrate 57 years of noisy recordings http://t.co/gIUv5yQEMd Are You Suffering From High Effort and Low Impact? | Personal Branding Blog - Dan Schawbel http://t.co/HqJDgy9O1W 4sqDay, thanks to Matteo Sarzana Who isn't used to play with a yo-yo like him? http://t.co/cFsnnhyAuV Connect, touch, play! http://t.co/wRhw9Chkyo 6 Things You Are Doing to Damage Your Personal Brand (via @username) http://t.co/t4qC7eSJbI Really interesting, sadly true. Thanks to Filippo Selden for sharing it with me! http://t.co/NVKKXt0nTz @username Happily true. Success Is More Than Just Showing Up http://t.co/h1JvhyDzax Bye bye pros? Apple seems to be ready to be considered a consumer brand. http://t.co/0iF44MtRZo The new iPhone 5 TV ad: bye bye pros? Apple seems to be ready to be considered a consumer brand. http://t.co/IMQN4ACry3 Masterbrand Aperitivo http://t.co/hkbLyhzACz The Unexpected Antidote to Procrastination http://t.co/GzyGjzbyXK 10 Things I’ve Learned About Business from Mountain Biking http://t.co/9C7Tdw29EY Listening to Your Inner Voice Makes You a Better Manager http://t.co/5Jci8nefpt Well played, Samsung http://t.co/gNalWTAVHR Samsung Presents Advertising's Most Idiotically Primitive Husband Ever http://t.co/8vheimCIfB Red Bull aperitive http://t.co/xsogEXxfZy Friday's mood http://t.co/bzvcsNf5bF 17 Innovative Examples of Rebranding http://t.co/OmV5My29fo Gershwin in concert http://t.co/TM4yOGhHlO That's enough: #occupygezi Time to evolve. Again. At the end, this is one of the best «morning mood» I've ever listemed to. http://t.co/0ZjqDk2iem Filippo Selden guess what? I'm going to watch a movie where some "iron" meets for the third time a "man". (finally) How to literally stop people from driving drunk? http://t.co/vsiZ3OnfGb Business Model Canvas I <3 U FiorelLa and Claudia, this is a good morning quote. http://t.co/lxPcOAHdId IED Masterbrand - Brand Champions: Maria Camila http://t.co/6VMT1EmHFx Branding Strategy Insider | What Makes A Great Brand Story? http://t.co/QdNDosUizC And then videos arrived on #Instagram: #Vine died. End of the story. Do you want to be a superhero? Give it a look!  [thanks to FiorelLa for sharing it] http://t.co/0FzNK7xHNu This is the only lessons where you can stay on Facebook... 'cause the teacher is Cris Nulli, Client Partner #Facebook http://t.co/RVP6HPteba Just learn. http://t.co/kFfibxtw4M 97 years old + Microsot Paint = Hal Lasko. A great story about a great man and a great passion. ...someone still... http://t.co/I22ya8997E "The Golfers" http://t.co/V8CueYb9rY Let's golf! http://t.co/e01ggHIhwZ Don't waste your time: "Get Up Early (or Stay Up Late)" http://t.co/39zy7EzFi2 «One of many other industries affected by the Internet age has definitely been marketing. Because marketing is... http://t.co/Gtft1J6D3j 10 things Italy does better than anywhere else http://t.co/FgFhZXwGwb And so, after today, pay attention to that one who wants to bring you out for a pizza. http://t.co/RX0c8CN8iT Wonderful woman, isn't she? Nope, because he's a man. A great brand idea and a new push-up for every woman... or... http://t.co/KURwIY0HoY How relationships work. http://t.co/fixSg9UDeF Back to Italy Brand Management vs. Brand Leadership http://t.co/qqCqJq5Vna Google Glasses VS Spaceglasses? http://t.co/sNE7cXLPF8 Facebook, Google Drive, Instagram, Vimeo, SoundCloud, Dropbox, SugarSync, YouTube, Flickr, Google+, Box... e chi... http://t.co/9Ngjvhm2zT What if you have only another 5 minutes to live? Be passioned in everything you do, that's the only answer. #work4rich What if...? “I Forgot My Phone” http://t.co/UUCPPLon7u “We need to work smart, not (just) hard.” http://t.co/0dVgFqJmuo Brilliant. Absolutely brilliant. #Android #KitKat http://t.co/UoHHCZlFKG Check out my new #CV #CurriculumVitae (a creative one) on @username! http://t.co/RgS1Il7Vs3 Only for geeks #iOS7 #GM http://t.co/3GHo5nvvlS Why do we need a colored iPhone? Here one of the many theory. http://t.co/NgOvdasbPq Why do we need a colored iPhone? Here one of the many theories. http://t.co/FYy7peNtKT “Shoppers prefer the store because it's a place for exploration and dreaming.” (Stephen Jay, Managing Director @username Fitch) #branding Mercedes-Benz TV: MAGIC BODY CONTROL TV commercial "Chicken" http://t.co/Tj1omg57MF Just make me happy! Go and buy one for me. http://t.co/xeMDxnQqOZ Anyone with a cat perfectly knows it. http://t.co/B0P6SaPucf Gift card? Nope, motivational card! http://t.co/RmCO9GnpmB Those things are true even if you are italian! http://t.co/5EIWVdqyji WANT! (Christmas is coming) http://t.co/yyVQ7sidyZ IED Masterbrand on the way to Ferrero Italia! http://t.co/kZB19SZBdZ #Movember a palla!  by #VML http://t.co/wPGbjOHtmf VML MILAN | VML'smoothie #4 http://t.co/j559tR66Rs Decathlon Italia wins, again!  #Decathlon #Android #phone #mountainproof http://t.co/CBDS9eYOLE "Better to have a short life, that is full of what you like doing, than a long life spent in a miserable way." -... http://t.co/uEnRhgUgdk Let's make your skin crawl. http://t.co/MNCMFnwqgr “Your time is limited, so don’t waste it living someone else’s life. The only way to do great work is to love... http://t.co/RE8CB4qaiW Winter + holidays = fireplace.  #happyholidays http://t.co/QwAerq5tv8 