A month until my b-day !! Doing my geography homework dont you guys  love high school I know tht im really broken when one direction doesnt even make me feel better Sorry i havent been on high school is tough I hate life why cant it always go up making you happy cause right now im going straight down Hey guys homework sucks thts all i got to say :P @username  omg  your pic is really cool how did you take it? #mtvhottest one direction @username hey guys retweet this cause it counts so vote for our husbands @username  make our boys win vote!! #mtvhottest one direction RT counts Hey good night everyone i g2g so BYEEE One direction is in the same city as me!!!!! IM SOOO HAPPY!!! too bad i wont get to see them :( #imagine you run into one direction while your on a shopping spree and they go buy stuff for you and carry your bags directioners athem : http://t.co/7dpigvwLfA My friend went to the one direction concert and she didn't take me!! @username  Paulina #2 went to with her cousin and she had seats in the middle Every one talking about how awesome the one direction concert was then there's me" I'm just happy the weren't 5,000,000 miles away from me" I LEARNED LEEROYS DANCE!!  its Per-fect!! :P #Awkward when your parents look through your one direction pics Me when my one direction poster falls ontop of me when im sleeping " LOUIS! YOUR BAAAD BOOY!!" Some girls in the locker room today were saying louis not loui then i got mad and yelled " THE S IS SILENT GET IT RIGHT!!" " cause you right here and i shouldve taken the chance but i got so scared and i lost the moment again" - One Direction You know you love somebody when it been over a year an your still not over them #notoveryou I'm sensitive okay so you can offend i'd use a come back then id go away and cry my heart away. when asked to rate 1D write down numbers 1-5 but then put all there names on #1 :P Hey guys i g2g dont know if i'll go on later but if i dont #GoodNight Saw i was following 666 people fraked out and followed 10 more #Christan @username  whoops i freaked out not fraked out #typo @username  what happened did something pop up and dont worry louis your famous (sexy too) one day you'll meet him. @username  Follow me @username  Please please please  Follow me  PLEASE :) :) :) You'd make me the happiest person in the world :) :) :):) :) REMINDER: 17 days till my B-day who wants to get me 1D as my Present :P #imagine one direction came to your house and spent a week with you 222 tweets thats like a perfect number well now its 223 :P One direction always makes me feel better My hearts better as of today @username 3:19 :)  gotta change my bio now VOTE FOR ONE DIRECTION!! Now for both #mtvhottest one direction  and for teen choice awards cmon directoners Leaving soon BYE GUYS!! Who's exited to see one direction @username the #TCA @username sorry i havent sent the response i'll tell you why in the response Took the trash out w/h my cousin she takes empty trash can i tell her to put it back same moment bro turns on lawn mower she runsand screams Louis " i dont think theres anything sexy about the way i look" Me: hahahahhahaha thats a good one louis!! @username @username  hahahaha no you should do it more often :P You should tell Louis to do it  him with dat sexy bum :D PLEASE  FOLLOW ME g2g guys more tweets tommorow i promise :P Hey guys have tooooons of homework tonight this'll be my only tweet sorry BYE Hey guys hows life?  mines well eh :P  JK IM HAAAAAAPPY !!!!!! Not really i more neutral but whateves Who loves 1D i love 1D who saw 1D win i saw 1D at the TCA's!! GOO DIRECTIONERS!! Next stop #mtvhottest one direction C'mon you guys Justin is catching up we gotta win VOTE!! #mtvhottest one direction  1D is waaay hotter then Justin so VOTE!! "happiness often seeps through a door you didn't know was open." Cmon you guys vote for one direction #mtvhottest one direction  and #voteonedirection Hey guys havent gone to the bathroom alllll day gonna go right now!! Sooooo yeah im kinda random :p Just went to the bathroom now making spaghetti #YUM getting off now wont be able to get back on do #goodnight you guys more tweets tomorrow Hey guys today im at home but at school cause were doing a classes online day and i finished all my work early YEAH!! Head phones were invented for only us to here are music but theres still the mouth. My brother tells me to shut up then i go "TO THE BEST.." @username  follow me ? @username @username OMG! I got angie to watch BSE!! she said it was okay!!! were making progress soon shell be a directioner !! hey guys i like food :p @username  hey lou wanted to be the first you saw on this tweet did i make it hope soo. Follow me? @username @username  hey lou hope you read this im what you call a dedicated directioner follow me? @username @username  Lou i really do hope you read this follow me ? Im what you call a dedicated directioner @username  Hope you get this i know how you dont think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me? @username Hope you get this i know how you dont think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me? @username Hope you get this i know how you dont think your sexy  "but your perfect to me" follow me? @username Hope you get this i know how you don't think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me? @username hope you get this i know how you dont think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me? @username Hope you get this i know how you dont think you'r sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me? @username Hope you get this i know  you dont think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me? @username Hope you get this i know  you don't think your sexy "but your perfect to me" follow me? just tweeted a bunch of times to louis in hopes he'll see it and follow me Said his name was louis tomlinson, and his daddy was a pro polo player @username @username  hahaha see thats what #Directioners do we make directionaters watch there videos and then make them fans hey guys sorry i wasnt on yesterday but well this is life #shithappens SOOO HAPPY TODAY MAKIN PROGRESS... with something that you guys dont know about My life has been filled with problems..most which have never occurred- Norman OMG 1D's NEW SONG LEAKED!!! Everyone look up cant let her go !! OMG!! I ATE IT TODAY!! In spainsh girl takes my chair i had no clue try to sit down and ended up falling IT WAS SOO FUNNY #epicfail Yesterday had cross country try-outs today had cross country practice yup i guess that means im a fast runner you guys :P I hate it when people tell blonde jokes in front of me its like really Doing a video spree on 1D #dedicated fan boreeed dont wanna watch little league game wait.. is it over eh idk i dont care just gonna finish this then sleep soooo tired she so mean but i gotta love it and i just cant let her go  - One direction Uggg stupid cross country ran 3 miles once and that was bad now i on sat. i have to run 6.4 miles thanks coach lopez #notethesacrasm hey guys finished my homework im tired sooo good night My birthday is 3 days away!!  soo tommorow imma a wear a big sticker that says its my b-day id let you hug me but.. i dont like hugs @username @username   haha lol and write there name on out hands with hearts for the dots on the i's or is that just me.. RUMOR CONFIRMED : Zayn and Perri are engaged Saw 705 following thought thats how many followers i had Me: oO then i realized thats how many people i was following me: -____- does this make anyone else hungry  cause i want a cookie now http://t.co/lQBnZUy9aE @username  3 days till my birthday and all i want is a follow from you Hey guys wanna know what i want for my b-day http://t.co/Hsdmn6cJRE boooored out of my mind what to do oh yeah listen to one direction :P I dont know if you can tell but ima a dedicated directioner you should see my english notebook "I see it in your eyes your disapointed cause im the foolish that you anointed with your heart i tore it aprat" - One Direction gonna pull a #allnighter who wants to do it with me!!! Who needs sleep when you can watch tv and go on Facebook Growing up sucks miss middle school :( #teardrop oh yeah tv rocks Hey guys still up told ya doin all nighter i think i just fell in love with someone on.. facebook :p 