 eh ehh hh. h.. ... ..  . b  bo boo ook oks ks  s o  on on  n m  my myt yth tho hol olo log ogy gy, y,  , t  th tha hat at  t i  is is. s.  . i  i  i k  kn kno now ow  w i  i  i s  sh sho hou oul uld ld  d h  ha hav ave ve  e a  an ans nsw swe wer ere red ed  d t  to to  o a  a  a l  lo lot ot  t o  of of  f h  he hel ell llo lo  o t  tw twe wee eet ets ts  s t  th tha hat at  t i  in inc ncl clu lud ude ded ed  d m  me me  e a  an and nd  d n  no now ow  w n  no not ot  t a  an any nym ymo mor ore re. e.  . i  i  i w  wa was as  s j  ju jus ust st  t t  to too oo  o b  bu bus usy sy  y o  of off ff  f l  la lat ate te  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #s #so sor orr rry ry  y i  i  i d  do don on' n't 't  t a  ag agr gre ree ee. e.  . i  is is  s n  ni nic ice ce, e,  , b  bu but ut  t (  (s (si six ixx xx) x)  ) i  is is  s c  co coo ool ol! l!! !!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y i  is is  s t  to tom omo mor orr rro row ow  w (  (i (i. i.e .e. e.  . h  he her ere re) e), ),  , d  de dec ec. c.  . 4  4t 4th th  h i  i  i m  ma may ay  y n  no not ot  t a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s a  an ans nsw swe wer er  r (  (l (li lik ike ke  e t  th the he  e m  ma man an  n o  of of  f m  my my  y l  li lif ife fe  e d  do doe oes esn snt nt  t a  al alw lwa way ays ys) s), ),  , b  bu but ut  t (  (l (li lik ike ke  e h  hi him im) m)  ) i  i  i s  se see ee  e i  it it  t a  al all ll! l!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? y  yo you ou  u h  ha hav ave ve  e a  a  a n  ni nic ice ce  e b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  to too oo! o!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : n  ne new ew  w f  fa fav avo vor ori rit ite te  e i  in ins nst sta tag agr gra ram am. m.  . y  yo you ou  u h  ha hav ave ve  e o  on one ne? e?‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i  i w  wi wis ish sh! h!! !!! !!  ! s  so so  o e  et ete ter ern rna nal all lly ly  y i  in in  n ?  ?? ??  ? w  wi wit ith th  h y  yo you ou. u.. ... ... ..  . ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th the her ere re' e's 's  s a  a  a v  ve ver ery ry  y t  th thi hin in  n l  li lin ine ne  e b  be bet etw twe wee een en  n f  fa fas ash shi hio ion on  n a  an and nd  d f  fa fak ake ke. e.  . c  ch che hec eck ck  k m  my my  y i  in ins nst sta tag agr gra ram am: m:  : a  a  a n  ni nic ice ce  e p  pi pic ic  c o  of of  f t  th tha hat at  t i  i  i t  tu tur urn rne ned ed  d i  in int nto to  o a  an an  n o  ol old ld  d s  st sty tyl yle le  e p  ph pho hot oto tog ogr gra rap aph ph. h.  . f  fo for or  r t  th the he  e n  ni nic ice ces est st  t #  #p #ph pho hot oto tog ogr gra rap aph phe her er  r o  ou out ut‚ t‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ g  go goo ood od  d r  re rea ead ad! d!  ! y  yo you our ur  r s  si sil ile len enc nce ce  e t  to tow owa war ard rds ds  s m  me me  e i  is is  s d  de dea eaf afe fen eni nin ing ng. g.. ... ..  . #  #u #ur urs rsi sil ile len ent ntu tus usc scr cre rea eam am  m ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ho hop ope pe  e y  yo you ou  u g  ge get et  t t  th the he  e s  st stu tuf uff ff  f o  on on  n t  ti tim ime me  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù m  ma may ayb ybe be  e t  to tod oda day ay, y,  , m  ma may ayb ybe be  e t  to tom omo mor orr rro row ow. w.. ... ..  . ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #b #bl bli lis iss ss  s i  is is  s t  th the he  e n  ne new ew  w m  ma mag agi gic ic  c w  wo wor ord rd. d.  . b  bl bli lis iss ss  s i  is is  s a  as as  s o  ol old ld  d a  as as  s t  th the he  e w  wo wor orl rld ld. d.  . b  bl bli lis iss ss  s i  is is  s w  wi wit ith thi hin in  n e  ev eve ver ery ryo yon one ne  e o  of of  f u  us us. s.  . l  lo loo ook ok  k f  fo for or  r i  it it. t.  . f  fi fin ind nd  d i  it it! t!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? 1  11 11: 1:1 :11 11  1 a  am am  m r  ri rig igh ght ht  t h  he her ere re  e r  ri rig igh ght ht  t n  no now ow. w.  . m  ma mak ake ke  e a  a  a w  wi wis ish sh! h!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  it it' t's 's  s b  be bea eau aut uty ty. y.  . i  it it' t's 's  s s  st str tre ren eng ngt gth th. h.  . i  it it' t's 's  s w  wi wis isd sdo dom om. m.  . #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : t  th thi his is  s i  is is  s o  on one ne  e o  of of  f t  th the he  e b  be bes est st  t m  m/ m/‚ /‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù w  wh wha hat at  t a  ab abo bou out ut  t m  my my  y l  la lat ate tes est st  t e  ed edi dit it? t?  ? ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? h  ha hap app ppy py  y f  fc fck ckn kn  n b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay, y,  , ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? t  to tom omo mor orr rro row ow  w i  is is  s m  my my  y #  #b #bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y a  an and nd  d j  ju jus ust st  t n  no now ow, w,  , t  th the he  e p  po pos ost st  t d  de del eli liv ive ver ery ry  y m  ma man an  n d  de del eli liv ive ver ere red ed  d a  a  a b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y p  pr pre res ese sen ent nt  t f  fr fro rom om‚ m‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ i  i  i a  am am  m n  no now ow  w f  fo fol oll llo low owi win ing ng  g p  pe peo eop opl ple le, e,  , ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? c  co coo ool ol  l o  on ons nst sta tag age ge  e p  ph pho hot oto to  o o  of of  f y  yo you ou, u,  , a  an and nd  d ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #r #ri rip ipm pmo mot otl tle ley eyc ycr cru rue ue  e c  co cou oul uld ld  d u  u  u c  cr cre rea eat ate te  e s  so son ong ngs gs  s w  wi wit ith th  h t  th thi his is  s s  sp spi pir iri rit itu tua ual al  l t  th the hem eme me? e?  ? #  #e #es esp spe pec eci cia ial all lly lyh yho hop ope pe  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? a  ar are re  e y  yo you ou  u g  ge get ett tti tin ing ng  g i  in ins nsp spi pir ira rat ati tio ion on  n f  fo for or  r n  ne new ew  w m  mu mus usi sic ic  c f  fr fro rom om  m j  jo jos ose sep eph ph  h c  ca cam amp mpb pbe bel ell ll, l,  , n  ni nik ikk kki ki? i?  ? i  it it' t's 's  s s  st sti til ill ll  l e  ea ear arl rly ly  y i  in int nto to  o d  de dec ec. c.  . 4  4, 4,  , b  bu but ut  t t  to tod oda day ay  y i  is is  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y &  &  & i  i' i'm 'm  m s  so so  o h  ha hap app ppy py  y t  to to  o b  be be  e a  al ali liv ive ve! e!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : y  ye yes es‚ s‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù m  my myt yth tho hol olo log ogy gy  y i  is is  s p  pa par art rt  t o  of of  f m  my my  y w  wo wor ork rk. k.  . i  i' i'm 'm  m a  a  a c  cl cla las ass ssi sic ici cis ist st. t.? .?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  to tod oda day ay  y i  is is  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay. y.  . g  ge get ett tti tin ing ng  g a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y f  fr fro rom om  m m  my my  y f  fa fav av  v m  mu mus usi sic ici cia ian an  n &  &  & c  cr cre rea eat ati tiv ive ve  e i  in ins nsp spi pir ira rat ato tor or  r w  wo wou oul uld ld  d b  be be  e s  so so  o n  ni nic ice ce! e!  ! t  ty ty  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou  u ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : "  "h "he hey ey  y r  ro ros ose se, e,  , h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  to to  o y  yo you ou! u!" !"  " ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! x  xo xo  o ?  ?? ??  ? f  fi fig igs gs  s v  vi vis isi sio ion on! n!  ! i  i  i w  wi wis ish sh  h y  yo you ou  u a  a  a g  go goo ood od  d n  ni nig igh ght ht. t.  . t  to tod oda day ay  y f  fo for or  r m  me me, e,  , d  de dec ec. c.  . i  is is  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay. y.  . c  ca can an  n i  i  i g  ge get et  t a  a  a "  "h "ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay" y"  " w  wi wis ish sh  h f  fr fro rom om  m y  yo you ou, u,  , p  pl ple lea eas ase se? e?  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay? y?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  tw twe wee eet et  t f  fr fro rom om  m w  wo wou oul uld ld  d b  be be  e w  wo won ond nde der erf rfu ful ul! l!! !!  ! p  pl ple lea eas ase se  e w  wi wis ish sh  h m  me me  e a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay, y,  , n  ni nik ikk kki ki? i?  ? i  it it' t's 's  s t  to tod oda day ay  y :  :) :)  ) t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou  u f  fo for or  r y  yo you our ur  r b  be bes est st  t w  wi wis ish she hes es, s,  , j  ja jam ami mie ie! e!! !!  ! x  xo xox oxo xo  o ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y r  ro ros ose se‚ e‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! x  xx xx  x ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay‚ y‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! t  to tod oda day ay  y i  is is  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay. y.  . i  i' i'm 'm  m e  en enj njo joy oyi yin ing ng  g i  it it. t.  . i  it it  t w  wo wou oul uld ld  d b  be be  e o  ou out uts tst sta tan and ndi din ing ng  g i  if if  f y  yo you ou  u p  po pos ost ste ted ed  d a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  tw twe wee eet et  t t  to to  o m  me me. e.  . p  pl ple lea eas ase se? e?  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : l  li lif ife fe  e i  is is  s n  no not ot  t a  ab abo bou out ut  t w  wh who ho  o h  hu hur urt rt  t y  yo you ou  u a  an and nd  d b  br bro rok oke ke  e y  yo you ou  u d  do dow own wn. n.  . i  it it' t's 's  s a  ab abo bou out ut  t w  wh who ho  o w  wa was as  s a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s t  th the her ere re  e a  an and nd  d w  wh who ho  o m  ma mad ade de  e y  yo you ou  u s  sm smi mil ile le  e a  ag agi gin in" n"  " f  fu fun unn nny ny. y.  . i  i  i c  ca can an' n't 't  t l  lo loa oad ad  d y  yo you our ur  r p  po pos ost st  t o  on on  n m  my my  y i  in ins nst sta tag agr gra ram am. m.  . i  is is  s m  my my  y i  in ins nst sta tag agr gra ram am  m l  la lag agg ggi gin ing ng? g?  ? h  hm hmm mm, m,  , m  mu mus ust st  t b  be be. e.. ... ..  . #  #w #wt wtf tf  f ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : y  ye yes es  s i  i  i t  th thi hin ink nk  k i  in ins nst stg tgr gra ram am  m i  is is  s l  la lag agg ggi gin ing ng  g .  .. ... ..  . n  ne nee eed eds ds  s t  th the he  e ?  ?? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äùy ùyu yup up  p y  yu yup up! p!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  it it' t's 's  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y a  an and nd  d i  i  i s  sm smi mil ile le  e i  if if  f i  i  i w  wa wan ant nt  t t  to to. o.. ... ... ..  . c  ca can an  n i  i  i h  ha hav ave ve  e a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  b- b-d -da day ay  y f  fr fro rom om  m y  yo you ou? u?  ? #  #p #pl ple lee eez ez  z t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s i  in int nte ter ere res est sti tin ing ng! g!  ! i  id idk dk  k w  wh why hy  y i  i  i l  li lik ike ke  e t  th the he  e t  te ter erm rmi min ina nat ato tor or. r.  . m  ma may ayb ybe be  e b  be bec eca cau aus use se  e o  of of  f t  th the he  e s  sa sal alv lva vat ati tio ion on  n t  th tho hou oug ugh ght ht  t t  th tha hat at' t's 's  s a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s t  th the her ere re  e h  ha hap app ppy py  y h  ho hol oli lid ida day ays ys! s!  ! w  wh why hy  y i  i  i c  ca car are re? e?  ? b  be bec eca cau aus use se  e i  i  i l  lo lov ove ve. e.  . i  i' i'm 'm  m h  ha hav avi vin ing ng  g a  an an  n a  aw awe wes eso som ome me  e b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y a  an and nd  d i  i  i c  ca can an' n't 't  t w  wa wai ait it  t f  fo for or  r t  th the he  e #  #s #si six ixx xxs xse sen ens nse se  e s  sh sho how ow  w t  to tod oda day ay! y!! !!? !?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!  ! j  ja jay ay  y z  z, z,  , t  ty tyr yra ra  a b  ba ban ank nks ks, s,  , a  an and nd  d j  je jef eff ff  f b  br bri rid idg dge ges es  s s  sh sha har are re  e a  a  a b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y w  wi wit ith th  h y  yo you ou! u!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nks ks  s a  ag aga gai ain in, n,  , h  ha hah aha hah aha ha! a!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : .  .  . h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  to to  o y  yo you ou  u g  gi gir irl rl  l :  :- :-) -)‚ )‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y !  !  ! i  i  i h  ho hop ope pe  e i  it it  t w  wa was as  s a  aw awe wes eso som ome me? e?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  it it  t w  wa was as! s!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? m  my my  y b  bd bda day ay  y i  is is  s t  to tod oda day ay, y,  , b  bu but ut  t s  si sin inc nce ce  e t  th thi his is  s m  mo mon ont nth th  h i  is is  s a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s o  on one ne  e b  bi big ig  g p  pa par art rty ty  y a  af aff ffa fai air ir  r w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the he  e h  ho hol oli lid ida day ays ys  s a  an and nd  d m  ma man any ny  y b  bd bda day ays ys, s,  , i  i' i'l 'll ll  l s  st str tre ret etc tch ch  h m  mi min ine ne  e u  un unt nti til il  l d  de dec ec  c 3  31 31. 1.. ..  . l  lo lol ol  l t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou, u,  , d  da daw awn wn! n!! !!  ! i  i  i w  wa wan ant nt  t t  to to  o t  th tha han ank nk  k a  al all ll  l m  my my  y f  fr fri rie ien end nds ds  s o  on onl nli lin ine ne  e &  &  & o  of off ffl fli lin ine ne  e f  fo for or  r a  al all ll  l t  th the hei eir ir  r n  ni nic ice ce  e &  &  & b  be bes est st  t w  wi wis ish she hes es  s f  fo for or  r m  me me  e o  on on  n m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!! !!! !!  ! #  #t #th tha han ank nky kyo you ou  u ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! i  it it' t's 's  s v  ve ver ery ry  y v  ve ver ery ry  y e  ea ear arl rly ly  y i  in int nto to  o d  de dec ec. c.  . a  an and nd  d a  af aft fte ter er  r s  so som ome me  e s  sl sle lee eep ep  p i  i' i'm 'm  m v  ve ver ery ry  y m  mu muc uch ch  h a  aw awa wak ake ke! e!  ! #  #l #lo lol ol  l a  an and nd  d t  th the he  e n  ni nig igh ght ht  t b  be bef efo for ore re  e s  st st. t.  . n  ni nic ich cho hol ola las as' s'  ' b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y p  pe peo eop opl ple le  e g  gi giv ive ve  e e  ea eac ach cho hot oth the her er  r g  gi gif ift fts ts  s i  in in  n n  nl nl. l.  . i  it it' t's 's  s c  ca cal all lle led ed  d s  st st. t.  . n  ni nic ich cho hol ola las as' s'  ' e  ev eve ve  e &  &  & g  gi gif ift fts ts  s e  ev eve ve! e!  ! d  de dec ec. c.  . t  th tha hat at  t i  is is. s.  . e  es esp spe pec eci cia ial all lly ly  y f  fo for or  r k  ki kid ids ds, s,  , t  th thi his is  s i  is is  s o  on one ne  e o  of of  f t  th the he  e y  ye yea ear ar' r's 's  s e  ep epi pic ic  c e  ev eve ven eni nin ing ngs gs! s!  ! a  an and nd  d t  th thi his is  s i  is is  s o  of of  f t  th the he  e r  re rea eas aso son ons ns  s w  wh why hy  y i  i  i l  lo lov ove ve  e h  hi him im: m:  : h  he he' e's 's  s s  so so  o p  pa pas ass ssi sio ion ona nat ate te  e a  ab abo bou out ut  t w  wh wha hat at  t h  he he  e l  lo lov ove ves es  s t  to to  o d  do do! o!  ! ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : l  li lif ife fe' e's 's  s p  pr pro rob obl ble lem ems ms  s w  wo wou oul uld ldn dn' n't 't  t b  be be  e c  ca cal all lle led ed  d "  "h "hu hur urd rdl dle les es" s"  " i  if if  f t  th the her ere re  e w  wa was asn sn' n't 't  t a  a  a w  wa way ay  y t  to to  o g  ge get et  t o  ov ove ver er  r t  th the hem em. m.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!! !!! !!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : w  wh whe hen en  n i  is is  s y  yo you our ur  r b  b  b d  da day ay? y?‚ ?‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù d  de dec ec  c 4  4. 4.  . f  fo for or  r m  me me  e t  th tha hat at' t's 's  s a  al alr lre rea ead ady dy  y y  ye yes est ste ter erd rda day ay  y ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : i  i  i t  th tho hou oug ugh ght ht  t i  it it  t w  wa was as  s m  mi mig igh ght hty ty  y a  at att ttr tra rac act cti tiv ive ve  e l  lo lol ol‚ l‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  it it' t's 's  s a  a  a m  ma mat att tte ter er  r o  of of  f o  op opi pin ini nio ion on. n.. ... ..b .bu but ut  t f  fo for or  r m  me me, e,  , e  eh ehh hhh hh. h.. ... ..n .no no. o.  . #  #l #lo lol ol  l o  of of  f c  co cou our urs rse se  e i  i  i d  do do  o a  an and nd  d i  i  i a  ag agr gre ree ee  e t  to to  o t  th tha hat at! t!  ! h  ha hah aha hah aha ha! a!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  is is  s t  th the her ere re  e s  so som ome met eth thi hin ing ng  g y  yo you ou  u s  st sti til ill ll  l h  ha hav ave ve  e t  to to  o p  ph pho hot oto tog ogr gra rap aph ph? h?  ? #  #a #as ask sks ksi six ixx xx  x i  it it' t's 's  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  to tod oda day ay. y.  . p  pl ple lea eas ase se  e w  wi wis ish sh  h m  me me  e a  a  a h  ha hap app ppy py  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay? y?  ? #  #a #as ask sks ksi six ixx xx  x n  ne nev eve ver er  r d  do do  o s  st ste ter ero roi oid ids ds  s n  ni nik ikk kki ki. i.  . t  th the hey ey  y w  wi wil ill ll  l k  ki kil ill ll  l y  yo you ou. u.  . t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou! u!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou, u,  , r  ro rod odn dne ney ey! y!! !!  ! i  it it  t s  su sur ure re  e w  wo wou oul uld ld  d b  be be! e!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôv ôve ve  e b  be bee een en  n a  aw awa way ay  y f  fo for or  r a  a  a w  wh whi hil ile le. e.  . n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g p  pe per ers rso son ona nal al. l.  . t  to tod oda day ay  y i  is is  s m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y &  &  & a  a  a s  sp spe pec eci cia ial al  l d  da day ay  y #  #n #ni nik ikk kki kit iti tim ime me  e w  w/ w/  / i  i' i'm 'm  m a  a  a w  wo wom oma man an, n,  , r  ro rod odn dne ney ey. y.  . ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? g  go goo ood od  d n  ni nig igh ghf hf  f a  an and nd  d t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou  u f  fo for or  r f  fa fav avi vin ing ng  g o  on one ne  e o  of of  f m  my my  y b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y t  tw twe wee eet ets ts  s ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ho hop ope pe  e y  yo you ou  u h  ha had ad  d a  a  a g  gr gre rea eat at  t b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay! y!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k y  yo you ou, u,  , y  ye yes es  s i  i  i d  di did id! d!! !!! !!  ! i  i' i'm 'm  m g  go gon onn nna na  a g  ge get et  t t  th the he  e n  ne new ew  w a  al alb lbu bum um  m s  so soo oon on! n!  ! a  a  a #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t o  of of  f y  yo you ou  u &  &  & #  #l #le lei eic ica cas asi six ixx xx  x a  an and nd  d a  a  a l  le len ens ns. s.  . i  i  i t  th tho hou oug ugh ght ht  t y  yo you ou' u'd 'd  d l  li lik ike ke  e t  th the he  e c  co com omb mbi bin ina nat ati tio ion on  n ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : h  ha hap app ppi pin ine nes ess ss  s d  do doe oes esn sn' n't 't  t r  re res esu sul ult lt  t f  fr fro rom om  m w  wh wha hat at  t w  we we  e g  ge get et, t,  , b  bu but ut  t f  fr fro rom om  m w  wh wha hat at  t w  we we  e g  gi giv ive ve. e.‚ .‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù i  i' i'm 'm  m n  no not ot  t #  #f #ff ff  f -  -i -in ing ng  g t  to tod oda day ay, y,  , '  'c 'ca cau aus use se  e i  i  i g  go got ot  t a  a  a l  lo lot ot  t t  to to  o d  do do, o,  , b  bu but ut  t t  th the her ere re' e's 's  s o  of of  f c  co cou our urs rse se  e o  on one ne  e g  gu guy uy  y t  th tha hat at  t a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s g  ge get ets ts  s a  a  a #  #s #sh sho hou out uto tou out ut  t :  :  : .  .. ... ... ... ... ..? .?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? a  a  a b  bi big ig  g m  me meg ega ga  a #  #s #sh sho hou out uto tou out ut  t f  fo for or  r t  th the he  e o  on one ne  e a  an and nd  d o  on onl nly ly  y !  !! !!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? n  no no  o #  #m #mo mod ode der ern rnv nvi vin int nta tag age ge  e a  ar are re  e t  th the hey ey  y c  cr cra raz azy zy? y?? ??? ??? ??  ? a  aw awe wes eso som ome me! e!  ! r  re rea eal al  l g  gu gui uit ita tar ar  r s  st stu tuf uff ff! f!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äú: ú:  : t  th thi his is  s i  is is  s a  a  a w  wo won ond nde der erf rfu ful ul  l p  pi pic ic! c!! !!! !!! !!‚ !‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù t  th tha han ank nk  k u  u  u h  ha hah aha hah aha ha! a!  ! w  wh whe hen en  n c  co com ome mes es  s i  in in  n a  an and nd  d e  en ent nte ter ers rs  s t  th the he  e p  pa par art rty ty! y!  ! #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? g  go got ot  t i  it it! t!  ! #  #i #it itu tun une nes es  s #  #c #cd cd  d #  #7 #7" 7"s "si sin ing ngl gle le  e j  ju jus ust st  t n  no not ot  t y  ye yet et: t:  : t  th the he  e #  #v #vi vin iny nyl yla lal alb lbu bum um  m ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? i  in in  n m  my my  y #  #w #wi wis ish shl hli lis ist st  t f  fo for or  r #  #s #si six ixx xxm xma mas as  s !  !! !!! !!  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ??  ? b  be bet etw twe wee een en  n y  yo you our ur  r b  bi bir irt rth thd hda day ay  y a  an and nd  d x  xm xma mas as! s!  ! o  on on  n m  my my  y #  #w #wi wis ish shl hli lis ist st  t !  !  ! ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? n  ni nik ikk kki ki, i,  , c  ca can an  n w  we we  e p  pr pre re- e-o -or ord rde der er  r t  th the he  e #  #v #vi vin iny nyl yl  l #  #m #mo mod ode der ern rnv nvi vin int nta tag age ge  e ?  ?? ??  ? w  wh whe hen en  n w  wa wal alk lks ks  s i  in int nto to  o a  a  a r  ro roo oom om. m.. ... ..  . #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? s  se sen end nd  d m  me me  e t  th the he  e p  pi pic ic  c y  yo you ou  u w  wa wan ant nt  t e  ed edi dit ite ted ed  d a  an and nd  d i  i' i'l 'll ll  l m  ma mak ake ke  e i  it it  t f  fo for or  r y  yo you ou  u c  ca can an  n w  we we  e p  pr pre re- e-o -or ord rde der er  r t  th the he  e #  #v #vi vin iny nyl yl  l v  ve ver ers rsi sio ion on  n o  of of  f #  #m #mo mod ode der ern rnv nvi vin int nta tag age ge  e ?  ?  ? w  wi wil ill ll  l i  it it  t b  be be  e a  av ava vai ail ila lab abl ble le  e o  on on  n y  yo you ou' u'r 're re  e w  we wel elc lco com ome me  e ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? #  #t #ta tag aga gar art rt  t #  #p #ph pho hot oto toe oed edi dit it  t b  by by  y ?  ?? ??? ??? ??  ? y  yo you ou' u'r 're re  e w  we wel elc lco com ome me! e!  !     ehh ehh. hh.. h... ...  .. b . bo  boo book ooks oks  ks o s on  on  on m n my  myt myth ytho thol holo olog logy ogy, gy,  y, t , th  tha that hat  at i t is  is. is.  s. i . i   i k i kn  kno know now  ow i w i   i s i sh  sho shou houl ould uld  ld h d ha  hav have ave  ve a e an  ans answ nswe swer were ered red  ed t d to  to  to a o a   a l a lo  lot lot  ot o t of  of  of h f he  hel hell ello llo  lo t o tw  twe twee weet eets ets  ts t s th  tha that hat  at i t in  inc incl nclu clud lude uded ded  ed m d me  me  me a e an  and and  nd n d no  now now  ow n w no  not not  ot a t an  any anym nymo ymor more ore. re.  e. i . i   i w i wa  was was  as j s ju  jus just ust  st t t to  too too  oo b o bu  bus busy usy  sy o y of  off off  ff l f la  lat late ate  te ? e ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? # ? #s  #so #sor sorr orry rry  ry i y i   i d i do  don don' on't n't  't a t ag  agr agre gree ree. ee.  e. i . is  is  is n s ni  nic nice ice, ce,  e, b , bu  but but  ut ( t (s  (si (six sixx ixx) xx)  x) i ) is  is  is c s co  coo cool ool! ol!! l!!! !!!  !! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? m ? my  my  my b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay i y is  is  is t s to  tom tomo omor morr orro rrow row  ow ( w (i  (i. (i.e i.e. .e.  e. h . he  her here ere) re), e),  ), d , de  dec dec. ec.  c. 4 . 4t  4th 4th  th i h i   i m i ma  may may  ay n y no  not not  ot a t al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys a s an  ans answ nswe swer wer  er ( r (l  (li (lik like ike  ke t e th  the the  he m e ma  man man  an o n of  of  of m f my  my  my l y li  lif life ife  fe d e do  doe does oesn esnt snt  nt a t al  alw alwa lway ways ays) ys), s),  ), b , bu  but but  ut ( t (l  (li (lik like ike  ke h e hi  him him) im)  m) i ) i   i s i se  see see  ee i e it  it  it a t al  all all! ll!  l! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? y ? yo  you you  ou h u ha  hav have ave  ve a e a   a n a ni  nic nice ice  ce b e bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay t y to  too too! oo!  o! ‚ ! ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: n : ne  new new  ew f w fa  fav favo avor vori orit rite ite  te i e in  ins inst nsta stag tagr agra gram ram. am.  m. y . yo  you you  ou h u ha  hav have ave  ve o e on  one one? ne?‚ e?‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i   i w i wi  wis wish ish! sh!! h!!! !!!  !! s ! so  so  so e o et  ete eter tern erna rnal nall ally lly  ly i y in  in  in ? n ??  ??  ?? w ? wi  wit with ith  th y h yo  you you. ou.. u... .... ...  .. ? . ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? t ? th  the ther here ere' re's e's  's a s a   a v a ve  ver very ery  ry t y th  thi thin hin  in l n li  lin line ine  ne b e be  bet betw etwe twee ween een  en f n fa  fas fash ashi shio hion ion  on a n an  and and  nd f d fa  fak fake ake. ke.  e. c . ch  che chec heck eck  ck m k my  my  my i y in  ins inst nsta stag tagr agra gram ram: am:  m: a : a   a n a ni  nic nice ice  ce p e pi  pic pic  ic o c of  of  of t f th  tha that hat  at i t i   i t i tu  tur turn urne rned ned  ed i d in  int into nto  to a o an  an  an o n ol  old old  ld s d st  sty styl tyle yle  le p e ph  pho phot hoto otog togr ogra grap raph aph. ph.  h. f . fo  for for  or t r th  the the  he n e ni  nic nice ices cest est  st # t #p  #ph #pho phot hoto otog togr ogra grap raph aphe pher her  er o r ou  out out‚ ut‚Ä t‚Ä¶ ‚Ä¶  Ä¶ g ¶ go  goo good ood  od r d re  rea read ead! ad!  d! y ! yo  you your our  ur s r si  sil sile ilen lenc ence nce  ce t e to  tow towa owar ward ards rds  ds m s me  me  me i e is  is  is d s de  dea deaf eafe afen feni enin ning ing. ng.. g... ...  .. # . #u  #ur #urs ursi rsil sile ilen lent entu ntus tusc uscr scre crea ream eam  am ‚ m ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ho  hop hope ope  pe y e yo  you you  ou g u ge  get get  et t t th  the the  he s e st  stu stuf tuff uff  ff o f on  on  on t n ti  tim time ime  me ? e ??  ??? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù m ù ma  may mayb aybe ybe  be t e to  tod toda oday day, ay,  y, m , ma  may mayb aybe ybe  be t e to  tom tomo omor morr orro rrow row. ow.. w... ...  .. ? . ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? # ? #b  #bl #bli blis liss iss  ss i s is  is  is t s th  the the  he n e ne  new new  ew m w ma  mag magi agic gic  ic w c wo  wor word ord. rd.  d. b . bl  bli blis liss iss  ss i s is  is  is a s as  as  as o s ol  old old  ld a d as  as  as t s th  the the  he w e wo  wor worl orld rld. ld.  d. b . bl  bli blis liss iss  ss i s is  is  is w s wi  wit with ithi thin hin  in e n ev  eve ever very eryo ryon yone one  ne o e of  of  of u f us  us. us.  s. l . lo  loo look ook  ok f k fo  for for  or i r it  it. it.  t. f . fi  fin find ind  nd i d it  it! it!  t! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? 1 ? 11  11: 11:1 1:11 :11  11 a 1 am  am  am r m ri  rig righ ight ght  ht h t he  her here ere  re r e ri  rig righ ight ght  ht n t no  now now. ow.  w. m . ma  mak make ake  ke a e a   a w a wi  wis wish ish! sh!  h! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? i ? it  it' it's t's  's b s be  bea beau eaut auty uty. ty.  y. i . it  it' it's t's  's s s st  str stre tren reng engt ngth gth. th.  h. i . it  it' it's t's  's w s wi  wis wisd isdo sdom dom. om.  m. # . #p  #ph #pho phot hoto otoe toed oedi edit dit  it b t by  by  by ? y ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: t : th  thi this his  is i s is  is  is o s on  one one  ne o e of  of  of t f th  the the  he b e be  bes best est  st m t m/  m/‚ m/‚Ä /‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù w ù wh  wha what hat  at a t ab  abo abou bout out  ut m t my  my  my l y la  lat late ates test est  st e t ed  edi edit dit? it?  t? ? ? ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? h ? ha  hap happ appy ppy  py f y fc  fck fckn ckn  kn b n bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day, ay,  y, ? , ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? t ? to  tom tomo omor morr orro rrow row  ow i w is  is  is m s my  my  my # y #b  #bi #bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay a y an  and and  nd j d ju  jus just ust  st n t no  now now, ow,  w, t , th  the the  he p e po  pos post ost  st d t de  del deli eliv live iver very ery  ry m y ma  man man  an d n de  del deli eliv live iver vere ered red  ed a d a   a b a bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay p y pr  pre pres rese esen sent ent  nt f t fr  fro from rom‚ om‚Ä m‚Ä¶ ‚Ä¶  Ä¶ i ¶ i   i a i am  am  am n m no  now now  ow f w fo  fol foll ollo llow lowi owin wing ing  ng p g pe  peo peop eopl ople ple, le,  e, ? , ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? c ? co  coo cool ool  ol o l on  ons onst nsta stag tage age  ge p e ph  pho phot hoto oto  to o o of  of  of y f yo  you you, ou,  u, a , an  and and  nd ? d ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? # ? #r  #ri #rip ripm ipmo pmot motl otle tley leyc eycr ycru crue rue  ue c e co  cou coul ould uld  ld u d u   u c u cr  cre crea reat eate ate  te s e so  son song ongs ngs  gs w s wi  wit with ith  th t h th  thi this his  is s s sp  spi spir piri irit ritu itua tual ual  al t l th  the them heme eme? me?  e? # ? #e  #es #esp espe spec peci ecia cial iall ally llyh lyho yhop hope ope  pe ? e ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? t ? th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!  u! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? a ? ar  are are  re y e yo  you you  ou g u ge  get gett etti ttin ting ing  ng i g in  ins insp nspi spir pira irat rati atio tion ion  on f n fo  for for  or n r ne  new new  ew m w mu  mus musi usic sic  ic f c fr  fro from rom  om j m jo  jos jose osep seph eph  ph c h ca  cam camp ampb mpbe pbel bell ell, ll,  l, n , ni  nik nikk ikki kki? ki?  i? i ? it  it' it's t's  's s s st  sti stil till ill  ll e l ea  ear earl arly rly  ly i y in  int into nto  to d o de  dec dec. ec.  c. 4 . 4,  4,  4, b , bu  but but  ut t t to  tod toda oday day  ay i y is  is  is m s my  my  my b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay & y &   & i & i'  i'm i'm  'm s m so  so  so h o ha  hap happ appy ppy  py t y to  to  to b o be  be  be a e al  ali aliv live ive! ve!  e! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day! ay!‚ y!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!  u! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: y : ye  yes yes‚ es‚Ä s‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù m ù my  myt myth ytho thol holo olog logy ogy  gy i y is  is  is p s pa  par part art  rt o t of  of  of m f my  my  my w y wo  wor work ork. rk.  k. i . i'  i'm i'm  'm a m a   a c a cl  cla clas lass assi ssic sici icis cist ist. st.? t.?? .??? ???? ???  ?? t ? to  tod toda oday day  ay i y is  is  is m s my  my  my b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day. ay.  y. g . ge  get gett etti ttin ting ing  ng a g a   a h a ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay f y fr  fro from rom  om m m my  my  my f y fa  fav fav  av m v mu  mus musi usic sici icia cian ian  an & n &   & c & cr  cre crea reat eati ativ tive ive  ve i e in  ins insp nspi spir pira irat rato ator tor  or w r wo  wou woul ould uld  ld b d be  be  be s e so  so  so n o ni  nic nice ice! ce!  e! t ! ty  ty  ty ? y ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day! ay!‚ y!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you  ou ‚ u ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day! ay!  y! ‚ ! ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!! u!!  !! ‚ ! ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: " : "h  "he "hey hey  ey r y ro  ros rose ose, se,  e, h , ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay t y to  to  to y o yo  you you! ou!" u!"  !" ‚ " ‚Ä  ‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!  u! x ! xo  xo  xo ? o ??  ??  ?? f ? fi  fig figs igs  gs v s vi  vis visi isio sion ion! on!  n! i ! i   i w i wi  wis wish ish  sh y h yo  you you  ou a u a   a g a go  goo good ood  od n d ni  nig nigh ight ght. ht.  t. t . to  tod toda oday day  ay f y fo  for for  or m r me  me, me,  e, d , de  dec dec. ec.  c. i . is  is  is m s my  my  my b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day. ay.  y. c . ca  can can  an i n i   i g i ge  get get  et a t a   a " a "h  "ha "hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day" ay"  y" w " wi  wis wish ish  sh f h fr  fro from rom  om y m yo  you you, ou,  u, p , pl  ple plea leas ease ase? se?  e? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day! ay!‚ y!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!  u! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? t ? th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!! u!!  !! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day? ay?? y??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!  u! t ! th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!! u!!  !! a ! a   a h a ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay t y tw  twe twee weet eet  et f t fr  fro from rom  om w m wo  wou woul ould uld  ld b d be  be  be w e wo  won wond onde nder derf erfu rful ful! ul!! l!!  !! p ! pl  ple plea leas ease ase  se w e wi  wis wish ish  sh m h me  me  me a e a   a h a ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day, ay,  y, n , ni  nik nikk ikki kki? ki?  i? i ? it  it' it's t's  's t s to  tod toda oday day  ay : y :)  :)  :) t ) th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!! u!!  !! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? t ? th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you  ou f u fo  for for  or y r yo  you your our  ur b r be  bes best est  st w t wi  wis wish ishe shes hes, es,  s, j , ja  jam jami amie mie! ie!! e!!  !! x ! xo  xox xoxo oxo  xo ‚ o ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay r y ro  ros rose ose‚ se‚Ä e‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!  u! x ! xx  xx  xx ‚ x ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day‚ ay‚Ä y‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!! u!!  !! t ! to  tod toda oday day  ay i y is  is  is m s my  my  my b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day. ay.  y. i . i'  i'm i'm  'm e m en  enj enjo njoy joyi oyin ying ing  ng i g it  it. it.  t. i . it  it  it w t wo  wou woul ould uld  ld b d be  be  be o e ou  out outs utst tsta stan tand andi ndin ding ing  ng i g if  if  if y f yo  you you  ou p u po  pos post oste sted ted  ed a d a   a h a ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay t y tw  twe twee weet eet  et t t to  to  to m o me  me. me.  e. p . pl  ple plea leas ease ase? se?  e? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: l : li  lif life ife  fe i e is  is  is n s no  not not  ot a t ab  abo abou bout out  ut w t wh  who who  ho h o hu  hur hurt urt  rt y t yo  you you  ou a u an  and and  nd b d br  bro brok roke oke  ke y e yo  you you  ou d u do  dow down own. wn.  n. i . it  it' it's t's  's a s ab  abo abou bout out  ut w t wh  who who  ho w o wa  was was  as a s al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys t s th  the ther here ere  re a e an  and and  nd w d wh  who who  ho m o ma  mad made ade  de y e yo  you you  ou s u sm  smi smil mile ile  le a e ag  agi agin gin" in"  n" f " fu  fun funn unny nny. ny.  y. i . i   i c i ca  can can' an't n't  't l t lo  loa load oad  ad y d yo  you your our  ur p r po  pos post ost  st o t on  on  on m n my  my  my i y in  ins inst nsta stag tagr agra gram ram. am.  m. i . is  is  is m s my  my  my i y in  ins inst nsta stag tagr agra gram ram  am l m la  lag lagg aggi ggin ging ing? ng?  g? h ? hm  hmm hmm, mm,  m, m , mu  mus must ust  st b t be  be. be.. e... ...  .. # . #w  #wt #wtf wtf  tf ? f ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: y : ye  yes yes  es i s i   i t i th  thi thin hink ink  nk i k in  ins inst nstg stgr tgra gram ram  am i m is  is  is l s la  lag lagg aggi ggin ging ing  ng . g ..  ... ...  .. n . ne  nee need eeds eds  ds t s th  the the  he ? e ??  ??‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äùy Äùyu ùyup yup  up y p yu  yup yup! up!! p!!  !! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? i ? it  it' it's t's  's m s my  my  my b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay a y an  and and  nd i d i   i s i sm  smi smil mile ile  le i e if  if  if i f i   i w i wa  wan want ant  nt t t to  to. to.. o... .... ...  .. c . ca  can can  an i n i   i h i ha  hav have ave  ve a e a   a h a ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y b-  b-d b-da -day day  ay f y fr  fro from rom  om y m yo  you you? ou?  u? # ? #p  #pl #ple plee leez eez  ez t z th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!! u!!  !! a ! al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys i s in  int inte nter tere eres rest esti stin ting ing! ng!  g! i ! id  idk idk  dk w k wh  why why  hy i y i   i l i li  lik like ike  ke t e th  the the  he t e te  ter term ermi rmin mina inat nato ator tor. or.  r. m . ma  may mayb aybe ybe  be b e be  bec beca ecau caus ause use  se o e of  of  of t f th  the the  he s e sa  sal salv alva lvat vati atio tion ion  on t n th  tho thou houg ough ught ght  ht t t th  tha that hat' at's t's  's a s al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys t s th  the ther here ere  re h e ha  hap happ appy ppy  py h y ho  hol holi olid lida iday days ays! ys!  s! w ! wh  why why  hy i y i   i c i ca  car care are? re?  e? b ? be  bec beca ecau caus ause use  se i e i   i l i lo  lov love ove. ve.  e. i . i'  i'm i'm  'm h m ha  hav havi avin ving ing  ng a g an  an  an a n aw  awe awes weso esom some ome  me b e bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay a y an  and and  nd i d i   i c i ca  can can' an't n't  't w t wa  wai wait ait  it f t fo  for for  or t r th  the the  he # e #s  #si #six sixx ixxs xxse xsen sens ense nse  se s e sh  sho show how  ow t w to  tod toda oday day! ay!! y!!? !!?? !??? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day! ay!  y! j ! ja  jay jay  ay z y z,  z,  z, t , ty  tyr tyra yra  ra b a ba  ban bank anks nks, ks,  s, a , an  and and  nd j d je  jef jeff eff  ff b f br  bri brid ridg idge dges ges  es s s sh  sha shar hare are  re a e a   a b a bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay w y wi  wit with ith  th y h yo  you you! ou!‚ u!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank anks nks  ks a s ag  aga agai gain ain, in,  n, h , ha  hah haha ahah haha aha! ha!  a! ‚ ! ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: . : .   . h . ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay t y to  to  to y o yo  you you  ou g u gi  gir girl irl  rl : l :-  :-) :-)‚ -)‚Ä )‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!  u! ‚ ! ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay ! y !   ! i ! i   i h i ho  hop hope ope  pe i e it  it  it w t wa  was was  as a s aw  awe awes weso esom some ome? me?? e??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???‚ ??‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù it  it  it w t wa  was was! as!  s! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? m ? my  my  my b y bd  bda bday day  ay i y is  is  is t s to  tod toda oday day, ay,  y, b , bu  but but  ut s t si  sin sinc ince nce  ce t e th  thi this his  is m s mo  mon mont onth nth  th i h is  is  is a s al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys o s on  one one  ne b e bi  big big  ig p g pa  par part arty rty  ty a y af  aff affa ffai fair air  ir w r wi  wit with ith  th t h th  the the  he h e ho  hol holi olid lida iday days ays  ys a s an  and and  nd m d ma  man many any  ny b y bd  bda bday days ays, ys,  s, i , i'  i'l i'll 'll  ll s l st  str stre tret retc etch tch  ch m h mi  min mine ine  ne u e un  unt unti ntil til  il d l de  dec dec  ec 3 c 31  31. 31.. 1..  .. l . lo  lol lol  ol t l th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you, ou,  u, d , da  daw dawn awn! wn!! n!!  !! i ! i   i w i wa  wan want ant  nt t t to  to  to t o th  tha than hank ank  nk a k al  all all  ll m l my  my  my f y fr  fri frie rien iend ends nds  ds o s on  onl onli nlin line ine  ne & e &   & o & of  off offl ffli flin line ine  ne f e fo  for for  or a r al  all all  ll t l th  the thei heir eir  ir n r ni  nic nice ice  ce & e &   & b & be  bes best est  st w t wi  wis wish ishe shes hes  es f s fo  for for  or m r me  me  me o e on  on  on m n my  my  my b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day! ay!! y!!! !!!  !! # ! #t  #th #tha than hank anky nkyo kyou you  ou ? u ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? t ? th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!  u! i ! it  it' it's t's  's v s ve  ver very ery  ry v y ve  ver very ery  ry e y ea  ear earl arly rly  ly i y in  int into nto  to d o de  dec dec. ec.  c. a . an  and and  nd a d af  aft afte fter ter  er s r so  som some ome  me s e sl  sle slee leep eep  ep i p i'  i'm i'm  'm v m ve  ver very ery  ry m y mu  muc much uch  ch a h aw  awa awak wake ake! ke!  e! # ! #l  #lo #lol lol  ol a l an  and and  nd t d th  the the  he n e ni  nig nigh ight ght  ht b t be  bef befo efor fore ore  re s e st  st. st.  t. n . ni  nic nich icho chol hola olas las' as'  s' b ' bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay p y pe  peo peop eopl ople ple  le g e gi  giv give ive  ve e e ea  eac each acho chot hoth othe ther her  er g r gi  gif gift ifts fts  ts i s in  in  in n n nl  nl. nl.  l. i . it  it' it's t's  's c s ca  cal call alle lled led  ed s d st  st. st.  t. n . ni  nic nich icho chol hola olas las' as'  s' e ' ev  eve eve  ve & e &   & g & gi  gif gift ifts fts  ts e s ev  eve eve! ve!  e! d ! de  dec dec. ec.  c. t . th  tha that hat  at i t is  is. is.  s. e . es  esp espe spec peci ecia cial iall ally lly  ly f y fo  for for  or k r ki  kid kids ids, ds,  s, t , th  thi this his  is i s is  is  is o s on  one one  ne o e of  of  of t f th  the the  he y e ye  yea year ear' ar's r's  's e s ep  epi epic pic  ic e c ev  eve even veni enin ning ings ngs! gs!  s! a ! an  and and  nd t d th  thi this his  is i s is  is  is o s of  of  of t f th  the the  he r e re  rea reas easo ason sons ons  ns w s wh  why why  hy i y i   i l i lo  lov love ove  ve h e hi  him him: im:  m: h : he  he' he's e's  's s s so  so  so p o pa  pas pass assi ssio sion iona onat nate ate  te a e ab  abo abou bout out  ut w t wh  wha what hat  at h t he  he  he l e lo  lov love oves ves  es t s to  to  to d o do  do! do!  o! ‚ ! ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: l : li  lif life ife' fe's e's  's p s pr  pro prob robl oble blem lems ems  ms w s wo  wou woul ould uldn ldn' dn't n't  't b t be  be  be c e ca  cal call alle lled led  ed " d "h  "hu "hur hurd urdl rdle dles les" es"  s" i " if  if  if t f th  the ther here ere  re w e wa  was wasn asn' sn't n't  't a t a   a w a wa  way way  ay t y to  to  to g o ge  get get  et o t ov  ove over ver  er t r th  the them hem. em.‚ m.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù ? ù ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? # ? #p  #ph #pho phot hoto otoe toed oedi edit dit  it b t by  by  by ? y ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day! ay!! y!!! !!!‚ !!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!! u!!  !! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: w : wh  whe when hen  en i n is  is  is y s yo  you your our  ur b r b   b d b da  day day? ay?‚ y?‚Ä ?‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù d ù de  dec dec  ec 4 c 4.  4.  4. f . fo  for for  or m r me  me  me t e th  tha that hat' at's t's  's a s al  alr alre lrea read eady ady  dy y y ye  yes yest este ster terd erda rday day  ay ‚ y ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: i : i   i t i th  tho thou houg ough ught ght  ht i t it  it  it w t wa  was was  as m s mi  mig migh ight ghty hty  ty a y at  att attr ttra trac ract acti ctiv tive ive  ve l e lo  lol lol‚ ol‚Ä l‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù it  it' it's t's  's a s a   a m a ma  mat matt atte tter ter  er o r of  of  of o f op  opi opin pini inio nion ion. on.. n... ...b ..bu .but but  ut f t fo  for for  or m r me  me, me,  e, e , eh  ehh ehhh hhh. hh.. h... ...n ..no .no. no.  o. # . #l  #lo #lol lol  ol o l of  of  of c f co  cou cour ours urse rse  se i e i   i d i do  do  do a o an  and and  nd i d i   i a i ag  agr agre gree ree  ee t e to  to  to t o th  tha that hat! at!  t! h ! ha  hah haha ahah haha aha! ha!  a! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? i ? is  is  is t s th  the ther here ere  re s e so  som some omet meth ethi thin hing ing  ng y g yo  you you  ou s u st  sti stil till ill  ll h l ha  hav have ave  ve t e to  to  to p o ph  pho phot hoto otog togr ogra grap raph aph? ph?  h? # ? #a  #as #ask asks sksi ksix sixx ixx  xx i x it  it' it's t's  's m s my  my  my b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay t y to  tod toda oday day. ay.  y. p . pl  ple plea leas ease ase  se w e wi  wis wish ish  sh m h me  me  me a e a   a h a ha  hap happ appy ppy  py b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day? ay?  y? # ? #a  #as #ask asks sksi ksix sixx ixx  xx n x ne  nev neve ever ver  er d r do  do  do s o st  ste ster tero eroi roid oids ids  ds n s ni  nik nikk ikki kki. ki.  i. t . th  the they hey  ey w y wi  wil will ill  ll k l ki  kil kill ill  ll y l yo  you you. ou.  u. t . th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you! ou!  u! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? t ? th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you, ou,  u, r , ro  rod rodn odne dney ney! ey!! y!!  !! i ! it  it  it s t su  sur sure ure  re w e wo  wou woul ould uld  ld b d be  be! be!  e! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? i ? i‚  i‚Ä i‚Äô ‚Äôv Äôve ôve  ve b e be  bee been een  en a n aw  awa away way  ay f y fo  for for  or a r a   a w a wh  whi whil hile ile. le.  e. n . no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng p g pe  per pers erso rson sona onal nal. al.  l. t . to  tod toda oday day  ay i y is  is  is m s my  my  my b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay & y &   & a & a   a s a sp  spe spec peci ecia cial ial  al d l da  day day  ay # y #n  #ni #nik nikk ikki kkit kiti itim time ime  me w e w/  w/  w/ i / i'  i'm i'm  'm a m a   a w a wo  wom woma oman man, an,  n, r , ro  rod rodn odne dney ney. ey.  y. ? . ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? g ? go  goo good ood  od n d ni  nig nigh ighf ghf  hf a f an  and and  nd t d th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you  ou f u fo  for for  or f r fa  fav favi avin ving ing  ng o g on  one one  ne o e of  of  of m f my  my  my b y bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay t y tw  twe twee weet eets ets  ts ? s ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ho  hop hope ope  pe y e yo  you you  ou h u ha  had had  ad a d a   a g a gr  gre grea reat eat  at b t bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day! ay!‚ y!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk y k yo  you you, ou,  u, y , ye  yes yes  es i s i   i d i di  did did! id!! d!!! !!!  !! i ! i'  i'm i'm  'm g m go  gon gonn onna nna  na g a ge  get get  et t t th  the the  he n e ne  new new  ew a w al  alb albu lbum bum  um s m so  soo soon oon! on!  n! a ! a   a # a #p  #ph #pho phot hoto otoe toed oedi edit dit  it o t of  of  of y f yo  you you  ou & u &   & # & #l  #le #lei leic eica icas casi asix sixx ixx  xx a x an  and and  nd a d a   a l a le  len lens ens. ns.  s. i . i   i t i th  tho thou houg ough ught ght  ht y t yo  you you' ou'd u'd  'd l d li  lik like ike  ke t e th  the the  he c e co  com comb ombi mbin bina inat nati atio tion ion  on ? n ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: h : ha  hap happ appi ppin pine ines ness ess  ss d s do  doe does oesn esn' sn't n't  't r t re  res resu esul sult ult  lt f t fr  fro from rom  om w m wh  wha what hat  at w t we  we  we g e ge  get get, et,  t, b , bu  but but  ut f t fr  fro from rom  om w m wh  wha what hat  at w t we  we  we g e gi  giv give ive. ve.‚ e.‚Ä .‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù i ù i'  i'm i'm  'm n m no  not not  ot # t #f  #ff #ff  ff - f -i  -in -ing ing  ng t g to  tod toda oday day, ay,  y, ' , 'c  'ca 'cau caus ause use  se i e i   i g i go  got got  ot a t a   a l a lo  lot lot  ot t t to  to  to d o do  do, do,  o, b , bu  but but  ut t t th  the ther here ere' re's e's  's o s of  of  of c f co  cou cour ours urse rse  se o e on  one one  ne g e gu  guy guy  uy t y th  tha that hat  at a t al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys g s ge  get gets ets  ts a s a   a # a #s  #sh #sho shou hout outo utou tout out  ut : t :   : . : ..  ... .... .... .... ...? ..?? .??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? a ? a   a b a bi  big big  ig m g me  meg mega ega  ga # a #s  #sh #sho shou hout outo utou tout out  ut f t fo  for for  or t r th  the the  he o e on  one one  ne a e an  and and  nd o d on  onl only nly  ly ! y !!  !!! !!!  !! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? # ? #p  #ph #pho phot hoto otoe toed oedi edit dit  it b t by  by  by ? y ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? # ? #p  #ph #pho phot hoto otoe toed oedi edit dit  it b t by  by  by ? y ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? n ? no  no  no # o #m  #mo #mod mode oder dern ernv rnvi nvin vint inta ntag tage age  ge a e ar  are are  re t e th  the they hey  ey c y cr  cra craz razy azy? zy?? y??? ???? ???  ?? a ? aw  awe awes weso esom some ome! me!  e! r ! re  rea real eal  al g l gu  gui guit uita itar tar  ar s r st  stu stuf tuff uff! ff!! f!!  !! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? ‚ ? ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äú: Äú:  ú: t : th  thi this his  is i s is  is  is a s a   a w a wo  won wond onde nder derf erfu rful ful  ul p l pi  pic pic! ic!! c!!! !!!! !!!‚ !!‚Ä !‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù t ù th  tha than hank ank  nk u k u   u h u ha  hah haha ahah haha aha! ha!  a! w ! wh  whe when hen  en c n co  com come omes mes  es i s in  in  in a n an  and and  nd e d en  ent ente nter ters ers  rs t s th  the the  he p e pa  par part arty rty! ty!  y! # ! #p  #ph #pho phot hoto otoe toed oedi edit dit  it b t by  by  by ? y ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? g ? go  got got  ot i t it  it! it!  t! # ! #i  #it #itu itun tune unes nes  es # s #c  #cd #cd  cd # d #7  #7" #7"s 7"si "sin sing ingl ngle gle  le j e ju  jus just ust  st n t no  not not  ot y t ye  yet yet: et:  t: t : th  the the  he # e #v  #vi #vin viny inyl nyla ylal lalb albu lbum bum  um ? m ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? i ? in  in  in m n my  my  my # y #w  #wi #wis wish ishl shli hlis list ist  st f t fo  for for  or # r #s  #si #six sixx ixxm xxma xmas mas  as ! s !!  !!! !!!  !! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???? ???  ?? b ? be  bet betw etwe twee ween een  en y n yo  you your our  ur b r bi  bir birt irth rthd thda hday day  ay a y an  and and  nd x d xm  xma xmas mas! as!  s! o ! on  on  on m n my  my  my # y #w  #wi #wis wish ishl shli hlis list ist  st ! t !   ! ? ! ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? n ? ni  nik nikk ikki kki, ki,  i, c , ca  can can  an w n we  we  we p e pr  pre pre- re-o e-or -ord orde rder der  er t r th  the the  he # e #v  #vi #vin viny inyl nyl  yl # l #m  #mo #mod mode oder dern ernv rnvi nvin vint inta ntag tage age  ge ? e ??  ??  ?? w ? wh  whe when hen  en w n wa  wal walk alks lks  ks i s in  int into nto  to a o a   a r a ro  roo room oom. om.. m... ...  .. # . #p  #ph #pho phot hoto otoe toed oedi edit dit  it b t by  by  by ? y ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? s ? se  sen send end  nd m d me  me  me t e th  the the  he p e pi  pic pic  ic y c yo  you you  ou w u wa  wan want ant  nt e t ed  edi edit dite ited ted  ed a d an  and and  nd i d i'  i'l i'll 'll  ll m l ma  mak make ake  ke i e it  it  it f t fo  for for  or y r yo  you you  ou c u ca  can can  an w n we  we  we p e pr  pre pre- re-o e-or -ord orde rder der  er t r th  the the  he # e #v  #vi #vin viny inyl nyl  yl v l ve  ver vers ersi rsio sion ion  on o n of  of  of # f #m  #mo #mod mode oder dern ernv rnvi nvin vint inta ntag tage age  ge ? e ?   ? w ? wi  wil will ill  ll i l it  it  it b t be  be  be a e av  ava avai vail aila ilab labl able ble  le o e on  on  on y n yo  you you' ou'r u're 're  re w e we  wel welc elco lcom come ome  me ? e ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? # ? #t  #ta #tag taga agar gart art  rt # t #p  #ph #pho phot hoto otoe toed oedi edit dit  it b t by  by  by ? y ??  ??? ???? ???  ?? y ? yo  you you' ou'r u're 're  re w e we  wel welc elco lcom come ome! me!  e!  !    