U2 - 11 O'Clock Tick Tock: http://t.co/sqeyn6bi MoA #U2newwave U2 - I Fall Down http://t.co/wodVpang #U2newwave @username I see what you did there. Nothing To Be Worried About Except Everything But You - Girless & The Orphan http://t.co/b5YAWstl via @username accendere @username e beccare Take Five. #priceless Listening to "Forever Cool" Internet Radio on @username http://t.co/IadmnVtn I’m listening to Hit the Road Jack by Ray Charles http://t.co/PsqXslFt via @username #jazz24 Now listening to: Medicine Bottle by Red House Painters The For Carnation - Emp. Man's Blues: http://t.co/ApU45s3a via @username Check out Roberto Fonseca – Zamazu http://t.co/r0RwYBHb via @username Ascolta Carolyn Leonhart – Sometimes I Think http://t.co/4PwDwJnN via @username Beach Boys - Wouldn't It Be Nice: http://t.co/lIYMGWxd via @username I Love Lists :: An Argument For Lists In Music http://t.co/10bsiz2x Listening to Slightly All the Time by Soft Machine #nowplaying http://t.co/XOEbJSXI Just entered to win a Nexus 10! Enter here:  http://t.co/XRCjb6FY via @username Listening to Waterloo Sunset by The Kinks #nowplaying #musicmonday http://t.co/9WYX3fJm Listening to Missing by The xx #nowplaying #musicmonday http://t.co/lYyTVrfV Listening to Cyborg by M83 #nowplaying #musicmonday http://t.co/deiXOpvs RT @username: B E R L U S C O N I Listening to Hero by Kleerup #nowplaying #tunesday http://t.co/D1XNKW30 Listening to Until We Bleed (feat. Lykke Li) by Kleerup http://t.co/0QT6zhCp Listening to Children Of The Grave by Black Sabbath #nowplaying http://t.co/25NPFFkM My Bloody Chinese Democracy http://t.co/fM3Kg4eF Lyons Maid poster - Retronaut http://t.co/wCxBAiW2 via @username Listening to Out on the Weekend by Neil Young #nowplaying http://t.co/bRcsFY3Y Check out RepliGo PDF Reader on Google Play! https://t.co/S2s5nIhj ? Summer Teenage Girl – Canadians http://t.co/7EASesyb #Spotify ? Aftermath – Sandro Codazzi http://t.co/A4mmxjuG #Spotify ? Second Sight – Lush http://t.co/FFjEtIac #Spotify ? Cupid Come – My Bloody Valentine http://t.co/Dbpdq3D6 #Spotify ? Nothing Much To Loose – My Bloody Valentine http://t.co/QJbdoPZw #Spotify Ce n'e` di roba su spotify. ? I’ve Waited Ages – Colin Newman http://t.co/O4p3fYRF #Spotify ? The Unknown Knows – Voivod http://t.co/c7NwOBCM #Spotify Italian elections: right, left or back to square one http://t.co/wBusdGZC3V via @username Check out Tapastic on Google Play! https://t.co/TxfQvHIbT7 Non vedo l'ora di avere 5 minuti per leggerlo: Election Preview: Italy 2013 | World Elections - http://t.co/j7a9ZZKEch ? The Waiting – Angel Olsen http://t.co/to4SpxOBgL #Spotify ? Good Good Bye – Giuni Russo http://t.co/Fg2UJbBgA1 #Spotify ? Coffy Is The Color - Soundtrack Version – Roy Ayers, Carl Clay http://t.co/6EMzCcokiC #Spotify @username can't wait for your analysis of the match ... Check out #Ancher – Toracebrace http://t.co/lqa60V3Yg0 via @username ? Fell On Black Days – Soundgarden http://t.co/Z3GMz0qUlQ #Spotify ? Circle Of Power – Soundgarden http://t.co/zfIWGH2Qzs #Spotify ? Head Down – Soundgarden http://t.co/We91lLTA4r #Spotify ? Oh My Golly! (Remastered) – Pixies http://t.co/izHPhP7Hgc #Spotify ? There Goes My Gun – Pixies http://t.co/Zyc7xClLHl #Spotify ? Cities – Hey Marseilles http://t.co/o8Djqw44yZ #Spotify @username how many games did they play without messi? ? Funeralopolis – Electric Wizard http://t.co/B3LiGw3bJj #Spotify ? Little Red Riding Hood Hit The Road – Robert Wyatt http://t.co/9fjylj9YIC #Spotify Where in the world are your followers? Map them by country, state or city at http://t.co/NynxuUHd2T ? Frontier Psychiatrist – The Avalanches http://t.co/NQA06R4ZyT #Spotify Authorization http://t.co/rxoovfBR6V Good read ? Corcovado (Quiet Nights Of Quiet Stars) – Stan Getz, Astrud Gilberto, Antonio Carlos Jobim, João Gilberto http://t.co/BCbWrTKJVZ totus politicus. @username manco ummagumma (o Frances the Mute)? ? New Math – Drive Like Jehu http://t.co/tWy1UZfYcf #Spotify ? Nothing Natural – Lush http://t.co/F1UyGhhoqU #Spotify @username the neverhood, road rash, lotus, james pond 2 Hugh Muir's diary http://t.co/mWufArfiuk via @username ? Koscinski's Requiem For A Golden Chariot – Giraffes? Giraffes! http://t.co/Ou4MpK5SDo #NowPlaying ? Bring Your Own Blood – The Redneck Manifesto http://t.co/PHLt9Xr6LX #NowPlaying ? Crybaby Blowout – Kinski http://t.co/2OqQJFaplN #NowPlaying ? Jaybird – Comets On Fire http://t.co/oZtVv5MSiT #NowPlaying ? Auberge Le Mouton Noir – Do Make Say Think http://t.co/UASLJXcHMH #NowPlaying ? Everybody Ruins – Q And Not U http://t.co/TW7mFdSyRW #NowPlaying ? Lil' Sparky – Q And Not U http://t.co/EGyuRifsNl #NowPlaying really useful, @username! howto read a file line by line: while read i; do echo $i;done < file.txt http://t.co/TjSrnseCEY ? Original Love – The Feelies http://t.co/mH60fBSEGE #NowPlaying ? Foxhole - Remastered LP Version – Television http://t.co/Iy7OXhJYA7 #NowPlaying Voivod – The Unknown Knows http://t.co/CL1uwyFtYd via @username Deconstructing: The O.C. And Indie Rock Gentrification http://t.co/X61hWdQiuK Listening to Dirty Feet and Giggles by Laika #nowplaying #tunesday http://t.co/DeoKi5Ji9d Listening to Breather by Laika #nowplaying http://t.co/mUNCckBW5S via @username Listening to Black Cat Bone by Laika #nowplaying #musicmonday http://t.co/M30HN8I7ei via @username Arcade Fire - Reflektor: http://t.co/6xlTlSkm1Y via @username [They did it again] Check out ???? – Risky http://t.co/rC5JwlZ5P9 via @username Listening to Do the Strand by Roxy Music #nowplaying #tunesday http://t.co/QtPkwFXHFq via @username Listening to Revolution Blues by Neil Young #nowplaying #musicmonday http://t.co/kxnonFnE3r Arcade Fire - Here Comes the Night Time: http://t.co/Giwd4IgBRX via @username Sonic Youth - Wish Fulfillment http://t.co/baCKDns2lg via @username Basia Bulat "Tall Tall Shadow" (Official Audio): http://t.co/iUAXUijKQz via @username American Beauty Soundtrack http://t.co/WCImHGkczC via @username Joe Hisaishi - The Rain: http://t.co/e3ypciL41Q via @username Acquarone given precautionary suspension by RCS Sport http://t.co/pn1uMudgRi via @username Debut album by @username & @username is free to download for a tweet/facebook post! Just share it! http://bit.ly/BPR01-DGM Epic win-win #ikeaordeath #nasum http://t.co/3WsMF5Ppku Richard Lloyd - The Cover Doesn't Matter - Ain't It Time: http://t.co/UydClv3h6U via @username Tom Verlaine - Souvenir for a dream: http://t.co/EiDhTSWD7y via @username ? New Math – Drive Like Jehu http://t.co/tWy1UZxzAP #NowPlaying Buzzcocks - Ever Fallen In Love (With Some You Shouldn't) http://t.co/CsIn5wqwBA via @username Don't think too hard about it. Use this thingy to generate a Twitter bio for yourself: http://t.co/jQL3wbQTbE My Bloody Valentine - Cupid Come: http://t.co/PJDZYswEYl via @username Arcade Fire - Reflektor (Full Album Teaser - Official): http://t.co/mFZB7GhyhD via @username @username Domenica @username goal, assist, man of the match e 10.0 su http://t.co/FNxn6bu9YN http://t.co/DPMiGsakbZ Daje Cote Daje! They did it again: Be Forest's new single "Captured Heart" - http://t.co/ovm3g2HNGT Mi Ami- "Time of Love" http://t.co/E54mYR5XE7 via @username No Biggie: Usain Bolt Says He Ate 1,000 Chicken McNuggets During Beijing Olympics http://t.co/Isqtb9qQyw via @username if an avalanche falls from Eyjafjallajökull and no one is swamped, does it make a sound? Yes, it sounds like Veður http://t.co/QXKActQks9 ? Haunted By You – Gene http://t.co/rCxAtlqqZn #NowPlaying 