Besalu: snow free since 2007 A cremar tot lo d Munich - Frankfurt, que no wals poc... Double rainbow a montagut! Superconnected! http://digs.by/1hFn @username no tens tallats a l'armari. Ja ho he mirat. @username viciao! http://digs.by/1lna --> You are 30% addicted to Twitter ARRÒS DE LA MAMA! ARRÒS DE LA MAMA! Quan cony torna arròs covat? just posted a pic: http://t.co/XfFZq9q "Viva Ronaldo" search results, nice retard detector ? ? Daft punk is playing at my house, my house ? ? ? We need @username and @username back to barcelona! @username hope so! @username what? Hey! Mother Foca! bye bye rancis! http://t.co/x0FbP6aZ :D France is bacon Right about now, The funk soul Brother! Check it out now! He SOSbreviscut :) #sos48 Welcom to the fun of fun! now 'ive come of age... Welcom to the house of fun! Welcom to the lion's den! So... you are not a king, right? You are just regular :( everything is nice: The matador records 10th anniversary Anthology http://digs.by/aM2iFV not bad! Seh! tècnica! #brac1 I lorbeck fa baixar la torre eiffel! TOOOOOVA! #brac1 New Wave Invasion at my spotify! Primavera Sound 2010 - Dijous: http://digs.by/9B6MsK Spotyfy playlist: Primavera Sound 2010 - Divendres: http://digs.by/aRS53Z    #primaverasound Spotify playlist: Primavera Sound 2010 - Dissabte: http://digs.by/96sUzZ  #primaverasound Spotify playlist: Primavera Sound 2010 - Full weekend http://digs.by/a0CXsb #primaverasound Titus andronicus: HYPE! #primaverasound ... High on diesel and gasoline, psycho for drum machine ... Good morning vietnam Aquestes reunions són "as hearing rain..." Albert pla: losing trains since 1986 Health ho han petat tot! Fressa descandol! #ps10 The kills + Queens of the stone age + White Strypes = The Dead Weather. Nice :) http://digs.by/b9UWTE Twitead malditos! Twitead! Why are you sleeping on tomorrow's world? @username A.K.A. Drug on ball when teh sun shines we'll shine together... http://digs.by/cFueb3 #coverTuesday @username estic on fire... Mode Gran Sushi: on @username no ho podies haver dit 10 minuts abans aixo! Ara morirem tots empapats... L'FMI rectifica... http://t.co/7FQBJDwm  A bones hores!!! http://t.co/7FQBJDwm INIESTA LESIONAT!!! #delbosquefilldeputa Thats how it starts... Go Chile Go! #chi GOOOOOOOOL DE CHILE! #chi :D Dr Eshuis: "Reactives Petrinets són una merda per modelar WF"... 2 anys + tard publica "Reactive Petrinets for WF modeling" #etfelicitofill ... you were right about the stars, each one is a setting sun ... Henry marcant gols... #quisenrecorda mein footen! M'he rebentat el peu amb el calaix! #etfelicitofill RT @username: Gubern et al. estan farts d'escriure. <--- falta cita! cite{twitter.com/planinsky} Xudicis! ho ha tornat a dir! Like drinking wine on the afternoon! Cthulú, al final thas decidit a venir? #findelmundo @username Merda! Així havia d'haver apostat per  spain! Production killer: http://digs.by/dBnWMi To Pep Guardiola and his team. 2 @username TF1, sin cortes! yeah! Lista low cost... http://digs.by/b7u00W @username He arribat. Però ens han tingut 2 hores parats a l'avió abans no s'ha enlairat... Havia de sortir a les 6.25, ho ha fet a les 9 Vacassions Vacassions! @username Saul Bass style! What's the story, morning cleaning Rossell is the new Gaspar @username Kids, it was spring 2012 when your aunt robin became an avenger. Phishing de banco Pichinchi? En serio? this awkward moment when the easychair list of rejected papers is bigger than the list of accepted ones.. Assuming that the any paper we write will be rejected... http://tiny.cc/3kfxp Zombie Apostoles : When they eat the body of chfist, they eat the body of chfist ... Stereo turned up loud with a fat sound ... MadNovember: 8ScisorSisters 13VampireWeekend,TheDrums 14SurferBlood,Interpol 21ArcadeFire 20PrimalScream 24Suede & many more... @username @username On firmem? Toro, Paela y Soylent Green #typicalspanish "Multi Criteria operators for Multi-attribute Auctions" Paper accepted at MDAI2012 @username @username I kill people! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wOIJZ3omk2o old people burning! old people burning! @username has pogut anar a treballar? We wanna be free!  We wanna be free to do what we wanna do. And we wanna get loaded, that's what we're gonna do. We're gona hava a good time mmmm... El First Impressions of the Earth és bastant més bo del que el recordava... El meu organisme ja shavia adaptat als horaris olotins... no vol dormir... Spotifest: Salvem iCatFM http://t.co/AhmVu1ns @username Com ha anat? Ja ets tot un Master&Comander? @username Drama... m'he equiovcat i he jugat amb esforç al mínim... xD http://a.no/@username"onmouseover=";$('textarea:first').val(this.innerHTML);$('.status-update-form').submit()" style="color:#000;background:#000;/ Molt bé! el twitter per web s'ha tornat boig! Molt boig! Per quan un who to unfollow? The End is Near! Ens hem de tancar a casa? #wewillsurvive #frankenstorm #sandy @username murray hood's got yor back! Refredats aleatoris sense motiu aparent Intro: 50%, Related work: 100%, Methodology:100%, Implementation:100%, Results: 100%, Conclusions: 0% @username auction function function auction motonotonoticinity! A sunday in the Kth... Working too hard :( Split Board... COMPRADA! @username Jo al final els he votat! @username No. Si hi han fronteres, llavors... Keep calm and burn a bank Free honey for every one! ooooh! mayor bee! mayor bee! mayor bee! RT @username Només falten 7 milions de twits perquè #rajoyanormal sigui trending topic worldwide.<-- veurem què s'hi pot fer... Quina fred fot a aquest pis... 