@username for what? chrome 14 supports Native Client. #NaCl those classy songs m/ #maachis just realised, have to finish some left out things immediately and these exams really suck. #screwed @username congrates! :) #include<stdio.h> void main() { printf("Good Bye Ritchie"); } Lose yourself in @username’s #Lights, an interactive & colorful music experience using #webgl http://t.co/jrb9UvMW @username it was created by Nohn Dewar in 1846. @username @username i meant John Dewar, sorry for the typo. @username  Single Malt whiskey and The white label blend. @username others are dewar's signature, special reserve blended, founder's reserve blended. @username Water, malt , yeast and people. I am going back to the stars  #hateexams #coldplay m/ @username i have vlsi to go, then me too giving up on elec. :D @username same here.. gonna read now. best of luck :) @username why don't you forward them to gmail instead? @username @username WTF! so i cant go back to webmail :S one more sem is gone, and i have one thing to share, 'Getting lost helps you knowing yourself better'. is in love with #lays saucy salsa falvour.. @username what's up? saw your pics mentioning <3 in captions.. ahem ahem. @username you are going to be ass-kicked if you get more than me. @username are you using three modems on your laptop? let me guess bsnl ethernet and reliance and airtel data-cards? @username yeah, i am still wondering about that, but dont tell me. I am trying to figure it out. @username which s/w did you use to write grub to mbr? reply asap.. @username in windows. @username nothing, i did comes college today. :P @username windows 8 screw me, @username is an asshole, i wants windows 7 setup and other s/w, so i goes. @username thou starts gre classes? @username wtf! it ain't good grading.. i got BC!! salla bc! @username i didn't mean that i deserved more, i expected more. :) @username @username lol :D i knows.. i knows..! @username ahaha.. seriously? @username you tell they are good bcz you are aware of network security unlike others! :P @username FUCK.. you seriously did it!! @username you are freak!! why? Up-time 24 hours and counting.. (not my computer's, mine :P ) @username details? about internship. @username are you sure it will remain cool when you use it? :P :P @username I dont understand this.. do you mean like remote desktop? or offline access to live profile? @username omg! they are going to provide 20/40 gB space to each registered windows? that's awesome! :) filter will run continuously! :D #OS @username and half of siddharth's bread-pakoda too i remember :P 1: what was prof teaching in economics class? 2: what economics class? 1:arre..first lecture. wasn't it..ohh! #bakar #SEN @username it's said that if you can drive in a'bad, you can drive anywhere. :P Got to spend whole night at delhi aorport.. :x it's not that boring though :P http://t.co/0a5ePfiq Everytime I hear this, makes me buy a new flute! broken 3 flutes already, so tin flute this time #TheCorrs #Intrumental http://t.co/d5usRDyp Maybe I am late to notice, but cloud based desktop?? :O #whatCloudCanDo I just realised I am an awesome instantaneous planner! m/ just landed on this interesting forum.. http://t.co/fx84HArw #fb @username we so badly need this! @username why not me! :P @username this https://t.co/haiqfeZ3 LED exceeds 100% efficiency. madness right? you gotta believe it, these are MIT guys. http://t.co/FPgWTImk @username Node.cs - a C# version of Node.js http://t.co/LdquymvO @username hahaha!! what was it about? An interactive animation explaining what REALLY happened in Inception, the movie!: http://t.co/a6Sky5h7 via @username @username then what would you say when hate story comes :P @username and what will allah do to hindu womans? i love this semester just to have a day like today, when you submit it and get done with it. #fb @username whatever geographic reasons may be, it ain't the number 2012 for sure!! I believe this http://t.co/Do9XTX4o :P last pacman -Syu made my touchpad working like shit! :-( hopeless internet of daiict. #examtimetrolling @username been there :P @username tonight's gonna be a good night :D @username hows gre prep going? @username http://t.co/Fl59RAVi interesting @username how abt this? http://t.co/xwuJz7fh @username is reading barron's wordlist right now #OyeLalit @username bcz it was started by someone special in past, i am just continuing #OyeLalit :P @username and it's dhruv btw :P :) poetry at its best, in loop http://t.co/6E2LhGs0 #jealous #friendship #kay @username not seeing you on fb these days.. moved on? :P @username @username who else? @username @username haha true that. #late :P @username @username really! that too #kuchbhi tweets :P @username hahaha that was an epic one! xD @username wt abt graph? started? watching @username glastonbury concert feels like living that dream! Y U NO come in india! #BringColdplayToIndia has finished every last piece of cooked food in kitchen #homealone @username why dude! where to? @username tweeting finally? :P A few minutes of perfection!: http://t.co/mhuXEgdh via @username #IfYouGiveALittleLove @username like this http://t.co/fjCV7CtF @username what do you think about it? i like to keep updated with rolling releases! and firefox rolls out its 20+MB new version every other day :S @username @username @username yes archlinux. i dont mean it literally! but its been frequent recently. just checked, 7 releases in last 4 n half months :P I hate it when i get caught after doing something wrong! :x got to learn telling ppl i dont have time :-/ @username 8 or 5? @username no man! i respect that underdog! @username @username wtf man! anything now! give me one reason to hate Nadal! he is the best player presently, you have got to accept that @username @username aww cho cutee! :P this is hell of a prejudice, guys! wtf #WhoAmI trending! dont they know they cant inject bash commands in twitter! @username  you were asking once why we use linux, probably this :P http://t.co/TSOn3xoM has moved from latte to americano @username roses are #FF0000 violets are  #0000FF all my base are belong to you! #geek #RosesAreRedVioletsAreBlue that phase after long time when you start watching hours of episodes in single go #BreakingBad #fuck linux partition got screwed! installing arch+xfce with @username 's bulky mozilla pendrive(blocks 2 more usb) at 2 am http://t.co/dAFruTePzA @username i dont know man.. i should give up on dual booting with windows and only rely on linux! but games.. :sigh: missing awesome #KDEMeetup in my own college :( 