#444 - Give me straight line. (Courtesy of C. Schiavi) - Dammi retta http://t.co/4yGujn0dCC #445 - High ringing. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Altisonante http://t.co/EY0GiJR3ik #447 - God liking. (Courtesy of M. Battiston) - A Dio piacendo http://t.co/0uZkPEhz5l #449 - Make the punk. - Far la cresta http://t.co/3hcJtn9p09 #451 - Accident between titans. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Scontro fra titani http://t.co/bv6S6QRAVN #455 - With the bitter in the mouth. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Con l’amaro in bocca http://t.co/2YwhRPcxi9 #456 - I go at arm. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Vado a braccio http://t.co/TpjKAvRQAv #457 - Coldhard. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Freddura http://t.co/OQ6Ah46wFJ #458 - I go there at wedding. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Ci vado a nozze http://t.co/V18FLKOOL6 #460 - A fixed nail. - Un chiodo fisso http://t.co/HJP1SIzmA1 #461 - To hold fight. - Tenere botta http://t.co/t3ROGBr7J5 #462 - The double way. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Il doppio senso http://t.co/dhpc0DGpDG #465 - Tonight is gone in white too. (Courtesy of S. Spreafico) - Anche ‘sta notte è andata in bianco http://t.co/4uaxA6jjbu Ho aggiunto un video a una playlist di @username: http://t.co/pTgNvnQyFu Joe Bonamassa - Live From The Royal Albert Hall (Part 1/2) #467 - Willthrow. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Farabutto http://t.co/JOMjq96EzR #468 - Leaves us the pens. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Lasciarci le penne http://t.co/LMXLP8eiV5 #470 - From what earth is earth. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Da che mondo è mondo http://t.co/yVCnt1IXRn #472 - At brought of hand. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - A portata di mano http://t.co/Yd1vYRZQMH #473 - Try suite. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Prova costume http://t.co/uNAZpBt2LG #475 - Grandfathering. (feat. A. Castelletti) - Nonnisimo http://t.co/H7e57LRyzD #476 - The anger of God. (Courtesy of C. Gatti) - L’ira di Dio http://t.co/tR1tMrf8aI #477 - Dishorsing. (feat. A. Castelletti) - Scavallare http://t.co/biMwvCdJS3 #478 - You can’t have the full tank and the drunk wife! - Non puoi avere la botte piena e la moglie ubriaca http://t.co/CfB6nvKpzE #480 - Wife and cows of your country. (Courtesy of C. Gatti) - Moglie e buoi dei paesi tuoi http://t.co/CebE7n6KQB #481 - It’s a headwork! (Courtesy of C. Gatti) - È un capolavoro http://t.co/UPt0sDu4N1 #482 - The ace of time. (Courtesy of C. Gatti) - Lasso di tempo http://t.co/zkpKRbnPuY #483 - Riceight. (Courtesy of S. Spreafico) - Risotto http://t.co/x8WwwrsllK #484 - Going to genius. (Courtesy of S. Spreafico) - Andare a genio http://t.co/RqHGD2ht3r #485 - A tiny arrow. - Una frecciatina http://t.co/TIX8OV9yN4 #487 - Hitting the dog for the farmyard. (Courtesy of A. Castelletti) - Menare il can per l’aia http://t.co/BTjtGwyCqj 