@username @username WAAROM NOEM JE ME DIK :'( KIJK DAAROM HEB JE GEEN VRIENDEN "They say that things cannot grow, beneath the winter snow, or so I have been told.." "Seems like I'll have to take that one step backwards, 'cause one step ahead is a step too far away from you" Stay Black In The Air Tonight - Phil Collins RT @username: Flyer 3e event hard battles! http://t.co/8NFqD7pfji So I dub thee Unforgiven. All over after tomorrow. "Don't just want a piece, I want my own destiny.. If you got it, I'm gon' take it, If you're in it, you're coming with me" Runnin' = classic En dan nu naar Gifted - Surreal & The Sound Providers Son they shook, 'cause ain't no such things as halfway crooks I'm only in the company of kings. RT @username: Lets get ready to rumble!!!!!!!!!! @username @username Awh, poor girl. Foto's Hard Battles Killer Instinct https://t.co/X5LcQz4TXA @username @username @username @username @username @username @username That's not meant for me. @username Check 't forum They shootin'! Aw made you look. Dreams - Cunninlynguists ft. Tunji & B.J. The Chicago Kid Real Muthaphukkin' G's Good Girls Go Bad - Game ft. Drake @username Harry Styles douchegel @username Linksonder, but that's my taste "I'm just saying, hey Mona Lisa, come home you know you can't roam without Caesar" Everything I'm not makes me everything I am. @username if you don't get sarcasm, yeah. Highs 2 Lows - Nujabes ft. Cise Starr I got the wings of angels walking down the valley of death, watching my step, 'cause The Devil's never one to respect Piraat013 changed my life. Singing in the rain.. Singing with a longontsteking @username You know you want it #yeshomo This ain't nothing to relate to.. Laurence Fishburnes rol in Mystic River - dit is te mooi http://t.co/EFN20zA5FO The Ride - Drake @username Phil Collins @username It's actually pretty nice in here. @username Just wait 'till married life RED 2 was nice, nu Wolverine! "But if all I'm hearing is me, then who should I be afraid of?" Stop trying to please everyone, please the ones that would do the same for you. Amen. Childish Gambino, Ab-Soul, Joey Bada$$.. Dopeste rappers van dit moment imo. "He's the kind of guy you don't wanna bring home to mom. Tell 'em why." "Cause I'll fuck your mom!" #genius Met moeite m'n ogen open. "The things I do for love" - Jaime Lannister @username @username you know what iyyis Wtf we hebben chopsticks in de trein. What's up loempia? @username Mystery solved! In love with her <3 Trust issues.. SLOW IT DOWN! Trust these shoes. @username Hahahaha Mark Henry up in this bitch Check it, Kama vs Krae, dope battle, support ieks! http://t.co/kGwe4ggGoU Murder to Excellence van The Throne = ill "First Steps"Completed! #aceattorneyt "The First Turnabout"Completed! #aceattorneyt 7 Days - Craig David Camping? Nee camwhatsapp Who the fuck is @username? @username @username Haha check je whapp ff "Turnabout Sisters"Completed! #aceattorneyt RT @username: How many Jews does it take to screw in a light bulb?  I don't know but 6 million wasn't enough to brighten my day "E equals MC squared, nah.. E equals Eater of MC's, beware" Success is the best revenge, that's true. I bought this gun from the money I got as a result of my success. @username IK LIJK GODVERDOMME HELEMAAL NIET OP ADRIAAN ???? Fuck outta here. Prins Friso overleden. Yup, I did it. RTV@username: TOO SOON, TOO SOON!! @username Iscool Strings http://t.co/FiPDNI95ec Financial Freedom - 50 Cent Almost home "But but hol' up, I'm not done yet" New World - Nas, favo nummer van Nastradamus, alleen al omdat ie Toto's Africa samplet. @username Hahaha random search? @username What's The Difference blijf ik nice vinden ja. "I am on point, bitch I'm verbally cactus" "Don't try act like I ain't poppin' homie, my style like Mandela meets Monster Kody" FOX this shit. They be simmin like Kimora "If my girlfriend wants to paint my nails, I'd let her." .. .. Please give God back your dick. "M'n chick" "M'n sma" "M'n bitch" Gewoon m'n lady, thank you. Have fun at the Vroesenpark folks! #Battleraps Binnenkort elke werkdag op RTL 5: The Bold and The Battlecats. "Since the Moon separated from Earth, that's why they say I'm the greatest that ever orchestrated a verse" @username @username Same goes for Alzheimer's disease! @username All right/alright*, people* Even the most ignorant people can prove themselves to be a hero, they just have to be loyal. RT @username: http://t.co/JlmQPiR3vc For real, @username  en @username moeten teamen, team Pornmetric. Harde punches guaranteed. "Put 'em in a box.. DOOS!" Hurt - Johnny Cash >>>>>>>>> "Long live the idols, may they never be your rivals, Pac was like Jesus, Nas wrote the Bible" Who (Victor Niglio Remix) - Plastik Funk & Tujamo, killer music voor in de ochtend, thanks @username "Freedom or jail, clips inserted, a baby's being born same time a man is murdered, the beginning and end" Chained like a Michael Vick hobby. @username No shit Sherlock. Zowat alles wordt op de hak genomen. "You know, I learned something today", allemaal mooie lessen en true ook "If what I say gets on your last nerve, then holla man, but truth is, y'all can't touch me like Pac's hologram" Whoops. @username @username PUKE OVER HIM! @username Wow stoer man @username IK HAAT MAANDAG OMG MAANDAG IS DE VRIEND DIE JE NIET WIL HEBBEN MAAR ELKE KEER TERUGKOMT RT ALS JE MAANDAG HAAT @username @username was een promo battle, no judges. 1 ronde unlimited. Laatste 2 Hard Battles gister op straat, back to the basics! 'Cause you know who did you know what with you know who, but let's keep that between me and you for now 