@username Don't take their abuse Bestune - you are CRAZY_BUSY!  Even I can clearly see that.  Ignore the haters - they don't know you Some Ratty Teenager made up the idea of SENIOR PROM long ago so that tired, middle aged moms would wake up randomly all night long & worry. Chattanooga Strong  -  Go Mocs! @username Can't wait to keep up with our favorite wrestling team - GO MOCS! @username FOLLOW @username - it's awesome and they just welcomed John to the team :)   Go Mocs!! @username GOOD LUCK!  You can do it - I haven't seen anything yet get the better of you, Tough Girl!!!  love, gigi @username @username Wow! Inspirational!  Have you girls had any thoughts about giving up nursing and becoming motivational speakers?? @username HAS to be K. Felix! WHY I SUB:   ME:You are NOT an ATHEIST-stop trying to side-track me. KID: How do YOU know? Me: For one thing, your name is Jesus. KID: True. @username I will miss you!!!  Come home safe and sound - come to 102 the MINUTE you roll back into town.  I love you, BB  <3  Debsky @username John's"Once again,Mrs. S, I AM SO SORRY!  PLEASE BELIEVE ME IT IS JOHN!....He's moving soon- so East TN will smell like Mid TN @username @username As always, girls - Keepin' it Classy!  I'm sure your mothers are so proud. @username Your parents must be so proud, Seniorita. @username @username  I KNOW that's right! @username Corona in a can.  Classy. @username @username ps-who do you think taught her to drop, pop and lock it??  You're not just BORN knowing that stuff! @username -I love you too!! I'm not really crazy-I just get so excited when I see/talk to @username -can't wait to hang with you girls @username @username @username This kind of makes me DOUBT you when you firmly denied seeing that movie!!!  You are grounded! I like my Martial Arts MIXED. @username Good News-I did a quick random survey of 10,000 people and 3 of them are having a worse day than you!  SEE-IT CAN ALWAYS BE WORSE! "I think, therefore I am."  Does this mean my teenagers are a figment of my imagination?? @username   The No. 1 Killer of Meetings -- And What You Can Do About It | Fox Business http://t.co/U8BIzwPS via @username @username  ("juice break"!) I <3 Jimmy Fallon vs Justin Bieber - Late Night With Jimmy Fallon: http://t.co/SAXMfaWt via @username "My dad was a drunk, a gambler and a womanizer.  I worshipped him." @username from General's Daughter. @username You are a bad girl for repeating that!  That was a Private Mother/Daughter Motivational Speech!!! Oh, and Yes, you are right! @username Why were you running late to work?  Did YOUR MOM'S CAR GET TOWED AGAIN?! Sorry those pesky little college students are in your way @username I've been trying and trying and trying to figure out why your twitter name is PaRiPaRtYpAnTs? I keep looking for clues-hmmm? @username @username If Katie wasn't there, and Katie's crazy mother wasn't there..... I have no idea - Sorry  (Otherwise-simple) @username and @username - Thought movie of Mon's baby Caden, Aunt Katie, cousins,etc-might help!  http://t.co/pu7Jj9P0 Wrestling - Schedule - University of Tennessee at Chattanooga Official Athletics Site: http://t.co/AEZeRmxk   GO MOCS!!! That Justin Bieber can really dance. @username @username Why don't you two Super Cool girls go to your regular hang-out, the Library, and try to pick up some Freshmen Bio majors? @username  Am I wrong to be fooled by the rocks that you got? @username @username good luck on your future careers and job interviews, Ladies!  #classy - that's right, I just did my first hashtag.  Bam. @username Skeeter! Since you love your mother and are coming home, could I get you to drop by for & take to my precious one in Chatt? @username @username  UNTWEET-UNTWEET! AND GO HOME NOW- THIS IS YOUR MOTHER TALKING- GO HOME AND DIG OUT COLLEGE RULES AND RE-STUDY THEM - NOW! @username @username Much more important than anything you two have found -is reuniting that famous BRAIN TRUST and figuring out my CRAZY spots @username @username Please remember that discretion is the better part of valor-very imp. here, ladies! KD, pls explain that to KT!  haha ilu @username @username Are you coming home this weekend? Oh-and that message made me miss you more! @username Are you in Franklin still?  What time do you head back to Chatt? @username WHAT? That is straight up Skangsta! You haven't lost it :)  (Did anybody come here that I know-going back today?) @username Are you with Austin???  I need to send a couple of things to JohnnyBoy with him to Chatt if possible!!  _Also - yay for KD! @username Ok. OH! - KT told me about KD - I had no idea!  I know you will love it and will make so many good friends there. @username I think Rachel is telling me you are in Fr. headed to Chatt today?  True?  I'm Aus's BFF (not RV) & need to send pk to Aus! @username I saw JB was "fighting big cats" this wkend - did you "slay"anything???  Would love a pic w/you and your catch! <3 You Kylie!!! @username I wish JB had Twitter- if nothing else, so I could get you to hack in and post for him, "Justin Bieber is the reason I smile"-fun @username  I just read that JB got a Twitter account!!  I can't believe it :) @username @username  Now I am a little afraid the world might really end in 2012!!!  Go Mocs! @username  What shoes are you wearing for Taylor Swift's appearance on VMA's tonight, y'all?! missing my girls- @username , @username , @username , @username , @username , @username - What's up, Ladies? @username Hey!  Did you guys go to knoxville today?  Big Fun had by all? @username Hey Alan!  Would you please p.m. me or text me Susan's phone number?  Need her and can't find number!!! @username YOU ROCK! @username HEY MON - hit me up with your schedule 4 the next few days - please!! - trying to make my calendar and you-know-who is VIP #1 @username Like visiting the Fam??  I bet they were thrilled :) @username I'm sorry - I have no idea what you are talking about???!!???  You obviously have me confused in your mind with someone else! @username  AWESOME, PARTY PANTS!!!!!  Now BREATHE... but only a little- then get right back on it!!  :) @username if you can remember where JB used to live -  stop by and bring me a couple of shirts- I am inspired by your effort and love! @username Are you and Terr-Bear Beefin' again? @username Do they need any other interns there?- tell them I'm SLIGHTLY older, mature and #partypants is not part of my twitter name:) @username @username @username What is up?  You ok? - just getting your arm checked, I hope!... OR-are you getting tired of stairs? @username Your biggest baby brother-his shirt says it ALL - and -duh, we knew that! Isn't he so cute?! #AllProsNoCons http://t.co/khc3EmAt @username You better stay away!  I can't write what he is saying about you guys-TRASH TALK like crazy-it is pretty ugly-u know how he gets! @username Oh boy- I can't wait!  You two are going to have to take it outside if punches are thrown!! @username  Terr-Bear found his "gift" from you - AFTER SCHOOL!!!!!!  Nice. Jack Shrader & I are in CHATT for UTC BLOOD DRIVE/WRESTLING CLINIC TOMORROW-will be a great day with the #CHATTANOOGASTRONG MOCS WRESTLERS!! @username you are welcome! @username    @username  Can you defend this sweet momma??  I love that Little John-John and had to protect him and make sure he was safe! @username Awwwwwwwwwww - I love you too, Loser!!!  Can't WAIT to see you! @username You really can't imagine!!! Wish you were here to share it with:) James gave me b-day toy fit for a one-year-old little girl and her grandmother to play in I can't wait! http://t.co/bP0oHJFz @username What if you really do know how to spell, but a lady named Siri on your new phone is deaf, ca-razy, and a horrible speller!?! @username Did you lose an ipod at Shrader house possibly?  Trying to track down owner! @username Can't you just come stay with me for a couple of days??!!!??!!!! @username @username @username @username @username There is a princess running wild up in here - watch out!! http://t.co/bZCzU0M8 @username having Twitter account 2nd only in shock value to @username having one!!  Go, T -party like it's 2010! http://t.co/e0ggBlf9 I don't think he will do it - he can't- for some reason, he can't, or he would have already done so.  They are a secret....@username "Snooze"?Yes,sleep-walking is the easiest response to overwhelming, serious things.  Sadly, ignoring never helps.@username @username AWESOME DAY@username -big crowd- Big Fun-lots of exciting wrestling! Mocs look awesome! http://t.co/pu5DTzYy UTC Blue/Gold Match yesterday-OUTSIDE! -What an Exciting and FUN DAY! We love our MOCS and our Coaches! @username http://t.co/pusPs5Jy TRANSCRIPT: Megyn Kelly&#8217;s Interview With Charles Woods, Father of Former Navy SEAL Killed in Libya Attack http://t.co/AgSoGTUh You are young, girl!  Can't change past-I WISH, but can start today, taking steps to be who/where you want to be!  123-GO!! @username @username Your awesomeness has made me unaware of your height--I say, Sorry to your son, but short or tall, he's doomed to be awesome @username @username @username @username @username @username Happy Halloween from your fave little princess! http://t.co/LHh3a3f8 @username not in need of a Coach purse, but might buy some of your clothes!  Do you have anything smaller than zero, b/c that's all I wear! @username Check yourself before you wreck yourself... you know you could end up chained to a treadmill <3 @username @username Go, JB!!!!  Go Mocs!! @username @username - sounds right to me - keep going and have a great season! @username thanks for being my text friend (TFF?) during Mocs matches today.. it helps to have someone to cheer with/be nervous with!!!  <3 Monday Moc Talk 11-12-12 http://t.co/s13ewpFu ... COME OUT THIS FRIDAY!!!- 4 teams total, wrestling starts at 2pm, UTC VS IOWA (#2 TEAM) 7PM Ready for Awesome Night! @username  #GO MOCS!!! YOUR FANS LOVE YOU- LET'S GO!! @username COMP. LOST my voice during your AWESOME match!!  How am I supposed to cheer at FR. Tourn tm for JS? Signs Language? #yourfault @username Thank you for AWESOME NIGHT! Crazy FUN -Wrestlers, Fans, Sold-out Arena-Electric -So Happy to be part of this great program! UTC Freshmen Wrestlers doing GREAT and having Fun at King College Open Tournament today! @username @username http://t.co/hJgKnvCU I'm not saying who's chair this is ... But she is small, round and low to the ground! http://t.co/YFav7ngv Grapple At The Garden: December 16th, 2012: http://t.co/SYYi97VD via @username  @username  CHATTANOOGA STRONG IN NEW YORK CITY! @username  how many times were you forced to say this on Thanksgiving Night Shift.  Start practicing now for Christmas! http://t.co/KzGtGgso I get even sadder :(  BUT-as long as there is gas in my tank or money on my debit card, you KNOW I'll be back to visit SOOOOON!  @username Danger, Danger, PartyPants!!!! @username "They say" if you don't stand for something, you will surely fall for anything!  Don't do it! @username It all makes sense now!  Prodigy. 