#31 313 13  3 -  -  - t  tu tur urn rns ns  s s  su sun uns ns. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - g  gi gir ira ras aso sol oli li  i #  #3 #31 314 14  4 -  -  - a  ag aga gai ain ins nst st  t h  ha han and nd. d.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  co con ont ntr tro rom oma man ano no  o #  #3 #31 316 16  6 -  -  - w  wi wit ith th  h i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôm ôm  m b  ba bac ack ck. k.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  co con ont nto tor orn rno no  o #  #3 #31 317 17  7 -  -  - d  di div ive ve  e a  at at  t t  th the he  e h  he hea ear art rt. t.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - t  tu tuf uff ffo fo  o a  al al  l c  cu cuo uor ore re  e #  #3 #32 320 20  0 -  -  - t  ti tin iny ny  y r  ro roa oas ast st. t.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - a  ar arr rro ros ost sti tic ici cin ino no  o #  #3 #32 321 21  1 -  -  - a  at at  t p  pa pai ain in. n.  . -  -  - a  ap app ppe pen ena na  a #  #3 #32 322 22  2 -  -  - p  pu put ut  t t  th the he  e h  ha han and nds ds  s a  ah ahe hea ead ad. d.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . p  pe ped ede der ers rse sen en) n)  ) -  -  - m  me met ett tte ter ere re  e l  le le  e m  ma man ani ni  i a  av ava van ant nti ti  i #  #3 #32 325 25  5 -  -  - w  wh wha hat at  t a  a  a t  ti tin iny ny  y t  ty typ ype pef efa fac ace ce! e!  ! (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  ch che he  e c  ca car ara rat att tte ter eri rin ino no! o!  ! #  #3 #32 326 26  6 -  -  - d  do don onk nke key eya yac act ct. t.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - m  mu mul ula lat att tto to  o #  #3 #32 328 28  8 -  -  - e  en ent nte ter ere red ed  d a  at at  t t  te ten ens ns  s l  le leg eg. g.  . -  -  - e  en ent ntr tra rat ato to  o a  a  a g  ga gam amb mba ba  a t  te tes esa sa  a #  #3 #32 329 29  9 -  -  - p  po pok oke ke  e t  to too oot oth th. h.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti  i f  fe fea eat at. t.  . m  m. m.  . e  en eng ngo gol oll lli li) i)  ) -  -  - s  st stu tuz uzz zzi zic ica cad ade den ent nte te  e #  #3 #33 330 30  0 -  -  - b  br bri rin ing ng  g h  ho hom ome me  e t  th the he  e r  re res esu sul ult lt. t.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f g  g. g.  . t  to toi oia ia) a)  ) -  -  - p  po por ort rta tar are re  e a  a  a c  ca cas asa sa  a i  il il  l r  ri ris isu sul ult lta tat ato to  o #  #3 #33 333 33  3 -  -  - a  at at  t f  fa fac ace ce  e g  ga gar arl rli lic ic. c.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f t  t. t.  . l  lo los osc sch chi hi) i)  ) -  -  - a  av avv vvi vis isa sag agl gli lia ia¬ a¬† ¬†  † #  #3 #33 334 34  4 -  -  - r  re re- e-a -as ass ss. s.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . s  s. s.  . p  pe ped ede der ers rse sen en) n)  ) -  -  - r  ri rin inc ncu cul ulo lo  o #  #3 #33 335 35  5 -  -  - a  a  a l  lu lum ump mp  p a  at at  t t  th the he  e t  th thr hro roa oat at. t.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - u  un un  n n  no nod odo do  o a  al all lla la  a g  go gol ola la  a #  #3 #33 336 36  6 -  -  - h  he he  e s  st sta tay ays ys  s o  on on  n h  hi his is. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  so som ome meo eon one ne  e i  i  i d  do don on‚ n‚Ä ‚Äô Äôt ôt  t r  re rem eme mem emb mbe ber er) r)  ) -  -  - s  st sta ta  a s  su sul ull lle le  e s  su sue ue  e i  i  i f  fa fav avo vor ori rit ite ted ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o l  le les es  s l  lu lut uth thi hie ier ers rs  s -  -  - p  pe per erd rdo don ona nal ala la  a (  (b (bo bol ol√ l√© √©r ©ro rol olo lo) o)  ) #  #3 #33 338 38  8 -  -  - w  wa wat ate ter er  r i  in in  n m  mo mou out uth th. h.  . -  -  - a  ac acq cqu qua ua  a i  in in  n b  bo boc occ cca ca  a #  #3 #33 339 39  9 -  -  - w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the he  e t  ti tim ime mes es  s t  th tha hat at  t r  ru run uns ns. s.  . -  -  - c  co coi oi  i t  te tem emp mpi pi  i c  ch che he  e c  co cor orr rro ron ono no  o #  #3 #34 341 41  1 -  -  - y  yo you ou  u l  li liv ive ve  e i  it it. t.  . (  (‚ (‚Ä ‚Äú Äúi úi  i k  kn kno now ow  w a  a  a c  ci cit ity ty‚ y‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù s  sp spe pec eci cia ial al  l e  ed edi dit iti tio ion on  n b  by by  y a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - t  te tel ela lav avi viv iv  v #  #3 #34 342 42  2 -  -  - t  th the he  e f  fo foo oot ot‚ t‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s t  tr tre ree ee. e.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . b  bu bub uba ban ani ni) i)  ) -  -  - l  la la  a p  pi pia ian ant nta ta  a d  de del el  l p  pi pie ied ede de  e #  #3 #34 343 43  3 -  -  - o  ou out ut  t r  re rea ead ads ds. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - f  fu fuo uor ori ri  i l  le leg egg gge ge  e #  #3 #34 345 45  5 -  -  - i  it it‚ t‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s a  at at  t a  a  a s  sh sho hot ot  t o  of of  f g  gu gun un. n.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f c  c. c.  . g  ga gat att tti ti  i f  fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -¬ -¬† ¬†√ †√® √®  ® a  a  a u  un un  n t  ti tir iro ro  o d  di di  i s  sc sch chi hio iop opp ppo po  o #  #3 #34 347 47  7 -  -  - i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôm ôm  m b  bo boa oat ati tin ing ng. g.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - m  mi mi  i s  st sto to  o i  im imb mba bar arc rca can and ndo do  o #  #3 #34 348 48  8 -  -  - c  ca car art rti tin ina na  a t  to tor orn rna nas aso sol ole le. e.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . a  am ame men end ndo dol ola lag agi gin ine ne) e)  ) -  -  - l  li lit itt ttl tle le  e p  pa pap ape per er  r c  co com ome meb eba bac ack cks ksu sun un  n #  #3 #34 348 48  8 -  -  - l  li lit itt ttl tle le  e p  pa pap ape per er  r c  co com ome meb eba bac ack cks ksu sun un. n.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . a  am ame men end ndo dol ola lag agi gin ine ne) e)  ) -  -¬ -¬† ¬†c †ca car art rti tin ina na  a t  to tor orn rna nas aso sol ole le  e #  #3 #35 350 50  0 -  -  - f  fi fis ish sh  h d  da day ay, y,  , t  ti tim ime me  e e  es esc sca cap ape pes es. s.  . (  (s (sp spe pec eci cia ial al  l e  ed edi dit iti tio ion on  n c  ce cel ele leb ebr bra rat ati tin ing ng  g t  th the he  e 3  35 350 50t 0th th  h p  po pos ost st) t)  ) -  -  - c  ca car arp rpe pe  e d  di die iem em  m t  te tem emp mpu pus us  s f  fu fug ugi git it  t #  #3 #35 351 51  1 -  -  - o  on oni nio ion on  n w  we wea ear ari rin ing ng. g.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f c  c. c.  . g  ga gat att tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - v  ve ves est sti tir irs rsi si  i a  a  a c  ci cip ipo pol oll lla la  a i  i  i l  li lik ike ked ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o m  mo mo? o?d ?d? d?e ?er er  r d  da dan ani nie iel els lss sso son on  n f  fr fre res esc sco co  o "  "a "af afr fri ric ica ca" a"  " #  #3 #35 355 55  5 -  -  - a  at at  t t  th the he  e b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l b  be bet ett tte ter er. r.  . -  -  - a  al all lla la  a b  be bel ell ll‚ l‚Ä ‚Äô Äôe ôe  e m  me meg egl gli lio io  o #  #3 #35 356 56  6 -  -  - s  st sta tay ay  y s  su sun unn nny ny. y.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f m  m. m.  . z  za zam amp mpo pol oll llo lo) o)  ) -  -  - s  st sta tai ai  i s  se ser ere ren eno no  o #  #3 #35 357 57  7 -  -  - i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôm ôm  m a  at at  t t  th the he  e t  ta tak ake ken en  n w  wi wit ith th‚ h‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ -  -  - s  so son ono no  o a  al all lle le  e p  pr pre res ese se  e c  co con on‚ n‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ #  #3 #35 358 58  8 -  -  - m  me me  e h  ha has as  s p  pu put ut  t t  th the he  e w  wa wal alk lki kin ing ng  g s  st sti tic ick cks ks  s b  be bet etw twe wee een en  n t  th the he  e w  wh whe hee eel els ls. s.  . -  -  - m  mi mi  i h  ha ha  a m  me mes ess sso so  o i  i  i b  ba bas ast sto ton oni ni  i f  fr fra ra  a l  le le  e r  ru ruo uot ote te  e #  #3 #36 360 60  0 -  -  - t  th the he  e b  br bra ran and nd  d o  of of  f b  bu bub ubb bbl ble le. e.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - l  la la  a m  ma mar arc rca ca  a d  da da  a b  bo bol oll llo lo  o #  #3 #36 361 61  1 -  -  - a  at at  t m  me mer erm rma mai aid ids ds  s e  ex exp xpl pla lai ain ine ned ed. d.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . m  m. m.  . z  za zam amp mpo pol oll llo lo) o)  ) -  -  - a  a  a s  si sir ire ren ene ne  e s  sp spi pie ieg ega gat ate te  e #  #3 #36 362 62  2 -  -  - a  at at  t h  ha han and ndc dcu cuf uff ffs fs. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f m  m. m.  . z  za zam amp mpo pol oll llo lo) o)  ) -  -  - a  a  a m  ma man ane net ett tta ta  a #  #3 #36 363 63  3 -  -  - d  da day ay  y o  of of  f t  th the he  e g  gr gra rac ace ce  e c  ch chi hin in  n a  ag aga gai ain in. n.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti  i f  fe fea eat at. t.  . m  m. m.  . z  za zam amp mpo pol oll llo lo) o)  ) -  -  - g  gi gio ior orn rno no  o d  de del el. l.. ... ..  . #  #3 #36 364 64  4 -  -  - h  ho hol old ld  d o  of of  f e  ey eye ye. e.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - t  ti tie ien eni ni  i d  d‚ d‚Ä ‚Äô Äôo ôoc occ cch chi hio io  o #  #3 #36 365 65  5 -  -  - s  st sto top op  p s  st sta tay ayi yin ing ng‚ g‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ -  -  - f  fe fer erm rmo mo  o r  re res est sta tan and ndo do‚ o‚Ä ‚Ä¶ Ä¶  ¶ #  #3 #36 366 66  6 -  -  - t  th the her ere re‚ e‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s w  wa wat ate ter erf rfa fal all ll. l.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of. f.  . s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - c  c‚ c‚Ä ‚Äô Äô√ ô√® √®  ® c  ca cas asc sca cat ata ta  a #  #3 #36 367 67  7 -  -  - p  po pop ope pe‚ e‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s p  po pop ope pe‚ e‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - p  pa pap apa pal ale le  e p  pa pap apa pal ale le  e #  #3 #36 368 68  8 -  -  - e  ey eye ye  e d  do doe oes esn sn‚ n‚Ä ‚Äô Äôt ôt  t s  se see ee  e h  he hea ear art rt  t d  do doe oes esn sn‚ n‚Ä ‚Äô Äôt ôt  t h  hu hur urt rt. t.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f t  t. t.  . l  lo los osc sch chi hi) i)  ) -  -  - o  oc occ cch chi hi  i n  no non on  n v  ve ved ede de  e c  cu cuo uor ore re  e n  no non on  n d  du duo uol ole le  e #  #3 #36 369 69  9 -  -  - i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôm ôm  m a  at at  t t  th the he  e j  jo joi oin int nt  t o  of of  f g  ga gas as. s.  . -  -  - s  so son ono no  o a  al all lla la  a c  ca can ann nna na  a d  de del el  l g  ga gas as  s #  #3 #37 371 71  1 -  -  - w  wa wai ait it  t a  an and nd  d h  ho hop ope pe. e.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - a  as asp spe pet ett tta ta  a e  e  e s  sp spe per era ra  a i  i  i l  li lik ike ked ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o m  ma mar arc rc  c r  ri rib ibo bot ot' t's 's  s c  ce cer era ram ami mic ic  c d  do dog og  g -  -  - l  li lie ies es  s m  my my  y b  bo bod ody dy  y t  to tol old ld  d m  me me  e #  #3 #37 374 74  4 -  -  - a  am amo mou oun unt nts ts  s t  th thr hro row owi win ing ng. g.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - t  ti tir ira rar are re  e l  le le  e s  so som omm mme me  e #  #3 #37 375 75  5 -  -  - n  ne ner erv rve ves es  s a  at at  t f  fl flo low owe wer er  r o  of of  f s  sk ski kin in. n.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - n  ne ner erv rvi vi  i a  a  a f  fi fio ior or  r d  di di  i p  pe pel ell lle le  e i  i  i l  li lik ike ked ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o j  ja jaz azz zze zed ed  d o  ou out ut  t o  os osl slo lo  o -  -  - d  da day ays ys  s i  in int nto to  o n  no nor orw rwe weg egi gia ian an  n j  ja jaz azz zz  z #  #3 #37 376 76  6 -  -  - w  wh whe hen en  n i  i‚ i‚Ä ‚Äô Äôm ôm  m h  ho hom ome me  e i  i  i h  hi hit it  t y  yo you ou  u w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the he  e p  ph pho hon one ne. e.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f h  hi his is  s m  ma maj aje jes est sty ty  y r  r. r.  . d  de del el  l n  ne ner ero ro) o)  ) -  -  - q  qu qua uan and ndo do  o s  so son ono no  o a  a  a c  ca cas asa sa  a t  ti ti. i.. ... ..  . #  #3 #37 378 78  8 -  -  - d  do don on‚ n‚Ä ‚Äô Äôt ôt  t d  do do  o t  th the he  e f  fa fal all lli lin ing ngd gde dea ead ad. d.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . a  am ame men end ndo dol ola lag agi gin ine ne) e)  ) -  -  - n  no non on  n f  fa far are re  e i  il il  l c  ca cas asc sca cam amo mor ort rto to¬ o¬† ¬†  † #  #3 #37 379 79  9 -  -  - l  li lik ike ke  e i  if if  f n  no not oth thi hin ing ng  g i  it it  t w  wo wou oul uld ld  d b  be be. e.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  co com ome me  e s  se se  e n  ni nie ien ent nte te  e f  fo fos oss sse se  e i  i  i l  li lik ike ked ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o h  hi him ima mal ala lay aya ya  a s  sp spe pee eed ed  d p  pa par art rt  t 2  2: 2:  : c  cl cli lim imb mbi bin ing ng  g c  ch cho hol ola lat ats tse se  e #  #3 #38 380 80  0 -  -  - b  bu buy uyp ypu put ut. t.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f c  c. c.  . g  ga gat att tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  co com omp mpr pro rom ome mes ess sso so  o #  #3 #38 381 81  1 -  -  - i  it it  t m  ma mak ake kes es  s m  me me  e f  fr fro rot oth thi hin ing ng. g.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - m  mi mi  i f  fa fa  a s  sc sch chi hiu ium uma mar are re  e #  #3 #38 382 82  2 -  -  - a  as ass ss  s a  an and nd  d s  sh shi hir irt rt. t.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  cu cul ulo lo  o e  e  e c  ca cam ami mic ici cia ia  a #  #3 #38 383 83  3 -  -  - e  ev eve ver ery ry  y h  ho hol ole le  e i  is is  s t  tu tun unn nne nel el. l.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f r  r. r.  . b  bi big igi gio iol oll lli li) i)  ) -  -  - o  og ogn gni ni  i b  bu buc uco co  o √  √® √®  ® g  ga gal all lle ler eri ria ia  a #  #3 #38 385 85  5 -  -  - w  we we  e a  ar are re  e c  ch cha har arg rge ged ed! d!  ! (  (d (d. d.  . g  ge ger eru rus uss ssi si  i f  fe fea eat at. t.  . w  w. w.  . a  an ang nge gel eli lin ini ni) i)  ) -  -  - s  si sia iam amo mo  o c  ca car ari ric ich chi hi! i!  ! #  #3 #38 386 86  6 -  -  - t  th the hey ey  y a  ar are re  e a  al all ll  l f  fe fen enn nne nel els ls  s w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the he  e o  ot oth the her ers rs‚ s‚Ä ‚Äô Äô  ô a  as ass sse ses es. s.  . -  -  - s  so son on  n t  tu tut utt tti ti  i f  fi fin ino noc occ cch chi hi  i c  co col ol  l c  cu cul ulo lo  o d  de deg egl gli li  i a  al alt ltr tri ri  i #  #3 #38 388 88  8 -  -  - a  at at  t b  bu bur urn rn  n f  fu fur ur. r.  . -  -  - a  a  a b  br bru ruc uci cia ia  a p  pe pel elo lo  o i  i  i l  li lik ike ked ed  d a  a  a v  vi vid ide deo eo  o m  mt mt  t e  ev eve ver ere res est st  t i  im ima max ax  x -  -  - t  th the he  e d  dr dre rea eam am  m i  is is  s a  al ali liv ive ve  e #  #3 #38 389 89  9 -  -  - f  fr fro rom om  m w  wh whe hen en  n t  to to  o h  he her ere re! e!? !?  ? -  -  - d  da da  a q  qu qua uan and ndo do  o i  in in  n q  qu qua ua! a!? !?  ? #  #3 #39 390 90  0 -  -  - a  a  a l  lo lot ot  t o  of of  f s  st stu tuf uff ff! f!  ! (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . a  am ame men end ndo dol ola lag agi gin ine ne) e)  ) -  -  - t  ta tan ant nta ta  a r  ro rob oba ba! a!  ! #  #3 #39 391 91  1 -  -  - f  fr fro rom om  m t  th the her ere re  e t  to to  o l  li lit itt ttl tle le. e.  . -  -  - d  di di  i l  l√ l√¨ √¨  ¨ a  a  a p  po poc oco co  o #  #3 #39 392 92  2 -  -  - s  sm smi mil ili lin ing ng  g t  ti tin iny ny  y c  ci cit ity ty. y.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - r  ri rid ide den ent nte te  e c  ci cit itt tta tad adi din ina na  a #  #3 #39 393 93  3 -  -  - f  fu fun une ner era ral al  l b  bl blo low owj wjo job obs bs. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . a  am ame men end ndo dol ola lag agi gin ine ne) e)  ) -  -  - p  po pom omp mpe pe  e f  fu fun une neb ebr bri ri  i #  #3 #39 394 94  4 -  -  - b  bi big ig  g w  wo wor ord rds ds  s a  ar are re  e f  fl fly lyi yin ing ng. g.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - v  vo vol ola lan ano no  o p  pa par aro rol ole le  e g  gr gro ros oss sse se  e #  #3 #39 395 95  5 -  -  - a  at at  t f  fr fre ree ee  e w  wh whe hee eel el. l.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - a  a  a r  ru ruo uot ota ta  a l  li lib ibe ber era ra  a #  #3 #39 396 96  6 -  -  - h  he he  e t  to too ook ok  k i  it it  t u  un und nde der er  r t  th the he  e l  le leg eg. g.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f f  f. f.  . p  pa pal all lla lav avi vid idi din ini ni) i)  ) -  -  - l  l‚ l‚Ä ‚Äô Äôh ôha ha  a p  pr pre res esa sa  a s  so sot ott tto to  o g  ga gam amb mba ba  a #  #3 #39 397 97  7 -  -  - t  to to  o o  ow owl wl. l.  . -  -  - g  gu guf ufa far are re  e #  #3 #39 398 98  8 -  -  - t  th the he  e d  dr dro rop op  p t  th tha hat at  t m  ma mak ake kes es  s b  be bet etw twe wee een enm nmo mou out uth th  h t  th the he  e v  va vas ase se. e.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - l  la la  a g  go goc occ cci cia ia  a c  ch che he  e f  fa fa  a t  tr tra rab abo boc occ cca car are re  e i  il il. l.. ... ..  . #  #4 #40 400 00  0 -  -  - w  wo wol olf lf  f i  in in  n t  ta tal ale le. e.  . (  (s (sp spe pec eci cia ial al  l e  ed edi dit iti tio ion on  n c  ce cel ele leb ebr bra rat ati tin ing ng  g t  th the he  e 4  40 400 00t 0th th  h p  po pos ost st) t)  ) -  -  - l  lu lup upu pus us  s i  in in  n f  fa fab abu bul ula la  a #  #4 #40 401 01  1 -  -  - a  at at  t a  al all ll  l r  ro rou oun und nd. d.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - a  a  a t  tu tut utt tto to  o t  to ton ond ndo do  o #  #4 #40 402 02  2 -  -  - t  to to  o i  in inw nwi wis ish sh. h.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - i  in ina nau aug ugu gur ura rar are re  e #  #4 #40 403 03  3 -  -  - o  on on  n e  ev eve ven eni nin ing ng‚ g‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s d  do doi oin ing ng. g.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - s  su sul ul  l f  fa far ar  r d  de del ell lla la  a s  se ser era ra  a #  #4 #40 404 04  4 -  -  - w  wh whi hit it  t t  th the he  e i  if if  f a  an and nd  d w  wi wit ith th  h t  th the he  e b  bu but ut  t y  yo you ou  u d  do don on‚ n‚Ä ‚Äô Äôt ôt  t m  ma mak ake ke  e h  hi his ist sto tor ory ry. y.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f w  w. w.  . a  an ang nge gel eli lin ini ni) i)  ) -  -  - c  co con on  n i  i  i s  se se  e e  e  e c  co con on  n i  i  i m  ma ma. a.. ... ..  . #  #4 #40 405 05  5 -  -  - i  is is  s n  no not ot  t b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l w  wh wha hat at  t i  is is  s b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l b  bu but ut  t i  is is  s b  be bea eau aut uti tif ifu ful ul  l w  wh wha hat at  t i  it it‚ t‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s l  li lik ike ked ed. d.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - n  no non on  n √  √® √®  ® b  be bel ell llo lo  o c  ci ci√ i√≤ √≤  ≤ c  ch che he  e √  √® √®  ® b  be bel ell llo lo. o.. ... ..  . #  #4 #40 406 06  6 -  -  - a  an ant nth the hem emg mgo goa oac act cti tio ion on. n.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - i  in inn nno nov ova vaz azi zio ion one ne  e #  #4 #40 408 08  8 -  -  - t  th the her ere re  e w  wa was as  s t  th the he  e h  h. h.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  ce cer era ra  a l  la lac acc cca ca  a #  #4 #40 409 09  9 -  -  - t  ta tak ake ken en  n g  go goo ood od. d.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - p  pr pre res eso so  o b  be ben ene ne  e #  #4 #41 410 10  0 -  -  - t  to to  o p  pa par are ren ent nts ts. s.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - a  ap app ppa par are ren ent nti ti  i #  #4 #41 411 11  1 -  -  - a  ai air ir‚ r‚Ä ‚Äô Äôs ôs  s r  ro roo oom om. m.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  ca cam ame mer era ra  a d  d‚ d‚Ä ‚Äô Äôa ôar ari ria ia  a #  #4 #41 412 12  2 -  -  - b  be beh ehi hin ind nd  d t  th the he  e f  fi fif ift fth ths hs. s.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - d  di die iet etr tro ro  o l  le le  e q  qu qui uin int nte te  e b  bo boo oot ots tst str tra rap ap  p p  ps psd sd: d:  : f  fr fre ree ee  e f  fo for or  r c  co com omm mme mer erc rci cia ial al  l a  an and nd  d p  pe per ers rso son ona nal al  l u  us use se! e!  ! b  by by  y #  #4 #41 416 16  6 -  -  - f  fo for or  r d  de dep epa par art rte ted ed  d t  ta tak ake ken en. n.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - p  pe per er  r p  pa par art rti tit ito to  o p  pr pre res eso so  o #  #4 #41 417 17  7 -  -  - i  is is  s l  li lik ike ke  e s  sh sho hoo oot oti tin ing ng  g o  on on  n t  th the he  e r  re red ed  d c  cr cro ros oss ss. s.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -¬ -¬† ¬†√ †√® √®  ® c  co com ome me  e s  sp spa par ara rar are re  e s  su sul ull lla la  a c  cr cro roc oce ce  e r  ro ros oss ssa sa  a #  #4 #41 418 18  8 -  -  - g  go go  o t  to to  o m  ma mak ake ke  e y  yo you our urs rse sel elf lf  f w  we wel ell lls lsa say ay. y.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f s  s. s.  . s  sp spr pre rea eaf afi fic ico co) o)  ) -  -  - v  va va‚ a‚Ä ‚Äô Äô  ô a  a  a f  fa far art rti ti  i b  be ben ene ned edi dir ire re  e #  #4 #41 419 19  9 -  -  - t  th the he  e b  bi big ig  g w  wi wiz iza zar ard rd. d.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - i  il il  l m  ma mag ago gon one ne  e #  #4 #42 423 23  3 -  -  - h  hu hun und ndr dre red eds dst sth the her ere reb ebo bor orn rn. n.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - c  ce cen ent nte tel ell lli lin ina nat ata ta  a #  #4 #42 426 26  6 -  -  - s  se sen ent nt  t i  in in  n w  wa wav ave ve. e.  . -  -  - m  ma man and nda dat ato to  o i  in in  n o  on ond nda da  a #  #4 #42 427 27  7 -  -  - t  to to  o d  dr dri rin ink nk  k a  at at  t t  th the he  e d  dr dro rop op. p.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - b  be ber ere re  e a  al all lla la  a g  go goc occ cci cia ia  a #  #4 #42 428 28  8 -  -  - a  al alw lwa way ays ys  s a  an and nd  d a  an any nyw ywa way ay. y.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - s  se sem emp mpr pre re  e e  e  e c  co com omu mun unq nqu que ue  e #  #4 #42 429 29  9 -  -  - i  if if  f y  yo you ou  u p  pu put ut  t o  on on  n t  th thi his is  s f  fl flo loo oor or. r.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - s  se se  e l  la la  a m  me met ett tti ti  i s  su su  u q  qu que ues est sto to  o p  pi pia ian ano no  o h  ho ho  o a  ag agg ggi giu iun unt nto to  o u  un un  n v  vi vid ide deo eo  o a  a  a u  un una na  a p  pl pla lay ayl yli lis ist st  t d  di di  i :  :  : k  k2 k2  2 -  -  - t  th the he  e k  ki kil ill lle ler er  r s  su sum umm mmi mit it  t (  (b (bb bbc bc  c f  fo fou our ur  r -  -  - s  st sto tor ory ryv yvi vil ill lle le  e -  -  - 2  20 201 014 14) 4)  ) #  #4 #43 433 33  3 -  -  - g  gi giv ive ve  e t  ti tim ime me  e t  to to  o w  we wea eat ath the her er. r.¬ .¬† ¬†  † -  -  - d  da dai ai  i t  te tem emp mpo po  o a  al al  l t  te tem emp mpo po  o #  #4 #43 434 34  4 -  -  - d  do do  o n  no not ot  t t  th thr hro row ow  w t  th the he  e s  st sto ton one ne  e a  an and nd  d t  th the hen en  n h  hi hid ide de  e t  th the he  e h  ha han and nd. d.  . (  (f (fe fea eat at. t.  . a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - n  no non on  n l  la lan anc nci cia iar are re  e l  la la  a p  pi pie iet etr tra ra  a e  e  e p  po poi oi. i.. ... ..  . #  #4 #43 437 37  7 -  -  - a  a  a b  ba bar arl rli lig igh ght ht. t.  . -  -  - u  un un  n b  ba bar arl rlu lum ume me  e -  -  - u  un unc nch cha hai ain ine ned ed. d.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . ‚  ‚Ä ‚Äú Äúu úun unc nch cha hai ain ine ned ed‚ d‚Ä ‚Äù Äù  ù c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - s  sc sca cat ate ten ena nat ato to  o #  #4 #44 441 41  1 -  -  - r  ro rot ott tte ten enf nfo foo oot ot. t.  . -  -  - m  ma mar arc rci cia iap api pie ied ede de  e #  #4 #44 442 42  2 -  -  - r  ra rat ath the her er  r t  ti tim ime me. e.  . (  (c (co cou our urt rte tes esy sy  y o  of of  f a  a. a.  . c  ca cas ast ste tel ell lle let ett tti ti) i)  ) -  -  - a  an anz nzi zit ite tem emp mpo po  o #  #4 #44 443 43  3 -  -  - w  wi win ind nd  d i  in in  n b  bo boo oob ob. b.  . -  -  - v  ve ven ent nto to  o i  in in  n p  po pop opp ppa pa a #313 313  13 - 3 -   - t - tu  tur turn urns rns  ns s s su  sun suns uns. ns.  s. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - g - gi  gir gira iras raso asol soli oli  li # i #3  #31 #314 314  14 - 4 -   - a - ag  aga agai gain ains inst nst  st h t ha  han hand and. nd.  d. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - c - co  con cont ontr ntro trom roma oman mano ano  no # o #3  #31 #316 316  16 - 6 -   - w - wi  wit with ith  th i h i‚  i‚Ä i‚Äô ‚Äôm Äôm  ôm b m ba  bac back ack. ck.  k. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - c - co  con cont onto ntor torn orno rno  no # o #3  #31 #317 317  17 - 7 -   - d - di  div dive ive  ve a e at  at  at t t th  the the  he h e he  hea hear eart art. rt.  t. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - t - tu  tuf tuff uffo ffo  fo a o al  al  al c l cu  cuo cuor uore ore  re # e #3  #32 #320 320  20 - 0 -   - t - ti  tin tiny iny  ny r y ro  roa roas oast ast. st.¬ t.¬† .¬†  ¬† - † -   - a - ar  arr arro rros rost osti stic tici icin cino ino  no # o #3  #32 #321 321  21 - 1 -   - a - at  at  at p t pa  pai pain ain. in.  n. - . -   - a - ap  app appe ppen pena ena  na # a #3  #32 #322 322  22 - 2 -   - p - pu  put put  ut t t th  the the  he h e ha  han hand ands nds  ds a s ah  ahe ahea head ead. ad.  d. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of s f s.  s.  s. p . pe  ped pede eder ders erse rsen sen) en)  n) - ) -   - m - me  met mett ette tter tere ere  re l e le  le  le m e ma  man mani ani  ni a i av  ava avan vant anti nti  ti # i #3  #32 #325 325  25 - 5 -   - w - wh  wha what hat  at a t a   a t a ti  tin tiny iny  ny t y ty  typ type ypef pefa efac face ace! ce!  e! ( ! (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - c - ch  che che  he c e ca  car cara arat ratt atte tter teri erin rino ino! no!  o! # ! #3  #32 #326 326  26 - 6 -   - d - do  don donk onke nkey keya eyac yact act. ct.¬ t.¬† .¬†  ¬† - † -   - m - mu  mul mula ulat latt atto tto  to # o #3  #32 #328 328  28 - 8 -   - e - en  ent ente nter tere ered red  ed a d at  at  at t t te  ten tens ens  ns l s le  leg leg. eg.  g. - . -   - e - en  ent entr ntra trat rato ato  to a o a   a g a ga  gam gamb amba mba  ba t a te  tes tesa esa  sa # a #3  #32 #329 329  29 - 9 -   - p - po  pok poke oke  ke t e to  too toot ooth oth. th.  h. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti  ti f i fe  fea feat eat. at.  t. m . m.  m.  m. e . en  eng engo ngol goll olli lli) li)  i) - ) -   - s - st  stu stuz tuzz uzzi zzic zica icad cade aden dent ente nte  te # e #3  #33 #330 330  30 - 0 -   - b - br  bri brin ring ing  ng h g ho  hom home ome  me t e th  the the  he r e re  res resu esul sult ult. lt.  t. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of g f g.  g.  g. t . to  toi toia oia) ia)  a) - ) -   - p - po  por port orta rtar tare are  re a e a   a c a ca  cas casa asa  sa i a il  il  il r l ri  ris risu isul sult ulta ltat tato ato  to # o #3  #33 #333 333  33 - 3 -   - a - at  at  at f t fa  fac face ace  ce g e ga  gar garl arli rlic lic. ic.  c. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of t f t.  t.  t. l . lo  los losc osch schi chi) hi)  i) - ) -   - a - av  avv avvi vvis visa isag sagl agli glia lia¬ ia¬† a¬†  ¬† # † #3  #33 #334 334  34 - 4 -   - r - re  re- re-a e-as -ass ass. ss.  s. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. s . s.  s.  s. p . pe  ped pede eder ders erse rsen sen) en)  n) - ) -   - r - ri  rin rinc incu ncul culo ulo  lo # o #3  #33 #335 335  35 - 5 -   - a - a   a l a lu  lum lump ump  mp a p at  at  at t t th  the the  he t e th  thr thro hroa roat oat. at.¬ t.¬† .¬†  ¬† - † -   - u - un  un  un n n no  nod nodo odo  do a o al  all alla lla  la g a go  gol gola ola  la # a #3  #33 #336 336  36 - 6 -   - h - he  he  he s e st  sta stay tays ays  ys o s on  on  on h n hi  his his. is.  s. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of s f so  som some omeo meon eone one  ne i e i   i d i do  don don‚ on‚Ä n‚Äô ‚Äôt Äôt  ôt r t re  rem reme emem memb embe mber ber) er)  r) - ) -   - s - st  sta sta  ta s a su  sul sull ulle lle  le s e su  sue sue  ue i e i   i f i fa  fav favo avor vori orit rite ited ted  ed a d a   a v a vi  vid vide ideo deo  eo l o le  les les  es l s lu  lut luth uthi thie hier iers ers  rs - s -   - p - pe  per perd erdo rdon dona onal nala ala  la ( a (b  (bo (bol bol√ ol√© l√©r √©ro ©rol rolo olo) lo)  o) # ) #3  #33 #338 338  38 - 8 -   - w - wa  wat wate ater ter  er i r in  in  in m n mo  mou mout outh uth. th.  h. - . -   - a - ac  acq acqu cqua qua  ua i a in  in  in b n bo  boc bocc occa cca  ca # a #3  #33 #339 339  39 - 9 -   - w - wi  wit with ith  th t h th  the the  he t e ti  tim time imes mes  es t s th  tha that hat  at r t ru  run runs uns. ns.  s. - . -   - c - co  coi coi  oi t i te  tem temp empi mpi  pi c i ch  che che  he c e co  cor corr orro rron rono ono  no # o #3  #34 #341 341  41 - 1 -   - y - yo  you you  ou l u li  liv live ive  ve i e it  it. it.  t. ( . (‚  (‚Ä (‚Äú ‚Äúi Äúi  úi k i kn  kno know now  ow a w a   a c a ci  cit city ity‚ ty‚Ä y‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù s ù sp  spe spec peci ecia cial ial  al e l ed  edi edit diti itio tion ion  on b n by  by  by a y a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - t - te  tel tela elav lavi aviv viv  iv # v #3  #34 #342 342  42 - 2 -   - t - th  the the  he f e fo  foo foot oot‚ ot‚Ä t‚Äô ‚Äôs Äôs  ôs t s tr  tre tree ree. ee.  e. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. b . bu  bub buba uban bani ani) ni)  i) - ) -   - l - la  la  la p a pi  pia pian iant anta nta  ta d a de  del del  el p l pi  pie pied iede ede  de # e #3  #34 #343 343  43 - 3 -   - o - ou  out out  ut r t re  rea read eads ads. ds.  s. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of s f s.  s.  s. s . sp  spr spre prea reaf eafi afic fico ico) co)  o) - ) -   - f - fu  fuo fuor uori ori  ri l i le  leg legg egge gge  ge # e #3  #34 #345 345  45 - 5 -   - i - it  it‚ it‚Ä t‚Äô ‚Äôs Äôs  ôs a s at  at  at a t a   a s a sh  sho shot hot  ot o t of  of  of g f gu  gun gun. un.  n. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of c f c.  c.  c. g . ga  gat gatt atti tti  ti f i fe  fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -¬  -¬† -¬†√ ¬†√® †√®  √® a ® a   a u a un  un  un t n ti  tir tiro iro  ro d o di  di  di s i sc  sch schi chio hiop iopp oppo ppo  po # o #3  #34 #347 347  47 - 7 -   - i - i‚  i‚Ä i‚Äô ‚Äôm Äôm  ôm b m bo  boa boat oati atin ting ing. ng.  g. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - m - mi  mi  mi s i st  sto sto  to i o im  imb imba mbar barc arca rcan cand ando ndo  do # o #3  #34 #348 348  48 - 8 -   - c - ca  car cart arti rtin tina ina  na t a to  tor torn orna rnas naso asol sole ole. le.  e. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. a . am  ame amen mend endo ndol dola olag lagi agin gine ine) ne)  e) - ) -   - l - li  lit litt ittl ttle tle  le p e pa  pap pape aper per  er c r co  com come omeb meba ebac back acks cksu ksun sun  un # n #3  #34 #348 348  48 - 8 -   - l - li  lit litt ittl ttle tle  le p e pa  pap pape aper per  er c r co  com come omeb meba ebac back acks cksu ksun sun. un.  n. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. a . am  ame amen mend endo ndol dola olag lagi agin gine ine) ne)  e) - ) -¬  -¬† -¬†c ¬†ca †car cart arti rtin tina ina  na t a to  tor torn orna rnas naso asol sole ole  le # e #3  #35 #350 350  50 - 0 -   - f - fi  fis fish ish  sh d h da  day day, ay,  y, t , ti  tim time ime  me e e es  esc esca scap cape apes pes. es.  s. ( . (s  (sp (spe spec peci ecia cial ial  al e l ed  edi edit diti itio tion ion  on c n ce  cel cele eleb lebr ebra brat rati atin ting ing  ng t g th  the the  he 3 e 35  350 350t 50th 0th  th p h po  pos post ost) st)  t) - ) -   - c - ca  car carp arpe rpe  pe d e di  die diem iem  em t m te  tem temp empu mpus pus  us f s fu  fug fugi ugit git  it # t #3  #35 #351 351  51 - 1 -   - o - on  oni onio nion ion  on w n we  wea wear eari arin ring ing. ng.  g. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of c f c.  c.  c. g . ga  gat gatt atti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - v - ve  ves vest esti stir tirs irsi rsi  si a i a   a c a ci  cip cipo ipol poll olla lla  la i a i   i l i li  lik like iked ked  ed a d a   a v a vi  vid vide ideo deo  eo m o mo  mo? mo?d o?d? ?d?e d?er ?er  er d r da  dan dani anie niel iels elss lsso sson son  on f n fr  fre fres resc esco sco  co " o "a  "af "afr afri fric rica ica" ca"  a" # " #3  #35 #355 355  55 - 5 -   - a - at  at  at t t th  the the  he b e be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul b l be  bet bett ette tter ter. er.  r. - . -   - a - al  all alla lla  la b a be  bel bell ell‚ ll‚Ä l‚Äô ‚Äôe Äôe  ôe m e me  meg megl egli glio lio  io # o #3  #35 #356 356  56 - 6 -   - s - st  sta stay tay  ay s y su  sun sunn unny nny. ny.  y. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of m f m.  m.  m. z . za  zam zamp ampo mpol poll ollo llo) lo)  o) - ) -   - s - st  sta stai tai  ai s i se  ser sere eren reno eno  no # o #3  #35 #357 357  57 - 7 -   - i - i‚  i‚Ä i‚Äô ‚Äôm Äôm  ôm a m at  at  at t t th  the the  he t e ta  tak take aken ken  en w n wi  wit with ith‚ th‚Ä h‚Ä¶ ‚Ä¶  Ä¶ - ¶ -   - s - so  son sono ono  no a o al  all alle lle  le p e pr  pre pres rese ese  se c e co  con con‚ on‚Ä n‚Ä¶ ‚Ä¶  Ä¶ # ¶ #3  #35 #358 358  58 - 8 -   - m - me  me  me h e ha  has has  as p s pu  put put  ut t t th  the the  he w e wa  wal walk alki lkin king ing  ng s g st  sti stic tick icks cks  ks b s be  bet betw etwe twee ween een  en t n th  the the  he w e wh  whe whee heel eels els. ls.  s. - . -   - m - mi  mi  mi h i ha  ha  ha m a me  mes mess esso sso  so i o i   i b i ba  bas bast asto ston toni oni  ni f i fr  fra fra  ra l a le  le  le r e ru  ruo ruot uote ote  te # e #3  #36 #360 360  60 - 0 -   - t - th  the the  he b e br  bra bran rand and  nd o d of  of  of b f bu  bub bubb ubbl bble ble. le.¬ e.¬† .¬†  ¬† - † -   - l - la  la  la m a ma  mar marc arca rca  ca d a da  da  da b a bo  bol boll ollo llo  lo # o #3  #36 #361 361  61 - 1 -   - a - at  at  at m t me  mer merm erma rmai maid aids ids  ds e s ex  exp expl xpla plai lain aine ined ned. ed.  d. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. m . m.  m.  m. z . za  zam zamp ampo mpol poll ollo llo) lo)  o) - ) -   - a - a   a s a si  sir sire iren rene ene  ne s e sp  spi spie pieg iega egat gate ate  te # e #3  #36 #362 362  62 - 2 -   - a - at  at  at h t ha  han hand andc ndcu dcuf cuff uffs ffs. fs.  s. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of m f m.  m.  m. z . za  zam zamp ampo mpol poll ollo llo) lo)  o) - ) -   - a - a   a m a ma  man mane anet nett etta tta  ta # a #3  #36 #363 363  63 - 3 -   - d - da  day day  ay o y of  of  of t f th  the the  he g e gr  gra grac race ace  ce c e ch  chi chin hin  in a n ag  aga agai gain ain. in.  n. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti  ti f i fe  fea feat eat. at.  t. m . m.  m.  m. z . za  zam zamp ampo mpol poll ollo llo) lo)  o) - ) -   - g - gi  gio gior iorn orno rno  no d o de  del del. el.. l... ...  .. # . #3  #36 #364 364  64 - 4 -   - h - ho  hol hold old  ld o d of  of  of e f ey  eye eye. ye.  e. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - t - ti  tie tien ieni eni  ni d i d‚  d‚Ä d‚Äô ‚Äôo Äôoc ôocc occh cchi chio hio  io # o #3  #36 #365 365  65 - 5 -   - s - st  sto stop top  op s p st  sta stay tayi ayin ying ing‚ ng‚Ä g‚Ä¶ ‚Ä¶  Ä¶ - ¶ -   - f - fe  fer ferm ermo rmo  mo r o re  res rest esta stan tand ando ndo‚ do‚Ä o‚Ä¶ ‚Ä¶  Ä¶ # ¶ #3  #36 #366 366  66 - 6 -   - t - th  the ther here ere‚ re‚Ä e‚Äô ‚Äôs Äôs  ôs w s wa  wat wate ater terf erfa rfal fall all. ll.  l. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of. of.  f. s . s.  s.  s. s . sp  spr spre prea reaf eafi afic fico ico) co)  o) - ) -   - c - c‚  c‚Ä c‚Äô ‚Äô√ Äô√® ô√®  √® c ® ca  cas casc asca scat cata ata  ta # a #3  #36 #367 367  67 - 7 -   - p - po  pop pope ope‚ pe‚Ä e‚Äô ‚Äôs Äôs  ôs p s po  pop pope ope‚ pe‚Ä e‚Äô ‚Äôs Äôs. ôs.  s. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of s f s.  s.  s. s . sp  spr spre prea reaf eafi afic fico ico) co)  o) - ) -   - p - pa  pap papa apal pale ale  le p e pa  pap papa apal pale ale  le # e #3  #36 #368 368  68 - 8 -   - e - ey  eye eye  ye d e do  doe does oesn esn‚ sn‚Ä n‚Äô ‚Äôt Äôt  ôt s t se  see see  ee h e he  hea hear eart art  rt d t do  doe does oesn esn‚ sn‚Ä n‚Äô ‚Äôt Äôt  ôt h t hu  hur hurt urt. rt.  t. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of t f t.  t.  t. l . lo  los losc osch schi chi) hi)  i) - ) -   - o - oc  occ occh cchi chi  hi n i no  non non  on v n ve  ved vede ede  de c e cu  cuo cuor uore ore  re n e no  non non  on d n du  duo duol uole ole  le # e #3  #36 #369 369  69 - 9 -   - i - i‚  i‚Ä i‚Äô ‚Äôm Äôm  ôm a m at  at  at t t th  the the  he j e jo  joi join oint int  nt o t of  of  of g f ga  gas gas. as.  s. - . -   - s - so  son sono ono  no a o al  all alla lla  la c a ca  can cann anna nna  na d a de  del del  el g l ga  gas gas  as # s #3  #37 #371 371  71 - 1 -   - w - wa  wai wait ait  it a t an  and and  nd h d ho  hop hope ope. pe.  e. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of s f s.  s.  s. s . sp  spr spre prea reaf eafi afic fico ico) co)  o) - ) -   - a - as  asp aspe spet pett etta tta  ta e a e   e s e sp  spe sper pera era  ra i a i   i l i li  lik like iked ked  ed a d a   a v a vi  vid vide ideo deo  eo m o ma  mar marc arc  rc r c ri  rib ribo ibot bot' ot's t's  's c s ce  cer cera eram rami amic mic  ic d c do  dog dog  og - g -   - l - li  lie lies ies  es m s my  my  my b y bo  bod body ody  dy t y to  tol told old  ld m d me  me  me # e #3  #37 #374 374  74 - 4 -   - a - am  amo amou moun ount unts nts  ts t s th  thr thro hrow rowi owin wing ing. ng.  g. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - t - ti  tir tira irar rare are  re l e le  le  le s e so  som somm omme mme  me # e #3  #37 #375 375  75 - 5 -   - n - ne  ner nerv erve rves ves  es a s at  at  at f t fl  flo flow lowe ower wer  er o r of  of  of s f sk  ski skin kin. in.  n. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - n - ne  ner nerv ervi rvi  vi a i a   a f a fi  fio fior ior  or d r di  di  di p i pe  pel pell elle lle  le i e i   i l i li  lik like iked ked  ed a d a   a v a vi  vid vide ideo deo  eo j o ja  jaz jazz azze zzed zed  ed o d ou  out out  ut o t os  osl oslo slo  lo - o -   - d - da  day days ays  ys i s in  int into nto  to n o no  nor norw orwe rweg wegi egia gian ian  an j n ja  jaz jazz azz  zz # z #3  #37 #376 376  76 - 6 -   - w - wh  whe when hen  en i n i‚  i‚Ä i‚Äô ‚Äôm Äôm  ôm h m ho  hom home ome  me i e i   i h i hi  hit hit  it y t yo  you you  ou w u wi  wit with ith  th t h th  the the  he p e ph  pho phon hone one. ne.  e. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of h f hi  his his  is m s ma  maj maje ajes jest esty sty  ty r y r.  r.  r. d . de  del del  el n l ne  ner nero ero) ro)  o) - ) -   - q - qu  qua quan uand ando ndo  do s o so  son sono ono  no a o a   a c a ca  cas casa asa  sa t a ti  ti. ti.. i... ...  .. # . #3  #37 #378 378  78 - 8 -   - d - do  don don‚ on‚Ä n‚Äô ‚Äôt Äôt  ôt d t do  do  do t o th  the the  he f e fa  fal fall alli llin ling ingd ngde gdea dead ead. ad.  d. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. a . am  ame amen mend endo ndol dola olag lagi agin gine ine) ne)  e) - ) -   - n - no  non non  on f n fa  far fare are  re i e il  il  il c l ca  cas casc asca scam camo amor mort orto rto¬ to¬† o¬†  ¬† # † #3  #37 #379 379  79 - 9 -   - l - li  lik like ike  ke i e if  if  if n f no  not noth othi thin hing ing  ng i g it  it  it w t wo  wou woul ould uld  ld b d be  be. be.  e. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - c - co  com come ome  me s e se  se  se n e ni  nie nien ient ente nte  te f e fo  fos foss osse sse  se i e i   i l i li  lik like iked ked  ed a d a   a v a vi  vid vide ideo deo  eo h o hi  him hima imal mala alay laya aya  ya s a sp  spe spee peed eed  ed p d pa  par part art  rt 2 t 2:  2:  2: c : cl  cli clim limb imbi mbin bing ing  ng c g ch  cho chol hola olat lats atse tse  se # e #3  #38 #380 380  80 - 0 -   - b - bu  buy buyp uypu yput put. ut.  t. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of c f c.  c.  c. g . ga  gat gatt atti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - c - co  com comp ompr mpro prom rome omes mess esso sso  so # o #3  #38 #381 381  81 - 1 -   - i - it  it  it m t ma  mak make akes kes  es m s me  me  me f e fr  fro frot roth othi thin hing ing. ng.  g. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - m - mi  mi  mi f i fa  fa  fa s a sc  sch schi chiu hium iuma umar mare are  re # e #3  #38 #382 382  82 - 2 -   - a - as  ass ass  ss a s an  and and  nd s d sh  shi shir hirt irt. rt.  t. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - c - cu  cul culo ulo  lo e o e   e c e ca  cam cami amic mici icia cia  ia # a #3  #38 #383 383  83 - 3 -   - e - ev  eve ever very ery  ry h y ho  hol hole ole  le i e is  is  is t s tu  tun tunn unne nnel nel. el.  l. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of r f r.  r.  r. b . bi  big bigi igio giol ioll olli lli) li)  i) - ) -   - o - og  ogn ogni gni  ni b i bu  buc buco uco  co √ o √®  √®  √® g ® ga  gal gall alle ller leri eria ria  ia # a #3  #38 #385 385  85 - 5 -   - w - we  we  we a e ar  are are  re c e ch  cha char harg arge rged ged! ed!  d! ( ! (d  (d. (d.  d. g . ge  ger geru erus russ ussi ssi  si f i fe  fea feat eat. at.  t. w . w.  w.  w. a . an  ang ange ngel geli elin lini ini) ni)  i) - ) -   - s - si  sia siam iamo amo  mo c o ca  car cari aric rich ichi chi! hi!  i! # ! #3  #38 #386 386  86 - 6 -   - t - th  the they hey  ey a y ar  are are  re a e al  all all  ll f l fe  fen fenn enne nnel nels els  ls w s wi  wit with ith  th t h th  the the  he o e ot  oth othe ther hers ers‚ rs‚Ä s‚Äô ‚Äô  Äô a ô as  ass asse sses ses. es.  s. - . -   - s - so  son son  on t n tu  tut tutt utti tti  ti f i fi  fin fino inoc nocc occh cchi chi  hi c i co  col col  ol c l cu  cul culo ulo  lo d o de  deg degl egli gli  li a i al  alt altr ltri tri  ri # i #3  #38 #388 388  88 - 8 -   - a - at  at  at b t bu  bur burn urn  rn f n fu  fur fur. ur.  r. - . -   - a - a   a b a br  bru bruc ruci ucia cia  ia p a pe  pel pelo elo  lo i o i   i l i li  lik like iked ked  ed a d a   a v a vi  vid vide ideo deo  eo m o mt  mt  mt e t ev  eve ever vere eres rest est  st i t im  ima imax max  ax - x -   - t - th  the the  he d e dr  dre drea ream eam  am i m is  is  is a s al  ali aliv live ive  ve # e #3  #38 #389 389  89 - 9 -   - f - fr  fro from rom  om w m wh  whe when hen  en t n to  to  to h o he  her here ere! re!? e!?  !? - ? -   - d - da  da  da q a qu  qua quan uand ando ndo  do i o in  in  in q n qu  qua qua! ua!? a!?  !? # ? #3  #39 #390 390  90 - 0 -   - a - a   a l a lo  lot lot  ot o t of  of  of s f st  stu stuf tuff uff! ff!  f! ( ! (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. a . am  ame amen mend endo ndol dola olag lagi agin gine ine) ne)  e) - ) -   - t - ta  tan tant anta nta  ta r a ro  rob roba oba! ba!  a! # ! #3  #39 #391 391  91 - 1 -   - f - fr  fro from rom  om t m th  the ther here ere  re t e to  to  to l o li  lit litt ittl ttle tle. le.  e. - . -   - d - di  di  di l i l√  l√¨ l√¨  √¨ a ¨ a   a p a po  poc poco oco  co # o #3  #39 #392 392  92 - 2 -   - s - sm  smi smil mili ilin ling ing  ng t g ti  tin tiny iny  ny c y ci  cit city ity. ty.  y. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - r - ri  rid ride iden dent ente nte  te c e ci  cit citt itta ttad tadi adin dina ina  na # a #3  #39 #393 393  93 - 3 -   - f - fu  fun fune uner nera eral ral  al b l bl  blo blow lowj owjo wjob jobs obs. bs.  s. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. a . am  ame amen mend endo ndol dola olag lagi agin gine ine) ne)  e) - ) -   - p - po  pom pomp ompe mpe  pe f e fu  fun fune uneb nebr ebri bri  ri # i #3  #39 #394 394  94 - 4 -   - b - bi  big big  ig w g wo  wor word ords rds  ds a s ar  are are  re f e fl  fly flyi lyin ying ing. ng.  g. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - v - vo  vol vola olan lano ano  no p o pa  par paro arol role ole  le g e gr  gro gros ross osse sse  se # e #3  #39 #395 395  95 - 5 -   - a - at  at  at f t fr  fre free ree  ee w e wh  whe whee heel eel. el.  l. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - a - a   a r a ru  ruo ruot uota ota  ta l a li  lib libe iber bera era  ra # a #3  #39 #396 396  96 - 6 -   - h - he  he  he t e to  too took ook  ok i k it  it  it u t un  und unde nder der  er t r th  the the  he l e le  leg leg. eg.  g. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of f f f.  f.  f. p . pa  pal pall alla llav lavi avid vidi idin dini ini) ni)  i) - ) -   - l - l‚  l‚Ä l‚Äô ‚Äôh Äôha ôha  ha p a pr  pre pres resa esa  sa s a so  sot sott otto tto  to g o ga  gam gamb amba mba  ba # a #3  #39 #397 397  97 - 7 -   - t - to  to  to o o ow  owl owl. wl.  l. - . -   - g - gu  guf gufa ufar fare are  re # e #3  #39 #398 398  98 - 8 -   - t - th  the the  he d e dr  dro drop rop  op t p th  tha that hat  at m t ma  mak make akes kes  es b s be  bet betw etwe twee ween eenm enmo nmou mout outh uth  th t h th  the the  he v e va  vas vase ase. se.  e. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - l - la  la  la g a go  goc gocc occi ccia cia  ia c a ch  che che  he f e fa  fa  fa t a tr  tra trab rabo aboc bocc occa ccar care are  re i e il  il. il.. l... ...  .. # . #4  #40 #400 400  00 - 0 -   - w - wo  wol wolf olf  lf i f in  in  in t n ta  tal tale ale. le.  e. ( . (s  (sp (spe spec peci ecia cial ial  al e l ed  edi edit diti itio tion ion  on c n ce  cel cele eleb lebr ebra brat rati atin ting ing  ng t g th  the the  he 4 e 40  400 400t 00th 0th  th p h po  pos post ost) st)  t) - ) -   - l - lu  lup lupu upus pus  us i s in  in  in f n fa  fab fabu abul bula ula  la # a #4  #40 #401 401  01 - 1 -   - a - at  at  at a t al  all all  ll r l ro  rou roun ound und. nd.¬ d.¬† .¬†  ¬† - † -   - a - a   a t a tu  tut tutt utto tto  to t o to  ton tond ondo ndo  do # o #4  #40 #402 402  02 - 2 -   - t - to  to  to i o in  inw inwi nwis wish ish. sh.¬ h.¬† .¬†  ¬† - † -   - i - in  ina inau naug augu ugur gura urar rare are  re # e #4  #40 #403 403  03 - 3 -   - o - on  on  on e n ev  eve even veni enin ning ing‚ ng‚Ä g‚Äô ‚Äôs Äôs  ôs d s do  doi doin oing ing. ng.  g. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of s f s.  s.  s. s . sp  spr spre prea reaf eafi afic fico ico) co)  o) - ) -   - s - su  sul sul  ul f l fa  far far  ar d r de  del dell ella lla  la s a se  ser sera era  ra # a #4  #40 #404 404  04 - 4 -   - w - wh  whi whit hit  it t t th  the the  he i e if  if  if a f an  and and  nd w d wi  wit with ith  th t h th  the the  he b e bu  but but  ut y t yo  you you  ou d u do  don don‚ on‚Ä n‚Äô ‚Äôt Äôt  ôt m t ma  mak make ake  ke h e hi  his hist isto stor tory ory. ry.  y. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of w f w.  w.  w. a . an  ang ange ngel geli elin lini ini) ni)  i) - ) -   - c - co  con con  on i n i   i s i se  se  se e e e   e c e co  con con  on i n i   i m i ma  ma. ma.. a... ...  .. # . #4  #40 #405 405  05 - 5 -   - i - is  is  is n s no  not not  ot b t be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul w l wh  wha what hat  at i t is  is  is b s be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul b l bu  but but  ut i t is  is  is b s be  bea beau eaut auti utif tifu iful ful  ul w l wh  wha what hat  at i t it  it‚ it‚Ä t‚Äô ‚Äôs Äôs  ôs l s li  lik like iked ked. ed.¬ d.¬† .¬†  ¬† - † -   - n - no  non non  on √ n √®  √®  √® b ® be  bel bell ello llo  lo c o ci  ci√ ci√≤ i√≤  √≤ c ≤ ch  che che  he √ e √®  √®  √® b ® be  bel bell ello llo. lo.. o... ...  .. # . #4  #40 #406 406  06 - 6 -   - a - an  ant anth nthe them hemg emgo mgoa goac oact acti ctio tion ion. on.  n. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - i - in  inn inno nnov nova ovaz vazi azio zion ione one  ne # e #4  #40 #408 408  08 - 8 -   - t - th  the ther here ere  re w e wa  was was  as t s th  the the  he h e h.  h.  h. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - c - ce  cer cera era  ra l a la  lac lacc acca cca  ca # a #4  #40 #409 409  09 - 9 -   - t - ta  tak take aken ken  en g n go  goo good ood. od.  d. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - p - pr  pre pres reso eso  so b o be  ben bene ene  ne # e #4  #41 #410 410  10 - 0 -   - t - to  to  to p o pa  par pare aren rent ents nts. ts.  s. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - a - ap  app appa ppar pare aren rent enti nti  ti # i #4  #41 #411 411  11 - 1 -   - a - ai  air air‚ ir‚Ä r‚Äô ‚Äôs Äôs  ôs r s ro  roo room oom. om.  m. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - c - ca  cam came amer mera era  ra d a d‚  d‚Ä d‚Äô ‚Äôa Äôar ôari aria ria  ia # a #4  #41 #412 412  12 - 2 -   - b - be  beh behi ehin hind ind  nd t d th  the the  he f e fi  fif fift ifth fths ths. hs.  s. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - d - di  die diet ietr etro tro  ro l o le  le  le q e qu  qui quin uint inte nte  te b e bo  boo boot oots otst tstr stra trap rap  ap p p ps  psd psd: sd:  d: f : fr  fre free ree  ee f e fo  for for  or c r co  com comm omme mmer merc erci rcia cial ial  al a l an  and and  nd p d pe  per pers erso rson sona onal nal  al u l us  use use! se!  e! b ! by  by  by # y #4  #41 #416 416  16 - 6 -   - f - fo  for for  or d r de  dep depa epar part arte rted ted  ed t d ta  tak take aken ken. en.  n. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - p - pe  per per  er p r pa  par part arti rtit tito ito  to p o pr  pre pres reso eso  so # o #4  #41 #417 417  17 - 7 -   - i - is  is  is l s li  lik like ike  ke s e sh  sho shoo hoot ooti otin ting ing  ng o g on  on  on t n th  the the  he r e re  red red  ed c d cr  cro cros ross oss. ss.  s. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -¬  -¬† -¬†√ ¬†√® †√®  √® c ® co  com come ome  me s e sp  spa spar para arar rare are  re s e su  sul sull ulla lla  la c a cr  cro croc roce oce  ce r e ro  ros ross ossa ssa  sa # a #4  #41 #418 418  18 - 8 -   - g - go  go  go t o to  to  to m o ma  mak make ake  ke y e yo  you your ours urse rsel self elf  lf w f we  wel well ells llsa lsay say. ay.  y. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of s f s.  s.  s. s . sp  spr spre prea reaf eafi afic fico ico) co)  o) - ) -   - v - va  va‚ va‚Ä a‚Äô ‚Äô  Äô a ô a   a f a fa  far fart arti rti  ti b i be  ben bene ened nedi edir dire ire  re # e #4  #41 #419 419  19 - 9 -   - t - th  the the  he b e bi  big big  ig w g wi  wiz wiza izar zard ard. rd.¬ d.¬† .¬†  ¬† - † -   - i - il  il  il m l ma  mag mago agon gone one  ne # e #4  #42 #423 423  23 - 3 -   - h - hu  hun hund undr ndre dred reds edst dsth sthe ther here ereb rebo ebor born orn. rn.  n. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - c - ce  cen cent ente ntel tell elli llin lina inat nata ata  ta # a #4  #42 #426 426  26 - 6 -   - s - se  sen sent ent  nt i t in  in  in w n wa  wav wave ave. ve.  e. - . -   - m - ma  man mand anda ndat dato ato  to i o in  in  in o n on  ond onda nda  da # a #4  #42 #427 427  27 - 7 -   - t - to  to  to d o dr  dri drin rink ink  nk a k at  at  at t t th  the the  he d e dr  dro drop rop. op.  p. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - b - be  ber bere ere  re a e al  all alla lla  la g a go  goc gocc occi ccia cia  ia # a #4  #42 #428 428  28 - 8 -   - a - al  alw alwa lway ways ays  ys a s an  and and  nd a d an  any anyw nywa yway way. ay.  y. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - s - se  sem semp empr mpre pre  re e e e   e c e co  com comu omun munq unqu nque que  ue # e #4  #42 #429 429  29 - 9 -   - i - if  if  if y f yo  you you  ou p u pu  put put  ut o t on  on  on t n th  thi this his  is f s fl  flo floo loor oor. or.  r. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - s - se  se  se l e la  la  la m a me  met mett etti tti  ti s i su  su  su q u qu  que ques uest esto sto  to p o pi  pia pian iano ano  no h o ho  ho  ho a o ag  agg aggi ggiu giun iunt unto nto  to u o un  un  un v n vi  vid vide ideo deo  eo a o a   a u a un  una una  na p a pl  pla play layl ayli ylis list ist  st d t di  di  di : i :   : k : k2  k2  k2 - 2 -   - t - th  the the  he k e ki  kil kill ille ller ler  er s r su  sum summ ummi mmit mit  it ( t (b  (bb (bbc bbc  bc f c fo  fou four our  ur - r -   - s - st  sto stor tory oryv ryvi yvil vill ille lle  le - e -   - 2 - 20  201 2014 014) 14)  4) # ) #4  #43 #433 433  33 - 3 -   - g - gi  giv give ive  ve t e ti  tim time ime  me t e to  to  to w o we  wea weat eath athe ther her. er.¬ r.¬† .¬†  ¬† - † -   - d - da  dai dai  ai t i te  tem temp empo mpo  po a o al  al  al t l te  tem temp empo mpo  po # o #4  #43 #434 434  34 - 4 -   - d - do  do  do n o no  not not  ot t t th  thr thro hrow row  ow t w th  the the  he s e st  sto ston tone one  ne a e an  and and  nd t d th  the then hen  en h n hi  hid hide ide  de t e th  the the  he h e ha  han hand and. nd.  d. ( . (f  (fe (fea feat eat. at.  t. a . a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - n - no  non non  on l n la  lan lanc anci ncia ciar iare are  re l e la  la  la p a pi  pie piet ietr etra tra  ra e a e   e p e po  poi poi. oi.. i... ...  .. # . #4  #43 #437 437  37 - 7 -   - a - a   a b a ba  bar barl arli rlig ligh ight ght. ht.  t. - . -   - u - un  un  un b n ba  bar barl arlu rlum lume ume  me - e -   - u - un  unc unch ncha chai hain aine ined ned. ed.  d. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. ‚ . ‚Ä  ‚Äú ‚Äúu Äúun úunc unch ncha chai hain aine ined ned‚ ed‚Ä d‚Äù ‚Äù  Äù c ù ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - s - sc  sca scat cate aten tena enat nato ato  to # o #4  #44 #441 441  41 - 1 -   - r - ro  rot rott otte tten tenf enfo nfoo foot oot. ot.  t. - . -   - m - ma  mar marc arci rcia ciap iapi apie pied iede ede  de # e #4  #44 #442 442  42 - 2 -   - r - ra  rat rath athe ther her  er t r ti  tim time ime. me.  e. ( . (c  (co (cou cour ourt urte rtes tesy esy  sy o y of  of  of a f a.  a.  a. c . ca  cas cast aste stel tell elle llet lett etti tti) ti)  i) - ) -   - a - an  anz anzi nzit zite item temp empo mpo  po # o #4  #44 #443 443  43 - 3 -   - w - wi  win wind ind  nd i d in  in  in b n bo  boo boob oob. ob.  b. - . -   - v - ve  ven vent ento nto  to i o in  in  in p n po  pop popp oppa ppa pa a 